<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<!--© The Office of the High Commisioner for Human Rights-->
<udhr xmlns="http://www.unhchr.ch/udhr" iso639-3="san" xml:lang="sa-Mahj" key="san_mahj" n="Sanskrit (Mahajani)" dir="ltr" iso15924="Mahj"><note><para>𑅬𑅐𑅧𑅯𑅐𑅦𑅑𑅕𑅐𑅭𑅐𑅢𑅐𑅧 𑅛𑅐𑅗𑅣-𑅐𑅫𑅑𑅘𑅔𑅖𑅳𑅢𑅐𑅛𑅐𑅱 𑅨𑅧𑅙𑅐𑅰𑅳𑅣𑅣𑅬𑅐 𑅯𑅭𑅖𑅳𑅨𑅒𑅭𑅣𑅑𑅱।</para>
      <para>1948-1998</para>
      <para>𑅬𑅐𑅧𑅯𑅐𑅦𑅑𑅕𑅐𑅭𑅐𑅢𑅐𑅧 𑅛𑅐𑅗𑅣-𑅐𑅫𑅑𑅘𑅔𑅖𑅳𑅢𑅐 {𑅐𑅧𑅛-𑅫𑅐𑅖𑅳𑅐-𑅭𑅒𑅨𑅐𑅧𑅣𑅭𑅐𑅢𑅑 𑅰𑅐𑅬𑅗𑅭𑅛𑅰𑅳𑅙}</para>
      <para>𑅓𑅣𑅙𑅚𑅣𑅐𑅪𑅥𑅰𑅛 𑅐𑅖𑅳𑅞𑅙𑅣𑅯𑅐𑅭𑅑𑅧𑅰𑅳𑅣𑅣𑅬𑅓 𑅯𑅭𑅖𑅳𑅓 𑅠𑅑𑅰𑅓𑅬𑅪𑅭-𑅬𑅐𑅰𑅓 𑅐𑅫𑅛𑅒𑅨𑅗𑅣𑅱 𑅐𑅫𑅑𑅘𑅔𑅖𑅳𑅑𑅣𑅰𑅳𑅙, 𑅬𑅱𑅐𑅰𑅫𑅐𑅛𑅐𑅱 217-𑅐-{3}-𑅑𑅣𑅛𑅐𑅖𑅛𑅱 𑅨𑅭𑅰𑅣𑅐𑅯𑅱।</para>
   </note>
   <preamble><title>𑅨𑅭𑅰𑅣𑅐𑅯𑅧𑅐</title>
      <para>𑅛𑅣𑅭 𑅛𑅗𑅣𑅑 𑅰𑅳𑅐𑅧𑅣𑅑-𑅧𑅛𑅐𑅛-𑅰𑅯𑅐𑅣𑅧𑅣𑅭𑅛𑅐𑅢𑅐𑅧 𑅐𑅦𑅐𑅭𑅱 𑅬𑅐𑅧𑅯-𑅨𑅭𑅑𑅯𑅐𑅭𑅰𑅛 𑅰𑅭𑅯𑅓𑅖𑅳𑅐𑅬𑅨𑅑 𑅰𑅥𑅰𑅛𑅐𑅧𑅐𑅧 𑅰𑅐𑅬𑅛𑅐𑅧𑅐𑅧 𑅐𑅖𑅢𑅠𑅑𑅣𑅐𑅧𑅐𑅝𑅙 𑅐𑅦𑅑𑅕𑅐𑅭𑅐𑅢𑅐𑅧, 𑅨𑅐𑅭𑅬𑅨𑅭𑅑𑅕-𑅗𑅒𑅭𑅯𑅰𑅛 𑅙𑅐𑅫𑅑𑅛𑅝𑅐𑅧𑅓 𑅰𑅛𑅐𑅣,𑅛𑅣𑅭 𑅬𑅐𑅧𑅯𑅐𑅦𑅑𑅕𑅐𑅭𑅐𑅢𑅐𑅧 𑅐𑅯𑅬𑅐𑅧𑅓𑅧 𑅐𑅧𑅐𑅥𑅭𑅓𑅢 𑅙 𑅕𑅐𑅭𑅛𑅐𑅢𑅑 𑅥𑅒𑅭𑅥𑅐𑅧𑅣𑅭𑅒𑅨𑅓𑅢 𑅨𑅭𑅑𑅢𑅬𑅑𑅣𑅐𑅧𑅑, 𑅛𑅑𑅱 𑅬𑅐𑅧𑅯𑅑𑅛-𑅙𑅓𑅣𑅧𑅐 𑅯𑅑𑅕𑅖𑅳𑅔𑅫𑅑𑅣𑅐, 𑅐𑅨𑅑 𑅙,𑅰𑅐𑅬𑅐𑅧𑅛-𑅛𑅧𑅐𑅧𑅐𑅧 𑅒𑅙𑅙𑅣𑅬𑅐𑅕𑅐𑅧𑅕𑅖𑅳𑅐𑅱 𑅐𑅫𑅑𑅘𑅔𑅖𑅳𑅑𑅣𑅐𑅱 𑅰𑅛𑅒𑅱, 𑅓𑅯𑅧 𑅱𑅑 𑅧𑅒𑅣𑅧𑅯𑅑𑅰𑅳𑅯𑅐𑅭𑅧𑅫𑅓𑅢, 𑅬𑅐𑅧𑅯𑅐𑅱 𑅐𑅫𑅑𑅯𑅛𑅕𑅣𑅓𑅱 𑅰𑅯𑅐𑅣𑅧𑅣𑅭𑅛𑅬𑅧𑅒𑅫𑅯𑅑𑅣𑅒𑅧 𑅰𑅳𑅕𑅖𑅳𑅛𑅧𑅣𑅑, 𑅧𑅑𑅭𑅫𑅛𑅐𑅰𑅳𑅙 𑅫𑅯𑅑𑅣𑅐𑅭𑅱, 𑅛𑅣𑅭 𑅙𑅑𑅣𑅣 𑅐𑅧𑅑𑅯𑅐𑅭𑅛𑅬 𑅛𑅥𑅑 𑅰𑅳𑅔𑅖𑅳𑅢𑅐𑅣𑅛𑅐𑅙𑅐𑅭𑅐𑅧 𑅯𑅑𑅭𑅒𑅦𑅛 𑅐𑅧𑅣𑅑𑅬-𑅨𑅭𑅛𑅐𑅰𑅣𑅯𑅓𑅧 𑅬𑅧𑅒𑅖𑅳𑅛𑅱, 𑅨𑅭𑅛𑅐𑅰𑅐𑅧𑅒𑅖𑅳𑅟𑅐𑅧𑅐𑅭𑅤𑅧 𑅧𑅑𑅯 𑅯𑅑𑅯𑅰𑅳𑅑𑅕𑅭𑅑𑅛𑅣𑅓 𑅙𑅓𑅣𑅣𑅥𑅐, 𑅬𑅐𑅧𑅯𑅐𑅦𑅑𑅕𑅐𑅭𑅐𑅱 𑅯𑅑𑅦𑅑-𑅧𑅑𑅛𑅬𑅓𑅧 𑅰𑅧𑅭𑅕𑅖𑅳𑅢𑅑𑅛𑅐𑅱,𑅛𑅣𑅭 𑅙 𑅭𑅐𑅖𑅳𑅞𑅭𑅓𑅖𑅳𑅒 𑅨𑅭𑅰𑅨𑅭𑅧 𑅰𑅖𑅛-𑅰𑅬𑅪𑅧𑅦𑅐𑅧𑅐𑅧 𑅯𑅑𑅕𑅐𑅰𑅛𑅐𑅣𑅧 𑅰𑅬𑅒𑅧𑅧𑅓𑅣𑅒𑅧 𑅨𑅭𑅬𑅐𑅯𑅰𑅳𑅛𑅕𑅧 𑅰𑅛𑅐𑅣,𑅛𑅣𑅭 𑅬𑅒𑅮𑅑𑅕𑅓𑅖𑅳𑅒 𑅬𑅐𑅧𑅯𑅐𑅦𑅑𑅕𑅐𑅭𑅓𑅖𑅳𑅒 𑅰𑅧𑅛𑅒𑅕𑅣-𑅭𑅐𑅖𑅳𑅞𑅭-𑅰𑅧𑅘𑅰𑅛 𑅛𑅧𑅐𑅱 𑅘𑅔𑅖𑅳𑅢𑅐𑅨𑅣𑅭𑅓 𑅰𑅯𑅑𑅛𑅐𑅰𑅤𑅐𑅧 𑅥𑅭𑅒𑅡𑅳𑅑𑅕𑅭𑅒𑅣𑅯𑅧𑅣𑅱, 𑅪𑅭𑅒𑅱𑅣𑅣𑅭𑅓 𑅙 𑅰𑅯𑅐𑅣𑅧𑅣𑅭𑅛𑅓 𑅫𑅥𑅭𑅣𑅭𑅧 𑅛𑅑𑅯𑅧𑅰𑅣𑅭𑅧 𑅰𑅐𑅬𑅐𑅛𑅑𑅕-𑅨𑅭𑅗𑅣𑅑𑅧 𑅙 𑅰𑅬𑅒𑅧𑅧𑅓𑅣𑅒𑅧 𑅧𑅑𑅭𑅢𑅑𑅣𑅬, 𑅰𑅣𑅭𑅑-𑅨𑅒𑅭𑅒𑅖𑅳𑅐𑅢𑅐𑅧 𑅰𑅐𑅬𑅛𑅐𑅦𑅑𑅕𑅐𑅭𑅓𑅖𑅳𑅒 𑅬𑅐𑅧𑅯-𑅯𑅛𑅕𑅣𑅓𑅱 𑅗𑅒𑅭𑅯𑅓 𑅬𑅒𑅮𑅛𑅓 𑅙 𑅧𑅑𑅖𑅳𑅟𑅐 𑅥𑅭𑅒𑅡𑅳𑅑𑅕𑅭𑅒𑅣𑅐,𑅛𑅣𑅭, 𑅰𑅥𑅰𑅛𑅥𑅓𑅰𑅳𑅐𑅱 𑅬𑅒𑅮𑅑𑅕-𑅰𑅯𑅐𑅣𑅧𑅝𑅛𑅐𑅢𑅐𑅧 𑅬𑅐𑅧𑅯𑅐𑅦𑅑𑅕𑅐𑅭𑅐𑅢𑅐𑅝𑅙 𑅨𑅭𑅑𑅨𑅐𑅮𑅧𑅐𑅭𑅤𑅧 𑅯𑅑𑅰𑅳𑅯𑅑𑅕𑅐𑅥𑅭𑅰𑅛 𑅰𑅬𑅒𑅧𑅧𑅣𑅛𑅓 𑅙, 𑅰𑅧𑅛𑅒𑅕𑅣-𑅭𑅐𑅖𑅳𑅞𑅭-𑅰𑅧𑅘𑅓𑅧 𑅰𑅧𑅫𑅒𑅛 𑅨𑅭𑅣𑅑𑅰𑅳𑅭𑅒𑅣𑅐𑅱 𑅰𑅛𑅒𑅱,𑅛𑅣𑅭 𑅰𑅯𑅑𑅛-𑅨𑅭𑅣𑅑𑅰𑅳𑅭𑅒𑅣𑅑𑅧𑅐𑅧 𑅨𑅭𑅑𑅨𑅒𑅭𑅢𑅣𑅐𑅛𑅑 𑅓𑅣𑅓𑅖𑅳𑅐𑅧 𑅐𑅦𑅑𑅕𑅐𑅭𑅐𑅢𑅐𑅧𑅰𑅯𑅐𑅣𑅧𑅣𑅭𑅛𑅐𑅢𑅐𑅧 𑅙 𑅰𑅐𑅬𑅐𑅧𑅛𑅐𑅯𑅗𑅬𑅧𑅧 𑅬𑅱𑅣𑅣𑅬𑅧 𑅬𑅱𑅣𑅣𑅯𑅐𑅦𑅐𑅛𑅑 𑅙 𑅰𑅛𑅐𑅣,𑅣𑅥𑅭𑅤𑅧 𑅰𑅐𑅬𑅨𑅭𑅣𑅬,𑅬𑅱𑅐𑅰𑅫𑅐 𑅰𑅭𑅯𑅓𑅖𑅳𑅐𑅧 𑅭𑅐𑅖𑅳𑅞𑅭𑅐𑅢𑅐𑅧 𑅰𑅭𑅯𑅓𑅖𑅳𑅐𑅧 𑅙 𑅛𑅧𑅐𑅧𑅐𑅧 𑅕𑅭𑅒𑅣𑅓 𑅰𑅐𑅬𑅐𑅧𑅛𑅔𑅨𑅮𑅪𑅦𑅑-𑅰𑅣𑅭-𑅭𑅒𑅨𑅓𑅢 𑅬𑅐𑅧𑅯𑅐𑅦𑅑𑅕𑅐𑅭𑅐𑅢𑅐𑅧 𑅓𑅧𑅐𑅧 𑅛𑅐𑅗𑅣𑅐𑅫𑅑𑅘𑅔𑅖𑅳𑅢𑅐𑅧 𑅐𑅫𑅑𑅘𑅔𑅖𑅳𑅛𑅣𑅑। 𑅰𑅬𑅐𑅛𑅰𑅛 𑅨𑅭𑅣𑅛𑅓𑅕𑅬𑅨𑅑 𑅐𑅧𑅗𑅬, 𑅨𑅭𑅣𑅛𑅓𑅕𑅬𑅨𑅑 𑅛𑅧𑅱, 𑅬𑅧𑅰𑅑 𑅰𑅣𑅣𑅧 𑅐𑅫𑅑𑅘𑅔𑅖𑅳𑅢𑅐𑅬𑅓𑅧𑅐𑅧 𑅧𑅑𑅦𑅐𑅛, 𑅓𑅣𑅓𑅖𑅳𑅐𑅧 𑅐𑅦𑅑𑅕𑅐𑅭𑅐𑅢𑅐𑅧𑅰𑅯𑅐𑅣𑅧𑅣𑅭𑅛𑅐𑅢𑅐𑅧 𑅙 𑅕𑅭𑅒𑅣𑅓 𑅰𑅬𑅬𑅐𑅧𑅧 𑅰𑅬𑅒𑅧𑅧𑅓𑅣𑅒𑅧 𑅰𑅳𑅑𑅕𑅖𑅳𑅐𑅦𑅛𑅐𑅨𑅧𑅐𑅭𑅤𑅧 𑅨𑅭𑅛𑅣𑅑𑅖𑅳𑅛𑅣𑅓, 𑅐𑅨𑅑 𑅙, 𑅰𑅯𑅑𑅛-𑅕𑅖𑅳𑅓𑅣𑅭𑅐𑅦𑅑𑅕𑅐𑅭𑅐𑅧𑅣𑅭𑅗𑅣𑅧 𑅕𑅖𑅳𑅓𑅣𑅭𑅯𑅐𑅰𑅣𑅯𑅛𑅓𑅖𑅳𑅒 𑅛𑅧𑅓𑅖𑅳𑅒 𑅰𑅯𑅓𑅖𑅳𑅒 𑅙 𑅰𑅥𑅰𑅛𑅥𑅓𑅰𑅳𑅓𑅖𑅳𑅒 𑅣𑅥𑅑𑅛𑅓𑅖𑅳𑅒 𑅛𑅧𑅓𑅖𑅳𑅒 𑅙 𑅰𑅯𑅑𑅛-𑅯𑅑𑅰𑅳𑅯𑅑𑅕-𑅨𑅭𑅫𑅐𑅯𑅑-𑅨𑅭𑅑𑅨𑅐𑅮𑅧𑅐𑅫𑅛𑅒𑅨𑅗𑅬𑅧𑅐𑅧𑅑 𑅰𑅧𑅭𑅕𑅖𑅳𑅑𑅣𑅒𑅧 𑅐𑅧𑅣𑅐𑅭𑅐𑅖𑅳𑅞𑅭𑅑𑅕𑅐𑅢𑅐𑅧 𑅭𑅐𑅖𑅳𑅞𑅭𑅑𑅕𑅐𑅢𑅐𑅝𑅙 𑅨𑅭𑅗𑅣𑅑𑅰𑅳𑅑𑅮𑅔𑅨𑅐𑅛𑅐𑅧𑅐𑅧 𑅙 𑅬𑅐𑅦𑅛𑅬𑅓𑅧 𑅨𑅭𑅛𑅣𑅑𑅖𑅳𑅛𑅣𑅓।</para>
   </preamble>
   <article number="1"><title>𑅐𑅧𑅒𑅙𑅚𑅓𑅥𑅱 १</title>
      <para>𑅰𑅭𑅯𑅓 𑅬𑅐𑅧𑅯𑅐𑅱 𑅰𑅯𑅣𑅧𑅣𑅭𑅐𑅱 𑅰𑅬𑅒𑅣𑅨𑅧𑅧𑅐𑅱 𑅯𑅭𑅣𑅧𑅣𑅓 𑅐𑅨𑅑 𑅙, 𑅗𑅒𑅭𑅯𑅥𑅭𑅒𑅰𑅳𑅐 𑅐𑅦𑅑𑅕𑅐𑅭𑅥𑅭𑅒𑅰𑅳𑅐 𑅙 𑅰𑅬𑅐𑅧𑅐𑅱 𑅓𑅯 𑅯𑅭𑅣𑅧𑅣𑅓। 𑅓𑅣𑅓 𑅰𑅭𑅯𑅓 𑅙𑅓𑅣𑅧𑅐-𑅣𑅭𑅕-𑅰𑅳𑅕𑅣𑅑𑅫𑅛𑅐𑅧 𑅰𑅒𑅰𑅬𑅨𑅧𑅧𑅐𑅱 𑅰𑅧𑅣𑅑। 𑅐𑅨𑅑 𑅙, 𑅰𑅭𑅯𑅓𑅨𑅑 𑅪𑅧𑅦𑅒𑅣𑅯-𑅫𑅐𑅯𑅧𑅛𑅐 𑅨𑅭𑅰𑅨𑅭𑅧 𑅯𑅛𑅯𑅱𑅭𑅧𑅣𑅒।</para>
   </article>
   <article number="2"><title>𑅐𑅧𑅒𑅙𑅚𑅓𑅥𑅱 २</title>
      <para>𑅐𑅰𑅛𑅐𑅧 𑅐𑅫𑅑𑅘𑅔𑅖𑅳𑅢𑅐𑅛𑅐𑅧 𑅧𑅑𑅭𑅥𑅑𑅖𑅳𑅞𑅐𑅱 𑅰𑅭𑅯𑅓𑅨𑅑 𑅐𑅦𑅑𑅕𑅐𑅭𑅐𑅱 𑅰𑅭𑅯𑅐𑅢𑅛𑅨𑅑 𑅙 𑅰𑅯𑅐𑅣𑅧𑅣𑅭𑅛𑅐𑅢𑅑, 𑅯𑅑𑅧𑅑𑅯 𑅛𑅐𑅣𑅑-𑅯𑅭𑅢-𑅮𑅑𑅧𑅗-𑅫𑅐𑅖𑅳𑅐-𑅦𑅭𑅬-𑅭𑅐𑅛𑅧𑅑𑅣𑅑𑅕-𑅣𑅥𑅑𑅣𑅭-𑅬𑅧𑅣𑅯𑅛𑅐𑅥𑅑-𑅫𑅓𑅥𑅬, 𑅭𑅐𑅖𑅳𑅞𑅭𑅑𑅛𑅧 𑅰𑅐𑅬𑅐𑅛𑅑𑅕𑅐𑅦𑅐𑅭𑅧 𑅰𑅬𑅨𑅛𑅛𑅧𑅬-𑅣𑅥𑅑𑅣𑅭 𑅰𑅣𑅭𑅝𑅙 𑅐𑅯𑅑𑅗𑅢𑅛𑅛, 𑅐𑅦𑅑𑅗𑅧𑅣𑅒𑅧 𑅰𑅭𑅯𑅔𑅨𑅑 𑅛𑅧𑅱 𑅨𑅭𑅫𑅯𑅣𑅑।</para>
      <para>𑅓𑅣𑅥𑅣𑅑𑅭𑅑𑅕𑅣𑅬, 𑅕𑅰𑅛𑅐𑅰𑅳𑅙𑅑𑅥𑅨𑅑 𑅨𑅭𑅫𑅒𑅰𑅣𑅣𑅐𑅛𑅐𑅱 𑅧𑅑𑅛𑅬𑅧𑅐𑅧𑅣𑅭𑅗𑅣𑅬, 𑅰𑅯𑅐𑅦𑅑𑅧𑅰𑅛 𑅐𑅣𑅬𑅨𑅭𑅰𑅳𑅐𑅰𑅧𑅓𑅣𑅭-𑅣𑅧𑅣𑅭𑅰𑅛, 𑅧𑅛𑅐𑅰𑅑𑅣𑅧𑅣𑅭𑅰𑅛 𑅯𑅐 𑅯𑅐𑅰𑅣𑅯𑅛𑅰𑅛 𑅨𑅭𑅥𑅓𑅰𑅳𑅰𑅛 𑅥𑅓𑅰𑅳𑅰𑅛 𑅯𑅐 𑅭𑅐𑅛𑅧𑅑𑅣𑅑𑅕-𑅰𑅑𑅬𑅐-𑅧𑅑𑅪𑅧𑅦𑅧𑅐𑅧𑅣𑅐𑅭𑅐𑅖𑅳𑅞𑅭𑅑𑅕-𑅰𑅣𑅭𑅐𑅦𑅐𑅭𑅓𑅢 𑅧 𑅕𑅔𑅨𑅑 𑅫𑅓𑅥𑅔 𑅯𑅑𑅦𑅐𑅰𑅛𑅣𑅓।</para>
   </article>
   <article number="3"><title>𑅐𑅧𑅒𑅙𑅚𑅓𑅥𑅱 ३</title>
      <para>𑅰𑅭𑅯𑅔𑅨𑅑 𑅛𑅧𑅱 𑅛𑅑𑅯𑅧-𑅰𑅯𑅐𑅣𑅧𑅣𑅭𑅛-𑅰𑅒𑅭𑅕𑅖𑅳𑅐𑅦𑅑𑅕𑅐𑅭𑅧 𑅰𑅧𑅦𑅣𑅣𑅓।</para>
   </article>
   <article number="4"><title>𑅐𑅧𑅒𑅙𑅚𑅓𑅥𑅱 ४</title>
      <para>𑅧 𑅕𑅬𑅨𑅑 𑅛𑅧𑅧 𑅥𑅐𑅰𑅣𑅯𑅓𑅧 𑅨𑅭𑅐𑅦𑅑𑅧𑅣𑅯𑅓𑅧 𑅯𑅐 𑅦𑅐𑅭𑅛𑅑𑅣𑅒𑅧 𑅐𑅧𑅒𑅛𑅝𑅐𑅰𑅛𑅣𑅓। 𑅐𑅨𑅑 𑅙 𑅥𑅐𑅰𑅯𑅛𑅐𑅨𑅐𑅭𑅱 𑅨𑅒𑅭𑅢𑅭𑅒𑅨𑅓𑅢 𑅨𑅭𑅣𑅑𑅖𑅳𑅑𑅥𑅦𑅱 𑅰𑅤𑅐𑅰𑅛𑅣𑅑।</para>
   </article>
   <article number="5"><title>𑅐𑅧𑅒𑅙𑅚𑅓𑅥𑅱 ५</title>
      <para>𑅧 𑅕𑅬𑅨𑅑 𑅛𑅧𑅧 𑅯𑅑𑅭𑅒𑅦𑅛 𑅐𑅯𑅬𑅐𑅧𑅧𑅐𑅣𑅬𑅕𑅧 𑅯𑅛𑅯𑅱𑅐𑅭𑅧 𑅥𑅢𑅠𑅧 𑅯𑅐 𑅕𑅭𑅒𑅭𑅧 𑅐𑅬𑅐𑅧𑅯𑅑𑅛𑅧 𑅨𑅭𑅣𑅔𑅥𑅧𑅧 𑅯𑅐 𑅨𑅭𑅯𑅭𑅣𑅛𑅑𑅣𑅒𑅧 𑅐𑅧𑅒𑅛𑅝𑅐𑅰𑅛𑅣𑅓।</para>
   </article>
   <article number="6"><title>𑅐𑅧𑅒𑅙𑅚𑅓𑅥𑅱 ६</title>
      <para>𑅯𑅑𑅦𑅓𑅱 𑅰𑅬𑅕𑅖𑅳𑅧 𑅰𑅭𑅯𑅔𑅨𑅑 𑅛𑅧𑅱 𑅰𑅭𑅯𑅣𑅭 𑅐𑅫𑅑𑅛𑅝𑅐𑅣𑅒𑅧 𑅐𑅦𑅑𑅕𑅐𑅭𑅧 𑅰𑅧𑅦𑅣𑅣𑅓।</para>
   </article>
   <article number="7"><title>𑅐𑅧𑅒𑅙𑅚𑅓𑅥𑅱 ७</title>
      <para>𑅯𑅑𑅦𑅓𑅱 𑅰𑅬𑅕𑅖𑅳𑅧 𑅰𑅭𑅯𑅓𑅨𑅑 𑅣𑅒𑅮𑅛𑅐𑅱 𑅰𑅬𑅐𑅧𑅐𑅰𑅳𑅙 𑅯𑅭𑅣𑅧𑅣𑅓। 𑅐𑅨𑅑 𑅙 𑅯𑅑𑅧𑅑𑅯 𑅕𑅬𑅨𑅑 𑅫𑅓𑅥𑅧 𑅯𑅑𑅦𑅓𑅱 𑅣𑅒𑅮𑅛𑅧 𑅰𑅧𑅭𑅕𑅖𑅳𑅢𑅬𑅯𑅐𑅨𑅣𑅒𑅧 𑅐𑅭𑅱𑅧𑅣𑅑। 𑅐𑅰𑅛𑅐𑅱 𑅐𑅫𑅑𑅘𑅔𑅖𑅳𑅢𑅐𑅛𑅐𑅱 𑅒𑅮𑅮𑅧𑅘𑅧𑅓 𑅕𑅬𑅨𑅑 𑅫𑅓𑅥𑅧, 𑅓𑅣𑅐𑅥𑅭𑅒𑅗𑅫𑅓𑅥𑅧 𑅯𑅐 𑅐𑅫𑅑𑅮𑅕𑅖𑅳𑅛 𑅕𑅐𑅬𑅨𑅑 𑅙𑅓𑅖𑅳𑅞𑅐𑅧 𑅯𑅑𑅭𑅒𑅦𑅛 𑅰𑅬𑅐𑅧-𑅰𑅧𑅭𑅕𑅖𑅳𑅢𑅐𑅭𑅱𑅐𑅱 𑅰𑅭𑅯𑅓𑅨𑅑 𑅯𑅭𑅣𑅧𑅣𑅓।</para>
   </article>
   <article number="8"><title>𑅐𑅧𑅒𑅙𑅚𑅓𑅥𑅱 ८</title>
      <para>𑅯𑅑𑅦𑅑𑅧𑅐 𑅰𑅧𑅯𑅑𑅦𑅐𑅧𑅓𑅧 𑅯𑅐 𑅨𑅭𑅥𑅣𑅣𑅐𑅧𑅐𑅧 𑅬𑅒𑅮𑅑𑅕𑅐𑅦𑅑𑅕𑅐𑅭𑅐𑅢𑅐𑅬𑅒𑅮𑅮𑅧𑅘𑅧-𑅕𑅐𑅭𑅛𑅐𑅢𑅐𑅧 𑅕𑅭𑅒𑅣𑅓, 𑅛𑅔𑅗𑅛𑅑𑅱 𑅭𑅐𑅖𑅳𑅞𑅭𑅑𑅛-𑅧𑅛𑅐𑅛𑅨𑅑𑅟𑅑𑅱 𑅰𑅧𑅰𑅣𑅒𑅣𑅐𑅧𑅐𑅧 𑅨𑅭𑅫𑅐𑅯𑅑𑅧𑅐𑅧 𑅰𑅬𑅒𑅨𑅐𑅛𑅐𑅧𑅐𑅧 𑅨𑅭𑅛𑅔𑅗𑅐𑅭𑅱𑅔 𑅱𑅑 𑅰𑅭𑅯𑅔 𑅛𑅧𑅔𑅰𑅣𑅑।</para>
   </article>
   <article number="9"><title>𑅐𑅧𑅒𑅙𑅚𑅓𑅥𑅱 ९</title>
      <para>𑅧 𑅕𑅔𑅨𑅑 𑅛𑅧𑅱 𑅰𑅯𑅓𑅙𑅚𑅛𑅐 𑅧𑅑𑅗𑅭𑅱𑅑𑅣𑅒𑅧, 𑅦𑅭𑅣𑅒𑅧, 𑅧𑅑𑅖𑅳𑅕𑅐𑅰𑅛𑅑𑅣𑅒𑅧 𑅯𑅐 𑅐𑅧𑅒𑅛𑅝𑅐𑅰𑅛𑅣𑅓।</para>
   </article>
   <article number="10"><title>𑅐𑅧𑅒𑅙𑅚𑅓𑅥𑅱 १०</title>
      <para>𑅰𑅭𑅯𑅔𑅨𑅑 𑅛𑅧𑅱, 𑅰𑅯𑅧 𑅯𑅑𑅭𑅒𑅦𑅛 𑅨𑅭𑅯𑅭𑅣𑅣𑅑𑅣𑅰𑅛 𑅕𑅰𑅛𑅐𑅨𑅑 𑅐𑅨𑅭𑅐𑅦𑅑𑅕𑅐𑅕𑅖𑅳𑅓𑅨𑅰𑅛, 𑅰𑅯𑅑𑅛𑅐𑅦𑅑𑅕𑅐𑅭𑅐𑅢𑅐𑅧 𑅥𑅐𑅛𑅑𑅣𑅯𑅐𑅧𑅐𑅧 𑅙, 𑅯𑅑𑅧𑅑𑅭𑅦𑅐𑅭𑅢𑅰𑅛 𑅙 𑅕𑅭𑅒𑅣𑅓, 𑅰𑅯𑅐𑅦𑅑𑅧𑅓𑅧 𑅧𑅑𑅖𑅳𑅨𑅕𑅖𑅳𑅓𑅢 𑅙 𑅧𑅛𑅐𑅛𑅨𑅑𑅟𑅓𑅧 𑅯𑅑𑅦𑅑𑅛𑅬𑅐𑅧𑅰𑅛 𑅰𑅬𑅒𑅙𑅑𑅣𑅰𑅛 𑅰𑅐𑅭𑅯𑅛𑅧𑅑𑅕𑅰𑅛 𑅰𑅳𑅭𑅯𑅢𑅰𑅛 𑅙 𑅕𑅭𑅒𑅣𑅓 𑅰𑅭𑅯𑅔𑅨𑅑 𑅛𑅧𑅱 𑅨𑅒𑅭𑅢𑅐𑅧 𑅰𑅬𑅐𑅧𑅣𑅐𑅧 𑅦𑅐𑅭𑅛𑅣𑅑।</para>
   </article>
   <article number="11"><title>𑅐𑅧𑅒𑅙𑅚𑅓𑅥𑅱 ११</title>
      <orderedlist><listitem tag="(१)"><para>𑅨𑅭𑅣𑅛𑅓𑅕𑅬𑅨𑅑 𑅛𑅧𑅱, 𑅯𑅑𑅦𑅓𑅭𑅧𑅒𑅰𑅐𑅭𑅓𑅢 𑅛𑅐𑅯𑅥𑅯𑅦𑅑 𑅰𑅐𑅭𑅯𑅛𑅧𑅑𑅕𑅐𑅫𑅑𑅛𑅔𑅗-𑅨𑅭𑅕𑅭𑅢𑅓 𑅨𑅭𑅬𑅒𑅖𑅐𑅨𑅭𑅐𑅦-𑅰𑅑𑅥𑅦𑅑𑅧 𑅧𑅑𑅯 𑅫𑅛𑅣𑅓, 𑅣𑅐𑅯𑅣𑅨𑅭𑅛𑅧𑅣𑅧 𑅧𑅑𑅭𑅥𑅒𑅖𑅳𑅞𑅱 𑅑𑅣𑅛𑅐𑅬𑅧𑅰𑅛𑅣𑅓। 𑅐𑅨𑅑 𑅙, 𑅰𑅯𑅑𑅛-𑅨𑅭𑅣𑅑𑅭𑅕𑅖𑅳𑅐𑅭𑅤𑅧 𑅣𑅓𑅧 𑅛𑅧𑅓𑅧 𑅰𑅭𑅯𑅬𑅨𑅑 𑅐𑅯𑅰𑅳𑅛𑅕-𑅨𑅭𑅣𑅑𑅫𑅒𑅣𑅑𑅛𑅐𑅣𑅧 𑅒𑅨𑅨𑅐𑅥𑅧𑅑𑅛𑅧 𑅯𑅭𑅣𑅣𑅓।</para>
         </listitem>
         <listitem tag="(२)"><para>𑅐𑅧𑅣𑅐𑅭𑅐𑅖𑅳𑅞𑅭𑅑𑅕𑅰𑅛 𑅭𑅐𑅖𑅳𑅞𑅭𑅑𑅕𑅰𑅛 𑅙 𑅯𑅑𑅦𑅓𑅭𑅧𑅣𑅭𑅗𑅣𑅬 𑅨𑅭𑅬𑅒𑅖𑅐𑅨𑅭𑅐𑅦-𑅧𑅑𑅖𑅳𑅨𑅭𑅫𑅐𑅯𑅕𑅰𑅛 𑅕𑅰𑅛𑅐𑅨𑅑 𑅕𑅐𑅭𑅛𑅰𑅛 𑅕𑅐𑅭𑅢𑅐𑅣 𑅧 𑅕𑅔𑅨𑅑 𑅨𑅭𑅬𑅒𑅖𑅐𑅨𑅭𑅐𑅦𑅐𑅭𑅤𑅧 𑅐𑅨𑅭𑅐𑅦𑅑𑅣𑅑 𑅗𑅢𑅛𑅑𑅖𑅳𑅛𑅣𑅓। 𑅧 𑅯𑅐, 𑅨𑅭𑅬𑅒𑅖𑅐𑅨𑅭𑅐𑅦-𑅕𑅐𑅮𑅓 𑅨𑅭𑅯𑅭𑅣𑅧𑅑𑅛-𑅥𑅢𑅠-𑅥𑅐𑅧𑅐𑅣 𑅧𑅐𑅦𑅑𑅕𑅣𑅭𑅔 𑅥𑅢𑅠𑅱 𑅕𑅰𑅬𑅑𑅧𑅰𑅳𑅙𑅑𑅥𑅨𑅑 𑅨𑅭𑅯𑅭𑅣𑅧𑅑𑅛𑅔 𑅫𑅯𑅑𑅣𑅐।</para>
         </listitem>
      </orderedlist>
   </article>
   <article number="12"><title>𑅐𑅧𑅒𑅙𑅚𑅓𑅥𑅱 १२</title>
      <para>𑅧 𑅕𑅰𑅛𑅐𑅨𑅑 𑅯𑅛𑅕𑅣𑅑𑅗𑅣𑅓 𑅨𑅐𑅭𑅑𑅯𑅐𑅭𑅑𑅕𑅓 𑅙 𑅛𑅑𑅯𑅧𑅓, 𑅗𑅭𑅒𑅱𑅓, 𑅨𑅣𑅭𑅯𑅛𑅯𑅱𑅐𑅭𑅓 𑅙 𑅰𑅯𑅓𑅙𑅚𑅛𑅐 𑅱𑅰𑅣𑅕𑅖𑅳𑅓𑅨𑅔𑅧𑅒𑅛𑅝𑅐𑅰𑅛𑅣𑅓, 𑅧 𑅯𑅐 𑅕𑅰𑅛𑅐𑅨𑅑 𑅖𑅛𑅐𑅣𑅑𑅧 𑅰𑅬𑅬𑅐𑅧𑅧 𑅯𑅐𑅕𑅭𑅐𑅧𑅣𑅒𑅧 𑅕𑅔𑅨𑅑 𑅰𑅳𑅕𑅖𑅳𑅛𑅣𑅑। 𑅓𑅣𑅐𑅱𑅕-𑅱𑅰𑅣𑅕𑅖𑅳𑅓𑅨𑅐𑅕𑅭𑅬𑅢𑅐𑅧𑅑 𑅯𑅑𑅭𑅒𑅦𑅛 𑅨𑅭𑅣𑅛𑅓𑅕𑅬𑅨𑅑-𑅛𑅧𑅱 𑅯𑅑𑅦𑅑-𑅰𑅧𑅭𑅕𑅖𑅳𑅢𑅧 𑅰𑅧𑅦𑅣𑅣𑅓।</para>
   </article>
   <article number="13"><title>𑅐𑅧𑅒𑅙𑅚𑅓𑅥𑅱 १३</title>
      <orderedlist><listitem tag="(१)"><para>𑅨𑅭𑅣𑅛𑅓𑅕𑅬𑅨𑅑 𑅭𑅐𑅖𑅳𑅞𑅭𑅰𑅛 𑅰𑅑𑅬𑅧𑅑 𑅐𑅯𑅐𑅰𑅰𑅛 𑅗𑅬𑅧𑅐𑅗𑅬𑅧𑅰𑅛 𑅙𑅰𑅯𑅐𑅣𑅧𑅣𑅭𑅛𑅐𑅦𑅑𑅕𑅐𑅭𑅧 𑅨𑅭𑅣𑅛𑅓𑅕𑅬𑅨𑅑 𑅛𑅧𑅱 𑅰𑅧𑅦𑅐𑅭𑅛𑅣𑅑।</para>
         </listitem>
         <listitem tag="(२)"><para>𑅰𑅯𑅥𑅓𑅰𑅳𑅔𑅨𑅓𑅣𑅧 𑅕𑅬𑅨𑅑 𑅥𑅓𑅰𑅳𑅧 𑅣𑅛𑅕𑅣𑅒𑅧 𑅰𑅯𑅥𑅓𑅰𑅳𑅧 𑅙 𑅨𑅭𑅣𑅛𑅐𑅗𑅧𑅣𑅒𑅧 𑅨𑅭𑅣𑅛𑅓𑅕𑅬𑅨𑅑 𑅐𑅦𑅑𑅕𑅭𑅒𑅣𑅔𑅰𑅣𑅑।</para>
         </listitem>
      </orderedlist>
   </article>
   <article number="14"><title>𑅐𑅧𑅒𑅙𑅚𑅓𑅥𑅱 १४</title>
      <orderedlist><listitem tag="(१)"><para>𑅒𑅨𑅥𑅭𑅯𑅓𑅫𑅛𑅔 𑅭𑅕𑅖𑅳𑅑𑅣𑅒𑅧 𑅐𑅧𑅛𑅥𑅓𑅰𑅳𑅓𑅖𑅳𑅒 𑅰𑅳𑅭𑅢𑅬𑅦𑅑𑅗𑅧𑅣𑅒𑅧 𑅨𑅭𑅣𑅛𑅓𑅕𑅬𑅨𑅑 𑅐𑅦𑅑𑅕𑅐𑅭𑅧 𑅰𑅧𑅦𑅣𑅣𑅓।</para>
         </listitem>
         <listitem tag="(२)"><para>𑅰𑅧𑅛𑅒𑅕𑅣𑅭𑅐𑅖𑅳𑅞𑅭𑅰𑅧𑅘𑅰𑅛 𑅰𑅑𑅥𑅦𑅐𑅧𑅣𑅐𑅧𑅐𑅧 𑅒𑅥𑅥𑅓𑅰𑅳𑅛𑅐𑅧𑅐𑅧 𑅙 𑅨𑅭𑅣𑅑𑅕𑅒𑅮𑅕𑅐𑅭𑅛𑅓𑅫𑅛𑅱 𑅭𑅐𑅛𑅧𑅑𑅣𑅑𑅕𑅓𑅣𑅭𑅐𑅨𑅭𑅐𑅦𑅓𑅫𑅛𑅰𑅳𑅙 𑅰𑅬𑅒𑅣𑅣𑅤𑅑𑅣𑅓𑅖𑅳𑅒 𑅯𑅐𑅰𑅣𑅯𑅑𑅕𑅐𑅫𑅑𑅛𑅔𑅗-𑅨𑅭𑅕𑅭𑅢𑅓𑅖𑅳𑅒 𑅐𑅦𑅑𑅕𑅐𑅭𑅔𑅛𑅧 𑅧𑅑𑅯 𑅨𑅭𑅫𑅯𑅑𑅣𑅐।</para>
         </listitem>
      </orderedlist>
   </article>
   <article number="15"><title>𑅐𑅧𑅒𑅙𑅚𑅓𑅥𑅱 १५</title>
      <orderedlist><listitem tag="(१)"><para>𑅨𑅭𑅣𑅛𑅓𑅕𑅬𑅨𑅑 𑅭𑅐𑅖𑅳𑅞𑅭𑅑𑅛𑅣𑅐𑅛𑅐𑅱 𑅐𑅦𑅑𑅕𑅐𑅭𑅧 𑅦𑅐𑅭𑅛𑅣𑅑।</para>
         </listitem>
         <listitem tag="(२)"><para>𑅧 𑅕𑅔𑅨𑅑 𑅰𑅯𑅓𑅙𑅚𑅛𑅐 𑅰𑅯𑅑𑅛𑅭𑅐𑅖𑅳𑅞𑅭𑅑𑅛𑅣𑅐𑅣𑅔 𑅯𑅝𑅙𑅑𑅣𑅱 𑅰𑅛𑅐𑅣, 𑅧 𑅯𑅐 𑅰𑅯𑅑𑅛-𑅭𑅐𑅖𑅳𑅞𑅭𑅑𑅛𑅣𑅐-𑅨𑅭𑅑𑅯𑅭𑅣𑅧𑅐𑅦𑅑𑅕𑅐𑅭𑅐𑅣 𑅨𑅭𑅣𑅛𑅐𑅖𑅛𑅐𑅣𑅔 𑅫𑅯𑅓𑅣।</para>
         </listitem>
      </orderedlist>
   </article>
   <article number="16"><title>𑅐𑅧𑅒𑅙𑅚𑅓𑅥𑅱 १६</title>
      <orderedlist><listitem tag="(१)"><para>𑅛𑅐𑅣𑅑-𑅦𑅭𑅬-𑅭𑅐𑅖𑅳𑅞𑅭𑅑𑅛𑅣𑅐-𑅧𑅑𑅛𑅬𑅧𑅧 𑅯𑅑𑅧𑅑𑅯 𑅨𑅒𑅭𑅢-𑅯𑅛𑅰𑅕𑅐𑅱 𑅰𑅣𑅭𑅑-𑅨𑅒𑅭𑅒𑅖𑅳𑅐𑅱, 𑅨𑅭𑅑𑅯𑅐𑅭𑅧 𑅨𑅭𑅣𑅑𑅖𑅳𑅟𑅐𑅨𑅛𑅑𑅣𑅒𑅧 𑅯𑅑𑅯𑅐𑅱𑅐𑅦𑅑𑅕𑅐𑅭𑅯𑅧𑅣𑅔 𑅯𑅭𑅣𑅣𑅧𑅣𑅓।</para>
         </listitem>
         <listitem tag="(२)"><para>𑅯𑅑𑅯𑅐𑅱𑅐𑅭𑅤𑅧, 𑅯𑅑𑅯𑅐𑅱𑅐𑅯𑅰𑅭𑅓, 𑅯𑅑𑅯𑅐𑅱-𑅯𑅑𑅙𑅚𑅓𑅥𑅓 𑅯𑅐 𑅣𑅓 𑅰𑅬𑅐𑅧𑅐𑅦𑅑𑅕𑅐𑅭𑅐𑅧 𑅰𑅧𑅦𑅐𑅭𑅛𑅧𑅣𑅑।</para>
         </listitem>
         <listitem tag="(३)"><para>𑅯𑅑𑅯𑅐𑅱𑅓𑅙𑅚𑅒𑅕𑅐𑅧𑅐𑅧 𑅨𑅒𑅭𑅢-𑅰𑅯𑅣𑅧𑅣𑅭-𑅰𑅱𑅬𑅣𑅛𑅑𑅯 𑅯𑅑𑅯𑅐𑅱-𑅰𑅧𑅰𑅕𑅐𑅭𑅱 𑅐𑅧𑅒𑅖𑅳𑅟𑅓𑅛𑅔𑅰𑅣𑅑।𑅨𑅭𑅑𑅯𑅐𑅭𑅰𑅣𑅒, 𑅰𑅬𑅐𑅛𑅰𑅛 𑅰𑅯𑅐𑅫𑅐𑅯𑅑𑅕𑅔 𑅬𑅒𑅮𑅑𑅕𑅰𑅳𑅙 𑅯𑅭𑅗𑅑𑅛𑅑𑅕𑅐𑅧𑅰𑅳𑅔 𑅯𑅭𑅣𑅣𑅓, 𑅐𑅨𑅑 𑅙𑅐𑅛𑅧 𑅰𑅬𑅐𑅛𑅓𑅧 𑅭𑅐𑅖𑅳𑅞𑅭𑅓𑅢 𑅯𑅐 𑅰𑅧𑅭𑅕𑅖𑅳𑅢𑅑𑅛𑅔𑅰𑅣𑅑।</para>
         </listitem>
      </orderedlist>
   </article>
   <article number="17"><title>𑅐𑅧𑅒𑅙𑅚𑅓𑅥𑅱 १७</title>
      <orderedlist><listitem tag="(१)"><para>𑅨𑅭𑅣𑅛𑅓𑅕𑅬𑅨𑅑 𑅐𑅧𑅛𑅓𑅖𑅳𑅐𑅧 𑅰𑅱𑅛𑅔𑅗-𑅨𑅒𑅭𑅰𑅰𑅭𑅧 𑅓𑅕𑅐𑅕𑅑 𑅓𑅯 𑅯𑅐 𑅰𑅬𑅨𑅣𑅰𑅧𑅦𑅐𑅭𑅢-𑅰𑅯𑅐𑅬𑅑𑅣𑅯𑅐𑅦𑅑𑅕𑅐𑅭𑅧 𑅰𑅧𑅦𑅣𑅣𑅓।</para>
         </listitem>
         <listitem tag="(२)"><para>𑅧 𑅕𑅔𑅨𑅑 𑅰𑅯𑅓𑅙𑅚𑅛𑅐 𑅰𑅯𑅑𑅛𑅰𑅧𑅨𑅣𑅰𑅯𑅐𑅬𑅑𑅣𑅯𑅐𑅦𑅑𑅕𑅐𑅭𑅐𑅣 𑅯𑅝𑅙𑅑𑅣𑅔 𑅫𑅯𑅓𑅣।</para>
         </listitem>
      </orderedlist>
   </article>
   <article number="18"><title>𑅐𑅧𑅒𑅙𑅚𑅓𑅥𑅱 १८</title>
      <para>𑅨𑅭𑅣𑅛𑅓𑅕𑅬𑅨𑅑 𑅯𑅑𑅙𑅐𑅭𑅐𑅢𑅐𑅧 𑅙𑅓𑅣𑅧𑅐𑅛𑅐𑅱 𑅦𑅭𑅬𑅰𑅛 𑅙𑅰𑅯𑅐𑅣𑅧𑅣𑅭𑅛𑅐𑅦𑅑𑅕𑅐𑅭𑅧 𑅰𑅧𑅦𑅣𑅣𑅓। 𑅐𑅰𑅬𑅑𑅧 𑅐𑅦𑅑𑅕𑅐𑅭𑅓, 𑅰𑅯𑅑𑅛𑅧 𑅦𑅭𑅬𑅧 𑅯𑅑𑅰𑅳𑅯𑅐𑅰𑅧 𑅯𑅐 𑅰𑅳𑅑𑅕𑅖𑅳𑅛𑅑𑅣𑅒𑅧 𑅐𑅫𑅛𑅰𑅣𑅒𑅧 𑅐𑅭𑅙𑅑𑅣𑅒𑅧 𑅨𑅭𑅑𑅨𑅐𑅮𑅛𑅑𑅣𑅒𑅧 𑅯𑅐, 𑅯𑅑𑅛𑅕𑅣𑅑𑅕𑅓 𑅰𑅐𑅬𑅐𑅛𑅑𑅕𑅓 𑅙 𑅛𑅑𑅯𑅧𑅓, 𑅐𑅧𑅛𑅑𑅰𑅳𑅙 𑅰𑅱 𑅰𑅐𑅬𑅒𑅥𑅐𑅛𑅑𑅕𑅛𑅑𑅯𑅧𑅓 𑅓𑅕𑅐𑅕𑅑𑅧𑅐 𑅯𑅐 𑅰𑅯𑅑𑅛𑅧 𑅦𑅭𑅬𑅧 𑅯𑅑𑅰𑅳𑅯𑅐𑅰𑅧𑅰𑅯𑅐𑅣𑅧𑅣𑅭𑅛𑅧 𑅙 𑅨𑅭𑅑𑅯𑅭𑅣𑅛𑅑𑅣𑅒𑅬𑅨𑅑 𑅨𑅭𑅣𑅛𑅓𑅕𑅧 𑅛𑅧𑅱 𑅰𑅯𑅐𑅣𑅧𑅣𑅭𑅛𑅧 𑅦𑅐𑅭𑅛𑅣𑅑।</para>
   </article>
   <article number="19"><title>𑅐𑅧𑅒𑅙𑅚𑅓𑅥𑅱 १९</title>
      <para>𑅨𑅭𑅣𑅛𑅓𑅕𑅬𑅨𑅑 𑅬𑅧𑅣𑅯𑅛𑅐𑅫𑅑𑅯𑅛𑅕𑅣𑅛𑅔𑅱 𑅐𑅦𑅑𑅕𑅐𑅭𑅧 𑅰𑅧𑅦𑅣𑅣𑅓। 𑅰𑅑𑅬𑅐𑅯𑅛𑅯𑅦𑅐𑅧𑅧 𑅐𑅯𑅑𑅗𑅢𑅛𑅛, 𑅕𑅓𑅧𑅐𑅨𑅑 𑅰𑅧𑅙𑅐𑅭-𑅬𑅐𑅦𑅛𑅬𑅓𑅧 𑅯𑅑𑅙𑅐𑅭𑅐𑅢𑅐𑅧 𑅰𑅒𑅙𑅧𑅐𑅧𑅐𑅧 𑅙 𑅐𑅥𑅐𑅧-𑅨𑅭𑅥𑅐𑅧𑅐𑅭𑅤𑅧 𑅯𑅑𑅧𑅑𑅯 𑅱𑅰𑅣𑅕𑅖𑅳𑅓𑅨𑅧 𑅕𑅑𑅰𑅳𑅙𑅥𑅨𑅑 𑅛𑅧𑅱, 𑅰𑅯𑅑𑅛-𑅬𑅧𑅣𑅯𑅛-𑅰𑅧𑅘𑅐𑅭𑅢𑅐𑅭𑅤𑅧 𑅐𑅦𑅑𑅕𑅐𑅭𑅓𑅰𑅬𑅑𑅧 𑅐𑅭𑅱𑅑𑅖𑅳𑅛𑅣𑅓।</para>
   </article>
   <article number="20"><title>𑅐𑅧𑅒𑅙𑅚𑅓𑅥𑅱 २०</title>
      <orderedlist><listitem tag="(१)"><para>𑅨𑅭𑅣𑅛𑅓𑅕𑅬𑅓𑅯 𑅛𑅧𑅱 𑅰𑅳𑅐𑅧𑅣𑅑𑅨𑅒𑅭𑅢𑅭𑅑𑅣𑅛𑅐 𑅰𑅬𑅬𑅑𑅮𑅑𑅣𑅒𑅧 𑅰𑅧𑅘𑅞𑅧𑅐𑅧𑅑 𑅙 𑅯𑅑𑅭𑅙𑅛𑅑𑅣𑅒𑅬𑅭𑅱𑅔 𑅯𑅭𑅣𑅣𑅓।</para>
         </listitem>
         <listitem tag="(२)"><para>𑅕𑅓𑅧𑅙𑅑𑅥𑅨𑅑 𑅰𑅧𑅘𑅞𑅧𑅓𑅧 𑅰𑅱 𑅐𑅣𑅬𑅐𑅧𑅧 𑅰𑅧𑅛𑅔𑅛𑅛𑅑𑅣𑅒𑅧 𑅧 𑅕𑅔𑅨𑅑 𑅯𑅑𑅯𑅰𑅳𑅑𑅕𑅭𑅣𑅒𑅧 𑅰𑅳𑅕𑅛𑅣𑅓।</para>
         </listitem>
      </orderedlist>
   </article>
   <article number="21"><title>𑅐𑅧𑅒𑅙𑅚𑅓𑅥𑅱 २१</title>
      <orderedlist><listitem tag="(१)"><para>𑅰𑅯𑅑𑅛𑅭𑅐𑅖𑅳𑅞𑅭𑅰𑅛 𑅨𑅭𑅰𑅳𑅐𑅰𑅧𑅓 𑅨𑅭𑅣𑅛𑅕𑅖𑅳𑅭𑅑𑅣𑅛𑅐 𑅐𑅤𑅯𑅐 𑅧𑅑𑅖𑅳𑅨𑅕𑅖𑅳𑅧𑅑𑅭𑅯𑅐𑅙𑅑𑅣-𑅨𑅭𑅣𑅑𑅧𑅑𑅦𑅑-𑅬𑅐𑅦𑅛𑅬𑅓𑅧 𑅨𑅭𑅣𑅛𑅓𑅕𑅧 𑅛𑅧𑅱 𑅰𑅱𑅫𑅐𑅗𑅑𑅫𑅯𑅑𑅣𑅒𑅬𑅭𑅱𑅣𑅑।</para>
         </listitem>
         <listitem tag="(२)"><para>𑅨𑅭𑅣𑅛𑅓𑅕𑅧 𑅛𑅧𑅰𑅣𑅥𑅑𑅛𑅓 𑅭𑅐𑅖𑅳𑅞𑅭𑅓 𑅮𑅔𑅕𑅰𑅓𑅯𑅐𑅛𑅐𑅱 𑅣𑅒𑅮𑅛𑅬𑅦𑅑𑅕𑅐𑅭𑅧 𑅰𑅧𑅦𑅣𑅣𑅓।</para>
         </listitem>
         <listitem tag="(३)"><para>𑅮𑅔𑅕𑅓𑅙𑅚𑅛𑅐 𑅨𑅭𑅰𑅳𑅐𑅰𑅧𑅐𑅦𑅑𑅕𑅐𑅭𑅔 𑅯𑅑𑅭𑅙𑅛𑅑𑅖𑅳𑅛𑅣𑅓; 𑅑𑅛𑅬𑅑𑅙𑅚𑅐 𑅕𑅐𑅮𑅪𑅥𑅦𑅑𑅱 𑅧𑅑𑅛𑅬𑅔𑅙𑅑𑅣𑅑𑅰𑅳𑅙 𑅧𑅑𑅭𑅯𑅐𑅙𑅧𑅑𑅱 𑅨𑅭𑅕𑅐𑅰𑅳𑅛𑅬 𑅐𑅗𑅧𑅣𑅭𑅑; 𑅑𑅬𑅐𑅧𑅑 𑅧𑅑𑅭𑅯𑅐𑅙𑅧𑅐𑅧𑅑 𑅙 𑅯𑅑𑅰𑅳𑅯𑅑𑅕𑅧 𑅣𑅒𑅮𑅛𑅧 𑅗𑅒𑅨𑅣𑅧 𑅬𑅣𑅥𑅐𑅧𑅓𑅧 𑅐𑅤𑅯𑅐 𑅣𑅒𑅮𑅛𑅬𑅓𑅯𑅓𑅣𑅭𑅓𑅢 𑅬𑅣𑅥𑅐𑅧𑅯𑅑𑅦𑅑𑅧𑅐 𑅫𑅯𑅑𑅣𑅐𑅭𑅱।</para>
         </listitem>
      </orderedlist>
   </article>
   <article number="22"><title>𑅐𑅧𑅒𑅙𑅚𑅓𑅥𑅱 २२</title>
      <para>𑅨𑅭𑅣𑅛𑅓𑅕𑅬𑅓𑅯 𑅛𑅧𑅱, 𑅰𑅐𑅬𑅐𑅛𑅑𑅕𑅣𑅯𑅐𑅣, 𑅰𑅐𑅬𑅐𑅛𑅑𑅕-𑅰𑅒𑅭𑅕𑅖𑅳𑅐𑅛𑅐 𑅐𑅦𑅑𑅕𑅐𑅭𑅧 𑅰𑅧𑅦𑅐𑅭𑅛𑅣𑅑; 𑅐𑅰𑅒 𑅱𑅑 𑅭𑅐𑅖𑅳𑅞𑅭𑅑𑅛𑅨𑅭𑅛𑅐𑅰𑅓𑅧 𑅐𑅧𑅣𑅐𑅭𑅐𑅖𑅳𑅞𑅭𑅑𑅛𑅰𑅱𑅛𑅔𑅗𑅓 𑅧 𑅙 𑅨𑅭𑅣𑅛𑅓𑅕𑅧 𑅭𑅐𑅛𑅛𑅰𑅛 𑅰𑅧𑅘𑅞𑅧-𑅰𑅧𑅰𑅐𑅦𑅧𑅐𑅧𑅒𑅭𑅒𑅨𑅬, 𑅰𑅯𑅑𑅛𑅐𑅯𑅑𑅫𑅐𑅛𑅛𑅐𑅭𑅤𑅑𑅕-𑅰𑅐𑅬𑅐𑅛𑅑𑅕-𑅰𑅐𑅧𑅰𑅕𑅭𑅒𑅣𑅑𑅕𑅐𑅦𑅑𑅕𑅐𑅭𑅐𑅢𑅐𑅧 𑅨𑅭𑅣𑅑𑅖𑅳𑅟𑅐𑅛𑅑, 𑅰𑅯𑅑𑅛𑅯𑅛𑅕𑅣𑅑𑅣𑅯𑅰𑅛 𑅒𑅧𑅬𑅒𑅕𑅣 {𑅰𑅭𑅯𑅐𑅧𑅗𑅑𑅢} 𑅯𑅑𑅕𑅐𑅰𑅐𑅭𑅤𑅧 𑅙 𑅰𑅧𑅰𑅑𑅥𑅦𑅑𑅧 𑅐𑅭𑅱𑅣𑅑।</para>
   </article>
   <article number="23"><title>𑅐𑅧𑅒𑅙𑅚𑅓𑅥𑅱 २३</title>
      <orderedlist><listitem tag="(१)"><para>𑅨𑅭𑅣𑅛𑅓𑅕𑅬𑅨𑅑 𑅧𑅑𑅭𑅯𑅭𑅒𑅣𑅣𑅑𑅣𑅐𑅧 𑅯𑅑𑅭𑅒𑅦𑅛 𑅰𑅧𑅭𑅕𑅖𑅳𑅢𑅬𑅦𑅑𑅗𑅧𑅣𑅒𑅧, 𑅐𑅧𑅒𑅕𑅒𑅮-𑅕𑅐𑅭𑅛-𑅰𑅤𑅑𑅣𑅑𑅧𑅐𑅧 𑅧𑅛𑅐𑅛𑅑𑅕𑅭𑅢𑅬𑅯𑅐𑅨𑅣𑅒𑅧 𑅰𑅯𑅣𑅧𑅣𑅭-𑅯𑅭𑅒𑅣𑅣𑅑𑅣𑅐-𑅙𑅛𑅧𑅧 𑅯𑅑𑅦𑅐𑅣𑅒𑅧 𑅕𑅐𑅭𑅛𑅐𑅢𑅑 𑅙𑅐𑅧𑅒𑅖𑅳𑅟𑅐𑅣𑅒𑅧 𑅐𑅦𑅑𑅕𑅐𑅭𑅧 𑅦𑅣𑅣𑅓।𑅨𑅭𑅣𑅛𑅓𑅕𑅬, 𑅯𑅑𑅧𑅑𑅯 𑅫𑅓𑅥𑅬, 𑅰𑅬-𑅕𑅐𑅭𑅛𑅐𑅭𑅤𑅬, 𑅰𑅬𑅐𑅧-𑅯𑅓𑅣𑅧𑅬𑅐𑅧𑅧 {𑅨𑅐𑅭𑅑𑅰𑅳𑅭𑅬𑅑𑅕𑅧} 𑅐𑅦𑅑𑅗𑅧𑅣𑅒𑅧 𑅐𑅦𑅑𑅕𑅭𑅒𑅣𑅔𑅰𑅣𑅑।</para>
         </listitem>
         <listitem tag="(२)"><para>𑅕𑅐𑅭𑅛𑅧𑅑𑅭𑅣𑅱 𑅨𑅭𑅣𑅛𑅓𑅕𑅬𑅨𑅑 𑅛𑅧𑅱, 𑅰𑅯𑅰𑅛 𑅰𑅯𑅑𑅛-𑅨𑅭𑅑𑅯𑅐𑅭𑅰𑅛 𑅙 𑅬𑅐𑅧𑅯𑅑𑅛-𑅗𑅒𑅭𑅯-𑅛𑅒𑅣𑅰𑅛 𑅐𑅰𑅣𑅑𑅣𑅯𑅰𑅛 𑅰𑅧𑅭𑅕𑅖𑅳𑅢𑅐𑅭𑅤𑅧 𑅰𑅬𑅒𑅙𑅑𑅣𑅐𑅧𑅒𑅕𑅒𑅮-𑅨𑅐𑅭𑅑𑅰𑅳𑅭𑅬𑅑𑅕𑅐𑅥𑅐𑅧𑅰𑅛 𑅐𑅦𑅑𑅕𑅐𑅭𑅧 𑅦𑅐𑅭𑅛𑅣𑅑।</para>
         </listitem>
         <listitem tag="(३)"><para>𑅐𑅯𑅰𑅳𑅛𑅕𑅓 𑅰𑅣𑅑 𑅙𑅐𑅰𑅒 𑅰𑅐𑅬𑅐𑅛𑅑𑅕-𑅰𑅧𑅭𑅕𑅖𑅳𑅢𑅰𑅛 𑅐𑅧𑅛𑅔𑅨𑅐𑅛𑅑𑅱 𑅓𑅣𑅣𑅨𑅒𑅭𑅛𑅑𑅣𑅒𑅧 𑅐𑅭𑅱𑅑𑅖𑅳𑅛𑅣𑅓।</para>
         </listitem>
         <listitem tag="(४)"><para>𑅰𑅯𑅑𑅛𑅱𑅑𑅣𑅐𑅧𑅐𑅧 𑅰𑅧𑅭𑅕𑅖𑅳𑅢𑅐𑅭𑅤𑅧 𑅨𑅭𑅣𑅛𑅓𑅕𑅬 𑅰𑅳𑅭𑅬𑅑𑅕𑅰𑅧𑅘𑅞𑅧𑅑𑅱 𑅰𑅐𑅕𑅧 𑅐𑅣𑅬𑅐𑅧𑅧 𑅰𑅧𑅛𑅔𑅛𑅛𑅑𑅣𑅒𑅧 𑅓𑅣𑅐𑅥𑅭𑅒𑅕-𑅰𑅧𑅘𑅞𑅧𑅧 𑅯𑅐 𑅰𑅧𑅭𑅙𑅛𑅑𑅣𑅒𑅧 𑅐𑅦𑅑𑅕𑅭𑅒𑅣𑅔𑅰𑅣𑅑।</para>
         </listitem>
      </orderedlist>
   </article>
   <article number="24"><title>𑅐𑅧𑅒𑅙𑅚𑅓𑅥𑅱 २४</title>
      <para>𑅕𑅐𑅭𑅛𑅱𑅔𑅭𑅐𑅢𑅐𑅧 𑅰𑅬𑅒𑅙𑅑𑅣-𑅧𑅑𑅛𑅬𑅧-𑅨𑅒𑅭𑅰𑅰𑅭𑅬, 𑅰𑅯𑅓𑅣𑅧𑅧 𑅙 𑅧𑅑𑅛𑅣𑅐𑅯𑅦𑅑𑅕𑅐𑅯𑅕𑅐𑅰𑅳𑅓𑅧 𑅰𑅱 𑅯𑅑𑅰𑅳𑅭𑅬𑅐𑅦𑅑𑅕𑅐𑅭𑅱 𑅨𑅭𑅣𑅛𑅕𑅰𑅬𑅑 𑅨𑅭𑅥𑅓𑅛𑅔𑅰𑅣𑅑।</para>
   </article>
   <article number="25"><title>𑅐𑅧𑅒𑅙𑅚𑅓𑅥𑅱 २५</title>
      <orderedlist><listitem tag="(१)"><para>𑅨𑅭𑅣𑅛𑅓𑅕𑅧 𑅛𑅧𑅱 𑅖𑅐𑅥𑅛-𑅯𑅰𑅣𑅭𑅐𑅯𑅐𑅰-𑅙𑅑𑅕𑅑𑅣𑅰𑅔𑅨𑅙𑅭𑅛𑅐𑅥𑅑𑅫𑅑𑅱, 𑅐𑅯𑅰𑅳𑅛𑅕-𑅰𑅐𑅬𑅐𑅛𑅑𑅕-𑅰𑅓𑅯𑅐𑅫𑅑𑅰𑅳𑅙 𑅰𑅱 𑅰𑅯𑅰𑅛 𑅰𑅯𑅑𑅛𑅨𑅭𑅑𑅯𑅐𑅭𑅰𑅛 𑅙 𑅐𑅧𑅐𑅬𑅛𑅣𑅐𑅛𑅑 𑅰𑅯𑅰𑅤𑅣𑅐𑅛𑅑 𑅙 𑅨𑅭𑅛𑅐𑅨𑅣𑅧 𑅛𑅑𑅯𑅧𑅰𑅣𑅭𑅧 𑅰𑅧𑅦𑅐𑅭𑅛𑅑𑅣𑅒𑅧 𑅐𑅦𑅑𑅕𑅭𑅒𑅣𑅔𑅰𑅣𑅑। 𑅐𑅨𑅑 𑅙, 𑅧𑅑𑅛𑅧𑅣𑅭𑅢-𑅰𑅳𑅒𑅧𑅛𑅐𑅰𑅒 𑅨𑅭𑅑𑅰𑅤𑅑𑅣𑅑𑅖𑅳𑅒 𑅐𑅧𑅛𑅰𑅬𑅑𑅧 𑅛𑅑𑅯𑅕𑅔𑅨𑅐𑅭𑅛𑅧𑅐𑅫𑅐𑅯𑅓 𑅯𑅭𑅒𑅥𑅦𑅐𑅯𑅰𑅤𑅐𑅛𑅐𑅧, 𑅯𑅑𑅦𑅯𑅛𑅨𑅭𑅐𑅨𑅣𑅒, 𑅐𑅛𑅔𑅗𑅛𑅣𑅐𑅛𑅐𑅧, 𑅭𑅒𑅗𑅢𑅣𑅐𑅛𑅐𑅧 𑅧𑅑𑅭𑅯𑅭𑅒𑅣𑅣𑅑𑅣𑅐𑅛𑅐𑅧 𑅙 𑅰𑅣𑅛𑅐𑅬, 𑅨𑅭𑅣𑅛𑅓𑅕𑅬𑅨𑅑 𑅰𑅒𑅭𑅕𑅖𑅳𑅐𑅦𑅑𑅕𑅐𑅭𑅧 𑅰𑅧𑅦𑅐𑅭𑅛𑅣𑅑।</para>
         </listitem>
         <listitem tag="(२)"><para>𑅬𑅐𑅣𑅭𑅒𑅣𑅯𑅰𑅛 𑅰𑅳𑅑𑅰𑅳𑅒𑅣𑅯𑅰𑅛 𑅙 𑅕𑅭𑅒𑅣𑅓 𑅯𑅑𑅰𑅳𑅑𑅖𑅳𑅞𑅰𑅐𑅱𑅐𑅛𑅛𑅔𑅨𑅙𑅭𑅛𑅐𑅛𑅐𑅣𑅧 𑅨𑅭𑅥𑅓𑅛𑅧 𑅫𑅯𑅑𑅣𑅐। 𑅐𑅯𑅑𑅦𑅐𑅱 𑅯𑅑𑅦𑅐𑅰𑅳𑅙 𑅰𑅭𑅯𑅓𑅨𑅑 𑅪𑅐𑅮𑅐𑅱, 𑅰𑅬𑅐𑅧𑅧 𑅰𑅐𑅬𑅐𑅛𑅑𑅕𑅧 𑅰𑅧𑅭𑅕𑅖𑅳𑅢𑅧 𑅐𑅯𑅐𑅨𑅣𑅒𑅧 𑅐𑅭𑅱𑅑𑅖𑅳𑅛𑅧𑅣𑅑।</para>
         </listitem>
      </orderedlist>
   </article>
   <article number="26"><title>𑅐𑅧𑅒𑅙𑅚𑅓𑅥𑅱 २६</title>
      <orderedlist><listitem tag="(१)"><para>𑅨𑅭𑅣𑅛𑅓𑅕𑅬𑅨𑅑 𑅛𑅧𑅱 𑅰𑅳𑅑𑅕𑅖𑅳𑅐𑅦𑅑𑅕𑅐𑅭𑅧 𑅰𑅧𑅦𑅣𑅣𑅓। 𑅨𑅭𑅐𑅤𑅬𑅑𑅕𑅓𑅖𑅳𑅒, 𑅬𑅒𑅮𑅑𑅕𑅰𑅣𑅭𑅓𑅖𑅳𑅒 𑅙 𑅰𑅳𑅑𑅕𑅖𑅳𑅐 𑅧𑅑𑅱𑅰𑅳𑅒𑅮𑅕𑅐 𑅯𑅭𑅣𑅑𑅣𑅐। 𑅨𑅭𑅐𑅤𑅬𑅑𑅕𑅑 𑅰𑅳𑅑𑅕𑅖𑅳𑅐 𑅐𑅧𑅑𑅯𑅐𑅭𑅛𑅐 𑅫𑅯𑅑𑅣𑅐। 𑅨𑅭𑅐𑅯𑅑𑅦𑅑𑅕𑅑 𑅯𑅛𑅐𑅯𑅰𑅐𑅛𑅑𑅕𑅑 𑅙 𑅰𑅳𑅑𑅕𑅖𑅳𑅐 𑅰𑅐𑅬𑅐𑅧𑅛𑅣𑅛𑅐 𑅒𑅨𑅨𑅐𑅥𑅛𑅑𑅖𑅳𑅛𑅣𑅓, 𑅒𑅙𑅙𑅣𑅭𑅰𑅳𑅑𑅕𑅖𑅳𑅐 𑅙, 𑅰𑅭𑅯𑅓𑅖𑅳𑅐𑅬𑅨𑅑 𑅕𑅭𑅒𑅣𑅓 𑅛𑅔𑅗𑅛𑅣𑅐𑅦𑅐𑅭𑅓𑅢 𑅰𑅬𑅐𑅧𑅭𑅒𑅨𑅓𑅢 𑅨𑅭𑅐𑅨𑅛𑅐 𑅫𑅯𑅑𑅣𑅐।</para>
         </listitem>
         <listitem tag="(२)"><para>𑅰𑅳𑅑𑅕𑅖𑅳𑅑𑅖𑅳𑅐 𑅬𑅐𑅧𑅯𑅑𑅛 𑅯𑅛𑅕𑅣𑅑𑅣𑅯𑅰𑅛 𑅰𑅭𑅯𑅐𑅧𑅗𑅑𑅢-𑅯𑅑𑅕𑅐𑅰𑅧 𑅨𑅭𑅣𑅑 𑅧𑅑𑅭𑅥𑅑𑅖𑅳𑅞𑅐 𑅫𑅯𑅑𑅣𑅐 𑅐𑅨𑅑 𑅙𑅑𑅖𑅳𑅐 𑅬𑅒𑅮𑅑𑅕𑅰𑅯𑅐𑅣𑅧𑅣𑅭𑅛𑅐𑅢𑅐𑅧 𑅬𑅐𑅧𑅯𑅐𑅦𑅑𑅕𑅐𑅭𑅐𑅢𑅐𑅧 𑅙 𑅕𑅭𑅒𑅣𑅓 𑅰𑅬𑅬𑅐𑅧-𑅰𑅧𑅯𑅭𑅦𑅑𑅕𑅐 𑅫𑅯𑅑𑅣𑅐। 𑅰𑅭𑅯𑅓𑅰𑅯𑅨𑅑 𑅭𑅐𑅖𑅳𑅞𑅭𑅓𑅖𑅳𑅒 𑅛𑅐𑅣𑅑𑅛𑅓𑅖𑅳𑅒 𑅦𑅐𑅭𑅬𑅑𑅕𑅓𑅖𑅳𑅒-𑅯𑅐 𑅯𑅭𑅗𑅓𑅖𑅳𑅒 𑅰𑅳𑅑𑅕𑅖𑅳𑅑𑅖𑅳𑅐। 𑅰𑅖𑅛𑅰𑅱𑅑𑅖𑅳𑅢𑅒𑅣𑅐-𑅰𑅥𑅫𑅐𑅯-𑅰𑅧𑅯𑅭𑅦𑅑𑅕𑅐 𑅯𑅭𑅣𑅣𑅑𑅣𑅐। 𑅐𑅨𑅑 𑅙𑅑𑅖𑅳𑅐, 𑅰𑅳𑅐𑅧𑅣𑅑-𑅰𑅧𑅦𑅐𑅭𑅢𑅐𑅭𑅤𑅧 𑅰𑅧𑅛𑅒𑅕𑅣 𑅭𑅐𑅖𑅳𑅞𑅭𑅰𑅧𑅘𑅰𑅛 𑅕𑅐𑅭𑅛𑅐𑅢𑅑 𑅑𑅣𑅔𑅨𑅛𑅗𑅭𑅓 𑅨𑅭𑅰𑅐𑅭𑅛𑅑𑅖𑅳𑅛𑅣𑅑।</para>
         </listitem>
         <listitem tag="(३)"><para>𑅪𑅐𑅮𑅐𑅧𑅐𑅧 𑅕𑅭𑅒𑅣𑅓 𑅨𑅭𑅥𑅓𑅛𑅐𑅧 𑅰𑅳𑅑𑅕𑅖𑅳𑅐𑅧 𑅙𑅓𑅣𑅒𑅧 𑅨𑅑𑅣𑅭𑅒 𑅨𑅭𑅐𑅤𑅬𑅛𑅐𑅦𑅭𑅒𑅣𑅧 𑅐𑅦𑅑𑅕𑅐𑅭𑅧 𑅦𑅐𑅭𑅛𑅣𑅱।</para>
         </listitem>
      </orderedlist>
   </article>
   <article number="27"><title>𑅐𑅧𑅒𑅙𑅚𑅓𑅥𑅱 २७</title>
      <orderedlist><listitem tag="(१)"><para>𑅯𑅑𑅯𑅑𑅦𑅕𑅮𑅐𑅧𑅐𑅧 𑅐𑅧𑅧𑅥-𑅰𑅧𑅥𑅔𑅱𑅬𑅧𑅒𑅫𑅯𑅑𑅣𑅒𑅧 𑅯𑅑𑅛𑅝𑅐𑅧𑅑𑅕𑅔-𑅨𑅮𑅰𑅦𑅑𑅧𑅐𑅧 𑅮𑅐𑅫𑅐𑅧 𑅙 𑅰𑅧𑅯𑅑𑅫𑅕𑅣𑅒𑅧 𑅯𑅑𑅫𑅑𑅧𑅧𑅐𑅧𑅐𑅧 𑅰𑅬𑅒𑅥𑅐𑅛𑅐𑅧𑅐𑅧 𑅰𑅐𑅧𑅰𑅕𑅭𑅒𑅣𑅑𑅕-𑅛𑅑𑅯𑅧𑅓 𑅙 𑅰𑅯𑅣𑅧𑅣𑅭𑅣𑅛𑅐 𑅰𑅱𑅛𑅔𑅕𑅣𑅒𑅧 𑅰𑅭𑅯𑅔𑅨𑅑 𑅛𑅧𑅱 𑅐𑅦𑅑𑅕𑅐𑅭𑅛𑅒𑅣𑅔𑅰𑅣𑅑।</para>
         </listitem>
         <listitem tag="(२)"><para>𑅕𑅰𑅛𑅐𑅨𑅑 𑅯𑅑𑅛𑅝𑅐𑅧𑅑𑅕-𑅰𑅐𑅱𑅑𑅣𑅛𑅑𑅕-𑅕𑅮𑅐𑅣𑅬𑅕𑅐𑅧𑅐𑅧 𑅧𑅑𑅭𑅬𑅐𑅢𑅐𑅧𑅐𑅧, 𑅛𑅰𑅛𑅐𑅰𑅒 𑅭𑅙𑅛𑅑𑅣𑅐𑅰𑅣𑅑, 𑅧𑅑𑅣𑅑𑅕𑅐𑅧𑅐𑅧 𑅯𑅰𑅣𑅒𑅗𑅣𑅐𑅧𑅐𑅧 𑅱𑅑𑅣𑅐𑅧𑅐𑅧 𑅰𑅧𑅭𑅕𑅖𑅳𑅢𑅐𑅭𑅤𑅧 𑅨𑅭𑅣𑅛𑅓𑅕𑅧 𑅛𑅧𑅔𑅦𑅑𑅕𑅐𑅭𑅧 𑅰𑅧𑅦𑅣𑅣𑅓।</para>
         </listitem>
      </orderedlist>
   </article>
   <article number="28"><title>𑅐𑅧𑅒𑅙𑅚𑅓𑅥𑅱 २८</title>
      <para>𑅐𑅰𑅛𑅐𑅧 𑅐𑅫𑅑𑅘𑅔𑅖𑅳𑅢𑅐𑅛𑅐𑅧 𑅧𑅑𑅭𑅥𑅑𑅖𑅳𑅞𑅐𑅧𑅐𑅧 𑅐𑅦𑅑𑅕𑅐𑅭𑅐𑅢𑅐𑅧 𑅰𑅯𑅐𑅣𑅧𑅣𑅭𑅛𑅐𑅢𑅐𑅧 𑅙 𑅨𑅭𑅐𑅨𑅣𑅛𑅓 𑅰𑅐𑅬𑅐𑅛𑅑𑅕𑅐𑅧𑅣𑅐𑅭𑅐𑅖𑅳𑅞𑅭𑅑𑅕-𑅯𑅛𑅯𑅰𑅤𑅐𑅛𑅐𑅧 𑅙 𑅨𑅒𑅭𑅢𑅣𑅛𑅐 𑅓𑅣𑅐𑅧 𑅐𑅦𑅑𑅗𑅧𑅣𑅒𑅧 𑅨𑅭𑅣𑅛𑅓𑅕𑅬𑅨𑅑 𑅛𑅧𑅔𑅭𑅱𑅑𑅖𑅳𑅛𑅣𑅓।</para>
   </article>
   <article number="29"><title>𑅐𑅧𑅒𑅙𑅚𑅓𑅥𑅱 २९</title>
      <orderedlist><listitem tag="(१)"><para>𑅨𑅭𑅣𑅛𑅓𑅕𑅧 𑅛𑅧𑅱 𑅰𑅬𑅒𑅥𑅐𑅛𑅰𑅛 𑅕𑅭𑅒𑅣𑅓 𑅕𑅭𑅣𑅯𑅛𑅥𑅐𑅛𑅑𑅣𑅯𑅧 𑅦𑅐𑅭𑅛𑅣𑅑 𑅛𑅓𑅧 𑅱𑅑 𑅰𑅯𑅑𑅛-𑅯𑅛𑅕𑅣𑅑𑅣𑅯𑅰𑅛 𑅨𑅒𑅭𑅢-𑅰𑅯𑅣𑅧𑅣𑅭-𑅯𑅑𑅕𑅐𑅰𑅱 𑅰𑅧𑅫𑅯𑅓𑅣।</para>
         </listitem>
         <listitem tag="(२)"><para>𑅰𑅯𑅑𑅛𑅐𑅦𑅑𑅕𑅐𑅭-𑅰𑅯𑅐𑅣𑅧𑅣𑅭𑅛𑅐𑅢𑅐𑅧 𑅕𑅭𑅑𑅛𑅐𑅧𑅯𑅛𑅧𑅓 𑅨𑅭𑅣𑅛𑅓𑅕𑅬 𑅛𑅧𑅱, 𑅐𑅧𑅛𑅓𑅖𑅳𑅐𑅧 𑅐𑅦𑅑𑅕𑅐𑅭-𑅰𑅯𑅐𑅣𑅧𑅣𑅭𑅛𑅐𑅢𑅑 𑅨𑅭𑅣𑅑 𑅰𑅬𑅒𑅙𑅑𑅣𑅐𑅫𑅑𑅛𑅝𑅐𑅧𑅐𑅥𑅭-𑅰𑅧𑅭𑅕𑅖𑅳𑅢𑅥𑅭𑅒𑅰𑅳𑅐 𑅧𑅒𑅧𑅧 𑅯𑅛𑅯𑅱𑅭𑅑𑅖𑅳𑅛𑅣𑅑। 𑅐𑅨𑅑 𑅙𑅐𑅰𑅒 𑅮𑅔𑅕𑅣𑅐𑅧𑅣𑅭𑅑𑅕-𑅰𑅬𑅐𑅛𑅓, 𑅰𑅐𑅬𑅐𑅧𑅛-𑅕𑅮𑅛𑅐𑅢𑅧 𑅰𑅐𑅭𑅯𑅛𑅧𑅑𑅕-𑅯𑅛𑅯𑅰𑅤𑅐𑅧 𑅧𑅑𑅣𑅑𑅕𑅣𑅐𑅛𑅐𑅱 𑅰𑅬𑅒𑅙𑅑𑅣𑅐𑅯𑅰𑅳𑅛𑅕𑅣𑅐𑅰𑅳𑅙 𑅨𑅭𑅣𑅑 𑅨𑅒𑅭𑅢𑅧 𑅥𑅐𑅛𑅑𑅣𑅯𑅧 𑅧𑅑𑅭𑅯𑅕𑅖𑅳𑅛𑅣𑅑।</para>
         </listitem>
         <listitem tag="(३)"><para>𑅓𑅣𑅓𑅦𑅑𑅕𑅐𑅭𑅐𑅱 𑅓𑅣𑅐𑅧𑅑 𑅰𑅯𑅐𑅣𑅧𑅣𑅭𑅛𑅐𑅢𑅑 𑅙, 𑅰𑅧𑅛𑅒𑅕𑅣𑅭𑅐𑅖𑅳𑅞𑅭𑅰𑅧𑅘𑅰𑅛 𑅒𑅥𑅥𑅓𑅰𑅳𑅛𑅐𑅧𑅑 𑅰𑅑𑅥𑅦𑅐𑅧𑅣𑅐𑅧 𑅙 𑅯𑅑𑅭𑅒𑅦𑅛 𑅧 𑅕𑅤𑅬𑅨𑅑 𑅨𑅭𑅛𑅔𑅕𑅖𑅳𑅛𑅧𑅣𑅓।</para>
         </listitem>
      </orderedlist>
   </article>
   <article number="30"><title>𑅐𑅧𑅒𑅙𑅚𑅓𑅥𑅱 ३०</title>
      <para>𑅐𑅰𑅛𑅐𑅧 𑅐𑅫𑅑𑅘𑅔𑅖𑅳𑅢𑅐𑅛𑅐𑅧 𑅧𑅑𑅭𑅥𑅑𑅖𑅳𑅞𑅐𑅧𑅐𑅧 𑅐𑅦𑅑𑅕𑅐𑅭𑅐𑅢𑅐𑅧 𑅰𑅯𑅐𑅣𑅧𑅣𑅭𑅛𑅐𑅢𑅐𑅧 𑅙 𑅧 𑅕𑅔𑅨𑅛𑅧𑅰𑅳𑅱, 𑅨𑅭𑅢𑅐𑅰𑅳-𑅮𑅕𑅖𑅳𑅛𑅐𑅦𑅐𑅭𑅓𑅢 𑅕𑅑𑅬𑅨𑅑 𑅕𑅐𑅭𑅛𑅬𑅧𑅒𑅖𑅳𑅟𑅐𑅣𑅒𑅧 𑅓𑅣𑅐𑅥𑅭𑅒𑅕𑅕𑅐𑅭𑅛𑅐𑅧𑅒𑅖𑅳𑅟𑅐𑅧𑅐𑅭𑅤𑅧 𑅯𑅐 𑅕𑅰𑅛𑅙𑅑𑅣 𑅭𑅐𑅖𑅳𑅞𑅭𑅰𑅛 𑅯𑅭𑅗𑅰𑅛 𑅛𑅧𑅰𑅛 𑅯𑅐 𑅰𑅬𑅑𑅱𑅑𑅣-𑅰𑅑𑅥𑅦𑅛𑅭𑅤𑅧 𑅐𑅧𑅛𑅤𑅐 𑅯𑅛𑅐𑅖𑅛𑅐𑅣𑅒𑅧 𑅧𑅑𑅯 𑅰𑅳𑅕𑅖𑅳𑅛𑅣𑅓।</para>
   </article>
   <note><para>𑅰𑅯𑅣𑅯𑅐𑅦𑅑𑅕𑅐𑅭𑅱 1997</para>
      <para>𑅬𑅐𑅧𑅯𑅐𑅦𑅑𑅕𑅐𑅭𑅐𑅢𑅐𑅧 𑅕𑅭𑅒𑅣𑅓 𑅰𑅧𑅛𑅒𑅕𑅣𑅭𑅐𑅖𑅳𑅞𑅭𑅔𑅙𑅙𑅐𑅛𑅒𑅕𑅣𑅰𑅛 𑅕𑅐𑅭𑅛𑅐𑅮𑅛𑅱</para>
      <para>𑅛𑅑𑅧𑅓𑅯𑅐, 𑅰𑅯𑅑𑅞𑅛𑅳𑅭𑅮𑅑𑅢𑅠</para>
   </note>
</udhr>
