<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<!--┬й The Office of the High Commisioner for Human Rights-->
<udhr xmlns="http://www.unhchr.ch/udhr" iso639-3="aii" xml:lang="aii-Phlp" key="aii_phlp" n="Assyrian Neo-Aramaic (Psalter Pahlavi)" dir="ltr" iso15924="Phlp"><title>ЁРоБЁРоЕЁРоГЁРоЛЁРоА ЁРоСЁРоИЁРоБЁРоКЁРоИЁРоА ЁРоКЁРоОЁРоЕЁРоС ЁРоЖЁРоГЁРоЛЁРоА ЁРоАЁРоМЁРоРЁРоИЁРоА</title>
   <preamble><title>ЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоГЁРоА</title>
      <para>ЁРоЛЁРоМ ЁРоНЁРоБЁРоБ ЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоГЁРоИЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоБЁРоАЁРоИЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоА ЁРоРЁРоЕЁРоРЁРоМЁРоИЁРоА ЁРоКЁРоЙЁРоКЁРоД ЁРоДЁРоГЁРоЛЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоЙЁРоКЁРоОЁРоС ЁРоГЁРоБЁРоЕЁРоМЁРоРЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоБЁРоЖЁРоГЁРоЛЁРоА ЁРоКЁРоА ЁРоЛЁРоСЁРоИЁРоДЁРоБЁРоМЁРоА ЁРоАЁРоИЁРоМЁРоА ЁРоАЁРоНЁРоЙЁРоИЁРоЛЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоЗЁРоАЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоЙЁРоИЁРоМЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоРЁРоКЁРоЛЁРоА ЁРоВЁРоЕ ЁРоСЁРоИЁРоБЁРоК.</para>
      <para>ЁРоЛЁРоМ ЁРоНЁРоБЁРоБ ЁРоОЁРоКЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоКЁРоА ЁРоЛЁРоИЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоЛЁРоНЁРоКЁРоИЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоЖЁРоГЁРоЛЁРоА ЁРоАЁРоМЁРоРЁРоИЁРоА ЁРоИЁРоБЁРоГЁРоЕЁРоМЁРоА ЁРоКЁРоЕЁРоБЁРоГЁРоЕЁРоИЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоБЁРоЕЁРоБЁРоЕЁРоИЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоВЁРоЖЁРоМЁРоА ЁРоКЁРоАЁРоМЁРоИЁРоС ЁРоГЁРоБЁРоЕЁРоМЁРоРЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА. ЁРоЕЁРоАЁРоСЁРоИЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЗЁРоГ ЁРоГЁРоЕЁРоМЁРоИЁРоА ЁРоАЁРоИЁРоЙЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоБЁРоЕЁРоМЁРоРЁРоА ЁРоБЁРоГ ЁРоОЁРоПЁРоЗ ЁРоБЁРоЗЁРоАЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоДЁРоЛЁРоЖЁРоЛЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоДЁРоИЁРоЛЁРоМЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоЗЁРоАЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЛЁРоМ ЁРоЖЁРоГЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоНЁРоМЁРоИЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоОЁРоИЁРоРЁРоИ ЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоБЁРоЗЁРоА ЁРоАЁРоИЁРоЙ ЁРоАЁРоМЁРоИ ЁРоМЁРоИЁРоРЁРоА ЁРоБЁРоЕЁРоР ЁРоЕЁРоКЁРоИЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоАЁРоМЁРоРЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоИЁРоГЁРоИЁРоА.</para>
      <para>ЁРоЛЁРоМ ЁРоНЁРоБЁРоБ ЁРоАЁРоМЁРоМЁРоЛЁРоИЁРоСЁРоАЁРоИЁРоКЁРоД ЁРоЛЁРоА ЁРоЛЁРоМЁРоЕЁРоМ ЁРоРЁРоАЁРоЛЁРоК ЁРоРЁРоЕЁРоОЁРоА ЁРоКЁРоМЁРоСЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЖЁРоГЁРоЛЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоБЁРоЕЁРоМЁРоРЁРоА ЁРоЛЁРоА ЁРоКЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоБЁРоГ ЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоГЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоЕЁРоЛЁРоБЁРоК ЁРоГЁРоСЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоМЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоЖЁРоКЁРоЕЁРоЛЁРоИЁРоА.</para>
      <para>ЁРоЛЁРоМ ЁРоНЁРоБЁРоБ ЁРоЕЁРоЛЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоАЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЛЁРоЗЁРоИЁРоГЁРоА ЁРоЛЁРоРЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоМЁРоА ЁРоВЁРоЕ ЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоГЁРоА ЁРоДЁРоИЁРоЛЁРоМЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоИ ЁРоВЁРоЕ ЁРоЖЁРоГЁРоЛЁРоА ЁРоАЁРоМЁРоРЁРоИЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоВЁРоЕ ЁРоАЁРоИЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоА ЁРоОЁРоЕЁРоПЁРоЕЁРоОЁРоИЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоБЁРоЕЁРоБЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоВЁРоЕ ЁРоЖЁРоГЁРоЛЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоРЁРоЕЁРоИЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоМЁРоРЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоГЁРоЙЁРоЕЁРоА. ЁРоЕЁРоЛЁРоБЁРоЕЁРоКЁРоМЁРоА ЁРоКЁРоСЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоЛЁРоА ЁРоКЁРоЛЁРоСЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоРЁРоЕЁРоРЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоРЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоОЁРоИЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоЛЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоЗЁРоИЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоК ЁРоЗЁРоГ ЁРоГЁРоЕЁРоВЁРоА ЁРоБЁРоЕЁРоР ЁРоЕЁРоКЁРоИЁРоА ЁРоВЁРоЕ ЁРоЗЁРоГ ЁРоАЁРоАЁРоЕ ЁРоГЁРоЗЁРоАЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоБЁРоЕЁРоР ЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоЗЁРоСЁРоА.</para>
      <para>ЁРоЕЁРоЛЁРоМ ЁРоНЁРоБЁРоБ ЁРоГЁРоАЁРоСЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоДЁРоГЁРоЛЁРоА ЁРоЛЁРоБЁРоЕЁРоКЁРоМЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоДЁРоИЁРоЕЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоЛ ЁРоАЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЛЁРоЗЁРоИЁРоГЁРоА ЁРоКЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоЗЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоЖЁРоГЁРоЛЁРоА ЁРоАЁРоМЁРоРЁРоИЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоМЁРоСЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЗЁРоАЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоРЁРоЕЁРоРЁРоМЁРоИЁРоСЁРоА.</para>
      <para>ЁРоАЁРоИЁРоЙЁРоА ЁРоОЁРоЕЁРоЛЁРоИЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЙЁРоКЁРоМЁРоИЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоКЁРоАЁРоМЁРоА ЁРоЖЁРоГЁРоЛЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоЗЁРоАЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоИЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоАЁРоИЁРоМЁРоА ЁРоАЁРоМЁРоМЁРоЛЁРоИЁРоА ЁРоКЁРоСЁРоЛЁРоЛЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоАЁРоДЁРоА ЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоКЁРоА.</para>
      <para>ЁРоБЁРоЕЁРоГ ЁРоАЁРоДЁРоА ЁРоЙЁРоМЁРоЕЁРоРЁРоИЁРоА ЁРоВЁРоЕЁРоМЁРоИЁРоА▄Ж</para>
      <para>ЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоГЁРоЕЁРоИЁРоКЁРоД ЁРоГЁРоАЁРоДЁРоА ЁРоБЁРоЕЁРоГЁРоЛЁРоА ЁРоСЁРоИЁРоБЁРоКЁРоИЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоЖЁРоГЁРоЛЁРоА ЁРоАЁРоМЁРоРЁРоИЁРоА ЁРоАЁРоИЁРоКЁРоА ЁРоЗЁРоГ ЁРоЛЁРоЙЁРоЛЁРоКЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоВЁРоЕЁРоМЁРоИЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЛЁРоА ЁРоЙЁРоКЁРоД ЁРоАЁРоМЁРоРЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоАЁРоСЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоКЁРоОЁРоЕЁРоС ЁРоМЁРоИЁРоРЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоЙЁРоК ЁРоОЁРоЕЁРоНЁРоЕЁРоОЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоЙЁРоК ЁРоВЁРоЕЁРоРЁРоЛЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоРЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоОЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоСЁРоЗЁРоЕЁРоА ЁРоДЁРоЛЁРоРЁРоА ЁРоКЁРоАЁРоДЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоГЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоВЁРоЕЁРоБЁРоИ ЁРоКЁРоЛЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоИЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоЛЁРоКЁРоОЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоКЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоЗЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоАЁРоИЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоА ЁРоЛЁРоА ЁРоАЁРоМЁРоА ЁРоЖЁРоГЁРоЛЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоЗЁРоАЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоБЁРоИЁРоГ ЁРоАЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоЗЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЛЁРоСЁРоЛЁРоГЁРоЛЁРоМЁРоА ЁРоАЁРоСЁРоЕЁРоМЁРоИЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоИЁРоБЁРоКЁРоИЁРоА ЁРоКЁРоМЁРоСЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоКЁРоАЁРоМЁРоА ЁРоОЁРоНЁРоЕЁРоКЁРоИЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЛЁРоСЁРоЛЁРоГЁРоЛЁРоМЁРоА.</para>
   </preamble>
   <article number="1"><title>ЁРоЛЁРоКЁРоЕЁРоАЁРоА 1</title>
      <para>ЁРоЙЁРоК ЁРоБЁРоЕЁРоМЁРоРЁРоА ЁРоБЁРоЕЁРоИЁРоКЁРоД ЁРоЗЁРоАЁРоЕЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоБЁРоЕЁРоБЁРоЕ ЁРоВЁРоЕ ЁРоАЁРоИЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоЖЁРоГЁРоЛЁРоА. ЁРоЕЁРоОЁРоИЁРоРЁРоИЁРоКЁРоД ЁРоИЁРоДЁРоБЁРоА ЁРоДЁРоЕЁРоМЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоАЁРоМЁРоИЁРоС. ЁРоБЁРоЕЁРоГ ЁРоГЁРоАЁРоДЁРоА ЁРоВЁРоРЁРоЛЁРоСЁРоИ ЁРоЕЁРоК ЁРоАЁРоЗЁРоЕЁРоМЁРоА ЁРоВЁРоЕЁРоВ ЁРоДЁРоЕЁРоИЁРоА ЁРоБЁРоЗЁРоГ ЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоЗЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоАЁРоЗЁРоМЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА.</para>
   </article>
   <article number="2"><title>ЁРоЛЁРоКЁРоЕЁРоАЁРоА 2</title>
      <para>ЁРоЙЁРоК ЁРоЗЁРоГ ЁРоАЁРоИЁРоСЁРоКЁРоД ЁРоДЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоКЁРоЖЁРоГЁРоЛЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоЗЁРоАЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоОЁРоИЁРоРЁРоМЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоРЁРоИЁРоЛЁРоА ЁРоВЁРоЕ ЁРоГЁРоАЁРоДЁРоА ЁРоБЁРоЕЁРоГЁРоЛЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоКЁРоА ЁРоДЁРоЙ ЁРоОЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоРЁРоЕЁРоМЁРоИЁРоА ЁРоБЁРоИЁРоК ЁРоСЁРоДЁРоЕ ЁРоАЁРоИЁРоЙ ЁРоВЁРоМЁРоНЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоМЁРоВЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоМЁРоРЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоГЁРоЙЁРоЕЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоКЁРоРЁРоМЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоЕЁРоГЁРоИЁРоСЁРоА. ЁРоЕЁРоОЁРоЕЁРоКЁРоИЁРоСЁРоИЁРоЛЁРоИ ЁРоИЁРоМ ЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоИЁРоМЁРоА ЁРоАЁРоЗЁРоЕЁРоМЁРоА. ЁРоАЁРоЕЁРоОЁРоЖЁРоА ЁРоОЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоРЁРоЕЁРоМЁРоИЁРоА ЁРоВЁРоЕЁРоВ ЁРоКЁРоА ЁРоОЁРоАЁРоЕЁРоР ЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоБЁРоА ЁРоБЁРоНЁРоБЁРоБ ЁРоАЁРоЙЁРоМЁРоИЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоОЁРоЕЁРоКЁРоИЁРоСЁРоИЁРоЛЁРоИЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоИЁРоМ ЁРоСЁРоБЁРоКЁРоИЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоЗЁРоГ ЁРоАЁРоСЁРоЕЁРоА ЁРоИЁРоМ ЁРоАЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоЗЁРоГ ЁРоОЁРоЕЁРоНЁРоЕЁРоОЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоНЁРоИЁРоЕЁРоИЁРоКЁРоД ЁРоБЁРоИЁРоД.</para>
   </article>
   <article number="3"><title>ЁРоЛЁРоКЁРоЕЁРоАЁРоА 3</title>
      <para>ЁРоЙЁРоК ЁРоЗЁРоГ ЁРоАЁРоИЁРоСЁРоКЁРоД ЁРоДЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоКЁРоЗЁРоИЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоЗЁРоАЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоРЁРоИЁРоМЁРоА ЁРоОЁРоЕЁРоНЁРоЕЁРоОЁРоИЁРоА.</para>
   </article>
   <article number="4"><title>ЁРоЛЁРоКЁРоЕЁРоАЁРоА 4</title>
      <para>ЁРоДЁРоЙ ЁРоЗЁРоГ ЁРоВЁРоЕЁРоВ ЁРоКЁРоА ЁРоОЁРоАЁРоР ЁРоГЁРоБЁРоИЁРоЛЁРоГЁРоА ЁРоВЁРоЕ ЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоКЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоИЁРоМ ЁРоЗЁРоКЁРоЛЁРоСЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоИЁРоМ ЁРоСЁРоЕЁРоВЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоЛЁРоКЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоЗЁРоКЁРоЛЁРоСЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА.</para>
   </article>
   <article number="5"><title>ЁРоЛЁРоКЁРоЕЁРоАЁРоА 5</title>
      <para>ЁРоДЁРоЙ ЁРоЗЁРоГ ЁРоОЁРоЕЁРоНЁРоЕЁРоОЁРоА ЁРоВЁРоЕЁРоВ ЁРоКЁРоА ЁРоОЁРоАЁРоР ЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоВЁРоЖЁРоА ЁРоИЁРоМ ЁРоАЁРоИЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоА ЁРоРЁРоЛЁРоИЁРоКЁРоА ЁРоИЁРоМ ЁРоЖЁРоКЁРоИЁРоЛЁРоА ЁРоИЁРоМ ЁРоСЁРоМЁРоБЁРоА ЁРоИЁРоДЁРоБЁРоА.</para>
   </article>
   <article number="6"><title>ЁРоЛЁРоКЁРоЕЁРоАЁРоА 6</title>
      <para>ЁРоЙЁРоК ЁРоЗЁРоГ ЁРоАЁРоМЁРоРЁРоА ЁРоВЁРоЕЁРоВ ЁРоОЁРоАЁРоР ЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоГЁРоИЁРоА ЁРоБЁРоИЁРоД ЁРоАЁРоИЁРоЙ ЁРоЗЁРоГ ЁРоОЁРоЕЁРоНЁРоЕЁРоОЁРоА ЁРоЛЁРоЛ ЁРоЛЁРоАЁРоМЁРоЕЁРоМ.</para>
   </article>
   <article number="7"><title>ЁРоЛЁРоКЁРоЕЁРоАЁРоА 7</title>
      <para>ЁРоЙЁРоК ЁРоАЁРоМЁРоРЁРоА ЁРоИЁРоКЁРоД ЁРоБЁРоЕЁРоБЁРоЕ ЁРоЛЁРоЛ ЁРоЛЁРоАЁРоМЁРоЕЁРоМ ЁРоЕЁРоВЁРоЕЁРоВ ЁРоОЁРоАЁРоР ЁРоМЁРоСЁРоИЁРоЕЁРоА ЁРоБЁРоИЁРоГ ЁРоЛЁРоАЁРоМЁРоЕЁРоМ ЁРоГЁРоКЁРоА ЁРоЛЁРоСЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоОЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоРЁРоЕЁРоМЁРоИЁРоА ЁРоБЁРоКЁРоИЁРоДЁРоИ. ЁРоЕЁРоЙЁРоК ЁРоАЁРоМЁРоРЁРоА ЁРоВЁРоЕЁРоВ ЁРоОЁРоИЁРоРЁРоИ ЁРоМЁРоСЁРоИЁРоЕЁРоА ЁРоБЁРоЕЁРоБЁРоЕ ЁРоЛЁРоЛ ЁРоЙЁРоК ЁРоОЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоРЁРоЕЁРоМЁРоИЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоРЁРоЛЁРоСЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоРЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоС ЁРоГЁРоАЁРоДЁРоА ЁРоБЁРоЕЁРоГЁРоЛЁРоА.</para>
   </article>
   <article number="8"><title>ЁРоЛЁРоКЁРоЕЁРоАЁРоА 8</title>
      <para>ЁРоЙЁРоК ЁРоЗЁРоГ ЁРоАЁРоИЁРоСЁРоКЁРоД ЁРоДЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоОЁРоАЁРоР ЁРоОЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоИЁРоА ЁРоБЁРоИЁРоГ ЁРоЗЁРоГ ЁРоБЁРоИЁРоС ЁРоГЁРоИЁРоМЁРоА ЁРоЛЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоБЁРоГЁРоЕЁРоИЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоКЁРоА ЁРоАЁРоМЁРоРЁРоИЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоОЁРоИЁРоРЁРоИ ЁРоЕЁРоИЁРоГЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоЕЁРоЛЁРоБЁРоК ЁРоГЁРоЖЁРоГЁРоЛЁРоА ЁРоРЁРоЕЁРоРЁРоМЁРоИЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоМЁРоСЁРоИЁРоЕЁРоМЁРоА ЁРоБЁРоИЁРоГ ЁРоЛЁРоМЁРоЕЁРоМЁРоА ЁРоРЁРоСЁРоНЁРоИЁРоА ЁРоИЁРоМ ЁРоБЁРоИЁРоГ ЁРоЛЁРоАЁРоМЁРоЕЁРоМ.</para>
   </article>
   <article number="9"><title>ЁРоЛЁРоКЁРоЕЁРоАЁРоА 9</title>
      <para>ЁРоВЁРоЕЁРоВ ЁРоДЁРоЙ ЁРоЗЁРоГ ЁРоКЁРоА ЁРоОЁРоАЁРоР ЁРоГЁРоБЁРоИЁРоЛЁРоА ЁРоИЁРоМ ЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоБЁРоА ЁРоВЁРоЕ ЁРоБЁРоИЁРоС ЁРоАЁРоНЁРоИЁРоЕЁРоА ЁРоИЁРоМ ЁРоСЁРоЕЁРоИЁРоГЁРоА ЁРоЛЁРоМ ЁРоАЁРоСЁРоЕЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоКЁРоА ЁРоЛЁРоАЁРоМЁРоЕЁРоМ.</para>
   </article>
   <article number="10"><title>ЁРоЛЁРоКЁРоЕЁРоАЁРоА 10</title>
      <para>ЁРоЙЁРоК ЁРоЗЁРоГ ЁРоАЁРоИЁРоКЁРоД ЁРоБЁРоЕЁРоБЁРоЕ ЁРоЛЁРоЛ ЁРоБЁРоИЁРоС ЁРоГЁРоИЁРоМЁРоА ЁРоЗЁРоАЁРоЕЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоКЁРоА ЁРоЛЁРоСЁРоВЁРоМЁРоИЁРоМЁРоА ЁРоВЁРоЕ ЁРоЛЁРоСЁРоИЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоДЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоВЁРоБЁРоЕЁРоИЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоЙЁРоК ЁРоВЁРоЕЁРоМЁРоЗЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоЕЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоКЁРоД.</para>
   </article>
   <article number="11"><title>ЁРоЛЁРоКЁРоЕЁРоАЁРоА 11</title>
      <orderedlist><listitem tag="▄Р."><para>ЁРоЙЁРоК ЁРоЗЁРоГ ЁРоГЁРоОЁРоАЁРоР ЁРоЛЁРоСЁРоДЁРоЛЁРоА ЁРоКЁРоРЁРоЛЁРоСЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоЛЁРоАЁРоМЁРоЕЁРоМ ЁРоАЁРоИЁРоСЁРоКЁРоД ЁРоДЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоКЁРоА ЁРоОЁРоАЁРоР ЁРоЗЁРоЕЁРоРЁРоБЁРоМЁРоА ЁРоВЁРоЕЁРоМЁРоДЁРоЙЁРоЕ ЁРоДЁРоК ЁРоГЁРоЛЁРоРЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоА ЁРоЛЁРоА ЁРоИЁРоКЁРоД ЁРоВЁРоЕЁРоМЁРоДЁРоЙЁРоЕ ЁРоБЁРоИЁРоГ ЁРоЛЁРоАЁРоМЁРоЕЁРоМ.</para>
         </listitem>
         <listitem tag="▄Т."><para>ЁРоКЁРоА ЁРоОЁРоАЁРоР ЁРоГЁРоИЁРоМЁРоА ЁРоДЁРоЙ ЁРоОЁРоЕЁРоНЁРоЕЁРоОЁРоА ЁРоЛЁРоМ ЁРоСЁРоЛЁРоЛЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЗЁРоГ ЁРоЕЁРоБЁРоГЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоИЁРоМ ЁРоЛЁРоЗЁРоОЁРоКЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЛЁРоМ ЁРоСЁРоЛЁРоЛЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЗЁРоГ ЁРоЕЁРоБЁРоГЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоАЁРоЗЁРоЙЁРоИ ЁРоАЁРоМ ЁРоЗЁРоГ ЁРоДЁРоГЁРоЗЁРоА ЁРоЛЁРоМЁРоГЁРоИ ЁРоОЁРоАЁРоР ЁРоЗЁРоЕЁРоРЁРоБЁРоМЁРоА ЁРоАЁРоИЁРоЙ ЁРоЗЁРоГ ЁРоВЁРоЕЁРоМЁРоЗЁРоА ЁРоЛЁРоАЁРоИЁРоЙ ЁРоЛЁРоАЁРоМЁРоЕЁРоМ ЁРоГЁРоАЁРоСЁРоЕЁРоА ЁРоИЁРоМ ЁРоЛЁРоАЁРоМЁРоЕЁРоМ ЁРоСЁРоБЁРоКЁРоИЁРоА ЁРоБЁРоГЁРоЕЁРоМЁРоА ЁРоБЁРоРЁРоЛЁРоКЁРоАЁРоИЁРоКЁРоД ЁРоРЁРоЕЁРоОЁРоА. ЁРоДЁРоЕ ЁРоБЁРоАЁРоИ ЁРоГЁРоЕЁРоМЁРоА ЁРоВЁРоЕЁРоВ ЁРоКЁРоА ЁРоОЁРоАЁРоР ЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоБЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоКЁРоД ЁРоЗЁРоГ ЁРоСЁРоМЁРоБЁРоА ЁРоБЁРоЕЁРоР ЁРоИЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоА ЁРоЛЁРоМ ЁРоГЁРоЕЁРоМЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоЛЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоДЁРоГЁРоЗЁРоА ЁРоЛЁРоМЁРоГЁРоИ.</para>
         </listitem>
      </orderedlist>
   </article>
   <article number="12"><title>ЁРоЛЁРоКЁРоЕЁРоАЁРоА 12</title>
      <para>ЁРоВЁРоЕЁРоВ ЁРоКЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоИ ЁРоВЁРоЕ ЁРоЗЁРоИЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоИЁРоКЁРоМЁРоИЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоЗЁРоГ ЁРоОЁРоЕЁРоНЁРоЕЁРоОЁРоА ЁРоИЁРоМ ЁРоБЁРоИЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоИЁРоМ ЁРоАЁРоВЁРоЕЁРоИЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоИЁРоМ ЁРоАЁРоИЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоА ЁРоИЁРоМ ЁРоРЁРоЛЁРоА ЁРоСЁРоБЁРоА ЁРоЛЁРоРЁРоЛЁРоДЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА. ЁРоЙЁРоК ЁРоЗЁРоГ ЁРоОЁРоЕЁРоНЁРоЕЁРоОЁРоА ЁРоАЁРоИЁРоСЁРоКЁРоД ЁРоДЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоОЁРоАЁРоР ЁРоМЁРоСЁРоИЁРоЕЁРоА ЁРоБЁРоИЁРоГ ЁРоЛЁРоАЁРоМЁРоЕЁРоМ ЁРоГЁРоЕЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоБЁРоК ЁРоДЁРоГЁРоЗЁРоА ЁРоПЁРоОЁРоЗЁРоИЁРоСЁРоА.</para>
   </article>
   <article number="13"><title>ЁРоЛЁРоКЁРоЕЁРоАЁРоА 13</title>
      <orderedlist><listitem tag="▄Р."><para>ЁРоЙЁРоК ЁРоЗЁРоГ ЁРоАЁРоИЁРоСЁРоКЁРоД ЁРоДЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоКЁРоЗЁРоАЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоВЁРоЕЁРоВЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЛЁРоЗЁРоИЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоВЁРоЕ ЁРоСЁРоЗЁРоЕЁРоБЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоЙЁРоК ЁРоАЁРоСЁРоЕЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоГЁРоИЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоК ЁРоАЁРоСЁРоЕЁРоА.</para>
         </listitem>
         <listitem tag="▄Т."><para>ЁРоЙЁРоК ЁРоЗЁРоГ ЁРоАЁРоИЁРоСЁРоКЁРоД ЁРоДЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоКЁРоРЁРоЕЁРоЛЁРоА ЁРоЙЁРоК ЁРоАЁРоСЁРоЕЁРоА ЁРоБЁРоЗЁРоБЁРоРЁРоА ЁРоАЁРоСЁРоЕЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоГЁРоИЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоК ЁРоАЁРоСЁРоЕЁРоА.</para>
         </listitem>
      </orderedlist>
   </article>
   <article number="14"><title>ЁРоЛЁРоКЁРоЕЁРоАЁРоА 14</title>
      <orderedlist><listitem tag="▄Р."><para>ЁРоЙЁРоК ЁРоЗЁРоГ ЁРоАЁРоИЁРоСЁРоКЁРоД ЁРоДЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоКЁРоЗЁРоАЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоСЁРоКЁРоБ ЁРоБЁРоИЁРоСЁРоВЁРоЕЁРоНЁРоА ЁРоОЁРоЕЁРоКЁРоИЁРоСЁРоИЁРоЛЁРоИЁРоА.</para>
         </listitem>
         <listitem tag="▄Т."><para>ЁРоЗЁРоГ ЁРоДЁРоГЁРоЗЁРоА ЁРоДЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоКЁРоИ ЁРоОЁРоИЁРоРЁРоА ЁРоИЁРоДЁРоБЁРоКЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЛЁРоА ЁРоАЁРоМЁРоРЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоБЁРоГЁРоМЁРоА ЁРоВЁРоМЁРоДЁРоА ЁРоКЁРоА ЁРоОЁРоЕЁРоКЁРоИЁРоСЁРоИЁРоЛЁРоИЁРоА ЁРоИЁРоМ ЁРоЕЁРоБЁРоГЁРоЕЁРоИЁРоСЁРоАЁРоКЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоБЁРоИЁРоЛЁРоА ЁРоЛЁРоМ ЁРоМЁРоИЁРоРЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоАЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЛЁРоЗЁРоИЁРоГЁРоА.</para>
         </listitem>
      </orderedlist>
   </article>
   <article number="15"><title>ЁРоЛЁРоКЁРоЕЁРоАЁРоА 15</title>
      <orderedlist><listitem tag="▄Р."><para>ЁРоЙЁРоК ЁРоЗЁРоГ ЁРоАЁРоИЁРоСЁРоКЁРоД ЁРоДЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЛЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоИЁРоСЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА.</para>
         </listitem>
         <listitem tag="▄Т."><para>ЁРоДЁРоЙ ЁРоЗЁРоГ ЁРоВЁРоЕЁРоВ ЁРоКЁРоА ЁРоОЁРоАЁРоР ЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоЗЁРоЕЁРоЛЁРоА ЁРоЛЁРоМ ЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоИЁРоСЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоИЁРоМ ЁРоЛЁРоМ ЁРоРЁРоЗЁРоКЁРоОЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоИЁРоСЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА.</para>
         </listitem>
      </orderedlist>
   </article>
   <article number="16"><title>ЁРоЛЁРоКЁРоЕЁРоАЁРоА 16</title>
      <orderedlist><listitem tag="▄Р."><para>ЁРоМЁРоРЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоЛ ЁРоГЁРоЙЁРоЕЁРоА ЁРоАЁРоИЁРоСЁРоКЁРоДЁРоЕЁРоМ ЁРоДЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоКЁРоВЁРоБЁРоЕЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоРЁРоСЁРоНЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоЙЁРоЕЁРоКЁРоС ЁРоГЁРоКЁРоА ЁРоДЁРоЙ ЁРоРЁРоЕЁРоС ЁРоВЁРоМЁРоНЁРоИЁРоА ЁРоИЁРоМ ЁРоСЁРоЕЁРоГЁРоИЁРоСЁРоМЁРоИЁРоА. ЁРоЕЁРоАЁРоИЁРоСЁРоКЁРоДЁРоЕЁРоМ ЁРоДЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЛЁРоАЁРоИЁРоЙ ЁРоАЁРоЗЁРоГЁРоГЁРоА ЁРоБЁРоГЁРоЕЁРоМЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоВЁРоБЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоИЁРоМ ЁРоЕЁРоОЁРоИЁРоСЁРоА.</para>
         </listitem>
         <listitem tag="▄Т."><para>ЁРоВЁРоБЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоБЁРоГ ЁРоРЁРоЛЁРоКЁРоА  ЁРоРЁРоЕЁРоОЁРоА ЁРоАЁРоИЁРоЛЁРоМ ЁРоСЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоИ ЁРоВЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоМЁРоА ЁРоНЁРоЖЁРоВЁРоЕЁРоА.</para>
         </listitem>
         <listitem tag="▄У."><para>ЁРоЙЁРоЕЁРоКЁРоОЁРоС ЁРоИЁРоКЁРоД ЁРоБЁРоИЁРоС ЁРоМЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоЗЁРоГ ЁРоРЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоОЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоВЁРоЕЁРоВ ЁРоОЁРоИЁРоРЁРоА ЁРоМЁРоСЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоБЁРоИЁРоГ ЁРоАЁРоМЁРоРЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоРЁРоЕЁРоКЁРоСЁРоМЁРоА.</para>
         </listitem>
      </orderedlist>
   </article>
   <article number="17"><title>ЁРоЛЁРоКЁРоЕЁРоАЁРоА 17</title>
      <orderedlist><listitem tag="▄Р."><para>ЁРоЙЁРоК ЁРоЗЁРоГ ЁРоАЁРоИЁРоСЁРоКЁРоД ЁРоДЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоГЁРоИЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоБЁРоМЁРоЕЁРоОЁРоРЁРоА ЁРоИЁРоМ ЁРоЕЁРоЛ ЁРоАЁРоЗЁРоЕЁРоМЁРоА.</para>
         </listitem>
         <listitem tag="▄Т."><para>ЁРоДЁРоЙ ЁРоЗЁРоГ ЁРоВЁРоЕЁРоВ ЁРоКЁРоА ЁРоОЁРоАЁРоР ЁРоЗЁРоНЁРоИЁРоЙЁРоА ЁРоЛЁРоМ ЁРоИЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА.</para>
         </listitem>
      </orderedlist>
   </article>
   <article number="18"><title>ЁРоЛЁРоКЁРоЕЁРоАЁРоА 18</title>
      <para>ЁРоЙЁРоК ЁРоЗЁРоГ ЁРоАЁРоИЁРоСЁРоКЁРоД ЁРоДЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоСЁРоЗЁРоЛЁРоМЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоГЁРоАЁРоМЁРоИЁРоС ЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоЕЁРоГЁРоИЁРоСЁРоА. ЁРоАЁРоДЁРоА ЁРоДЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоБЁРоЗЁРоБЁРоРЁРоИЁРоКЁРоА ЁРоДЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоРЁРоЗЁРоКЁРоОЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоСЁРоЕЁРоГЁРоИЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоИЁРоМ ЁРоДЁРоИЁРоЛЁРоМЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоЗЁРоАЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоБЁРоМЁРоЕЁРоОЁРоРЁРоА ЁРоИЁРоМ ЁРоЕЁРоЛ ЁРоВЁРоЕ ЁРоРЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоОЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоЛ ЁРоАЁРоЗЁРоЕЁРоМЁРоА.</para>
   </article>
   <article number="19"><title>ЁРоЛЁРоКЁРоЕЁРоАЁРоА 19</title>
      <para>ЁРоЙЁРоК ЁРоЗЁРоГ ЁРоАЁРоИЁРоСЁРоКЁРоД ЁРоДЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоИЁРоМЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоДЁРоЛЁРоЖЁРоЛЁРоСЁРоА. ЁРоАЁРоДЁРоА ЁРоЗЁРоАЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоБЁРоЗЁРоБЁРоРЁРоИЁРоКЁРоА ЁРоЗЁРоАЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоИЁРоМЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоКЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоВЁРоЕЁРоИ ЁРоЛЁРоМ ЁРоДЁРоЙ ЁРоАЁРоМЁРоРЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоИЁРоА ЁРоБЁРоСЁРоЕ ЁРоЕЁРоЛЁРоБЁРоКЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЛЁРоГЁРоЕЁРоМЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоБЁРоЙЁРоК ЁРоАЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоЗЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоДЁРоЕЁРоИЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоКЁРоА ЁРоЛЁРоИЁРоГЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоСЁРоЗЁРоЕЁРоБЁРоА.</para>
   </article>
   <article number="20"><title>ЁРоЛЁРоКЁРоЕЁРоАЁРоА 20</title>
      <orderedlist><listitem tag="▄Р."><para>ЁРоЙЁРоК ЁРоЗЁРоГ ЁРоАЁРоИЁРоСЁРоКЁРоД ЁРоДЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоЗЁРоАЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоКЁРоВЁРоЛЁРоИЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоБЁРоРЁРоКЁРоЛЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоРЁРоЕЁРоИЁРоЙЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА.</para>
         </listitem>
         <listitem tag="▄Т."><para>ЁРоКЁРоДЁРоЙ ЁРоЗЁРоГ ЁРоВЁРоЕЁРоВ ЁРоКЁРоА ЁРоЛЁРоСЁРоБЁРоИ ЁРоЗЁРоИЁРоКЁРоА ЁРоКЁРоРЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоЙЁРоА ЁРоВЁРоЕ ЁРоЗЁРоГ ЁРоЙЁРоМЁРоЕЁРоРЁРоМЁРоА.</para>
         </listitem>
      </orderedlist>
   </article>
   <article number="21"><title>ЁРоЛЁРоКЁРоЕЁРоАЁРоА 21</title>
      <orderedlist><listitem tag="▄Р."><para>ЁРоЙЁРоК ЁРоЗЁРоГ ЁРоАЁРоИЁРоСЁРоКЁРоД ЁРоДЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоКЁРоЛЁРоРЁРоСЁРоЕЁРоОЁРоА ЁРоВЁРоЕ ЁРоРЁРоЕЁРоКЁРоСЁРоМЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоАЁРоСЁРоЕЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоЕЁРоЖЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоЕЁРоЖ ЁРоИЁРоМ ЁРоБЁРоАЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоЗЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоЛЁРоИЁРоЕЁРоЛЁРоА ЁРоЛЁРоВЁРоЕЁРоБЁРоИЁРоА ЁРоБЁРоЗЁРоАЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА.</para>
         </listitem>
         <listitem tag="▄Т."><para>ЁРоЙЁРоК ЁРоЗЁРоГ ЁРоАЁРоИЁРоСЁРоКЁРоД ЁРоДЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоОЁРоАЁРоР ЁРоИЁРоДЁРоБЁРоА ЁРоОЁРоЕЁРоНЁРоС ЁРоКЁРоРЁРоЛЁРоКЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоРЁРоЕЁРоКЁРоА ЁРоВЁРоЕ ЁРоАЁРоСЁРоЕЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоКЁРоА ЁРоОЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоРЁРоМЁРоИЁРоА.</para>
         </listitem>
         <listitem tag="▄У."><para>ЁРоПЁРоБЁРоИЁРоМЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоАЁРоМЁРоРЁРоА ЁРоИЁРоКЁРоД ЁРоЛЁРоБЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоРЁРоЕЁРоКЁРоСЁРоМЁРоА. ЁРоАЁРоДЁРоА ЁРоПЁРоБЁРоИЁРоМЁРоА ЁРоВЁРоЕЁРоВ ЁРоОЁРоАЁРоР ЁРоСЁРоЕЁРоЛЁРоЛЁРоА ЁРоБЁРоВЁРоБЁРоИЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЖЁРоБЁРоМЁРоМЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоРЁРоЕЁРоИЁРоЕЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоОЁРоИЁРоРЁРоИ ЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоЙЁРоЛЁРоКЁРоА ЁРоБЁРоИЁРоДЁРоБЁРоКЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоЛЁРоКЁРоА ЁРоСЁРоРЁРоИЁРоАЁРоИЁРоС ЁРоЕЁРоБЁРоЕЁРоБЁРоЕ ЁРоБЁРоИЁРоК ЁРоЙЁРоК ЁРоЗЁРоГ ЁРоИЁРоМ ЁРоАЁРоИЁРоЙ ЁРоЗЁРоГ ЁРоАЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоЗЁРоА ЁРоАЁРоЗЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоАЁРоИЁРоЙЁРоА ЁРоЗЁРоАЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоВЁРоБЁРоИЁРоМЁРоА ЁРоОЁРоИЁРоРЁРоА ЁРоМЁРоСЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА.</para>
         </listitem>
      </orderedlist>
   </article>
   <article number="22"><title>ЁРоЛЁРоКЁРоЕЁРоАЁРоА 22</title>
      <para>ЁРоЙЁРоК ЁРоЗЁРоГ ЁРоОЁРоЕЁРоНЁРоЕЁРоОЁРоА ЁРоАЁРоИЁРоЙ ЁРоЗЁРоГ ЁРоДЁРоГЁРоЛЁРоА ЁРоВЁРоЕ ЁРоРЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоОЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоАЁРоИЁРоСЁРоКЁРоД ЁРоДЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоКЁРоЗЁРоСЁРоЕЁРоВЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоРЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоОЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоВЁРоЕ ЁРоСЁРоЛЁРоЛЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоБЁРоАЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоЗЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоБЁРоГЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоАЁРоСЁРоЕЁРоИЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоДЁРоИЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоСЁРоБЁРоКЁРоИЁРоСЁРоА. ЁРоЕЁРоЙЁРоК ЁРоЗЁРоГ ЁРоАЁРоИЁРоЙ ЁРоЛЁРоБЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоАЁРоСЁРоЕЁРоА ЁРоАЁРоИЁРоСЁРоКЁРоД ЁРоДЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоКЁРоДЁРоИЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоАЁРоЛЁРоМЁРоЕЁРоЛЁРоИЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоРЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоОЁРоИЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоГЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоМЁРоИЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоЕЁРоЛЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоЛ ЁРоАЁРоИЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоЛЁРоСЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоОЁРоЕЁРоНЁРоЕЁРоОЁРоИЁРоСЁРоА.</para>
   </article>
   <article number="23"><title>ЁРоЛЁРоКЁРоЕЁРоАЁРоА 23</title>
      <orderedlist><listitem tag="▄Р."><para>ЁРоЙЁРоК ЁРоЗЁРоГ ЁРоАЁРоМЁРоРЁРоА ЁРоАЁРоИЁРоСЁРоКЁРоД ЁРоДЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоКЁРоОЁРоЕЁРоКЁРоЗЁРоМЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоЗЁРоАЁРоЕЁРоАЁРоИЁРоКЁРоД ЁРоКЁРоВЁРоБЁРоИЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоОЁРоЕЁРоКЁРоЗЁРоМЁРоА ЁРоВЁРоЕ ЁРоЗЁРоГ ЁРоАЁРоЙЁРоМЁРоИЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоПЁРоОЁРоИ ЁРоЕЁРоОЁРоАЁРоР ЁРоМЁРоСЁРоИЁРоЕЁРоА ЁРоЛЁРоМ ЁРоБЁРоСЁРоИЁРоКЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА.</para>
         </listitem>
         <listitem tag="▄Т."><para>ЁРоЙЁРоК ЁРоЗЁРоГ ЁРоГЁРоКЁРоА ЁРоДЁРоЙ ЁРоОЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоРЁРоЕЁРоМЁРоИЁРоА ЁРоАЁРоИЁРоСЁРоКЁРоД ЁРоДЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоОЁРоАЁРоР ЁРоОЁРоЕЁРоИЁРоА ЁРоЛЁРоАЁРоИЁРоЙ ЁРоДЁРоЕ ЁРоАЁРоЗЁРоЕЁРоМЁРоА.</para>
         </listitem>
         <listitem tag="▄У."><para>ЁРоЙЁРоК ЁРоЗЁРоГ ЁРоАЁРоИЁРоСЁРоКЁРоД ЁРоДЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЛЁРоА ЁРоАЁРоИЁРоВЁРоЕЁРоА ЁРоЙЁРоИЁРоМЁРоА ЁРоЛЁРоРЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоА ЁРоЛЁРоСЁРоЕ ЁРоЕЁРоЛЁРоА ЁРоЙЁРоЕЁРоКЁРоОЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЛЁРоА ЁРоЗЁРоИЁРоА ЁРоБЁРоАЁРоИЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоА.</para>
         </listitem>
         <listitem tag="▄Х."><para>ЁРоЙЁРоК ЁРоЗЁРоГ ЁРоАЁРоИЁРоСЁРоКЁРоД ЁРоДЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоКЁРоРЁРоСЁРоАЁРоНЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоЖЁРоБЁРоВЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоИЁРоЛ ЁРоЗЁРоЕЁРоИЁРоГЁРоА ЁРоСЁРоЕЁРоВЁРоЕЁРоИЁРоА ЁРоКЁРоЗЁРоЛЁРоИЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоИЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоЕЁРоМЁРоА.</para>
         </listitem>
      </orderedlist>
   </article>
   <article number="24"><title>ЁРоЛЁРоКЁРоЕЁРоАЁРоА 24</title>
      <para>ЁРоЙЁРоК ЁРоЗЁРоГ ЁРоАЁРоИЁРоСЁРоКЁРоД ЁРоДЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЛЁРоА ЁРоЛЁРоМЁРоИЁРоЗЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоБЁРоЕЁРоНЁРоЛЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоБЁРоЗЁРоБЁРоРЁРоА ЁРоЛЁРоСЁРоЗЁРоЛЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоНЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоОЁРоЕЁРоКЁРоЗЁРоМЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоИЁРоЕЁРоЛЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоЛЁРоМЁРоИЁРоЗЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоБЁРоОЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоМЁРоА.</para>
   </article>
   <article number="25"><title>ЁРоЛЁРоКЁРоЕЁРоАЁРоА 25</title>
      <orderedlist><listitem tag="▄Р."><para>ЁРоЙЁРоК ЁРоЗЁРоГ ЁРоАЁРоИЁРоСЁРоКЁРоД ЁРоДЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоКЁРоЗЁРоГ ЁРоЛЁРоГЁРоЕЁРоА ЁРоПЁРоОЁРоИ ЁРоЛЁРоМ ЁРоЗЁРоЕЁРоКЁРоЛЁРоМЁРоА ЁРоБЁРоЗЁРоБЁРоРЁРоА ЁРоЛЁРоЙЁРоЕЁРоКЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоКЁРоБЁРоРЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоБЁРоИЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоГЁРоЕЁРоЛЁРоМЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоДЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоКЁРоЗЁРоСЁРоЕЁРоВЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоБЁРоГЁРоЕЁРоМЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоБЁРоСЁРоКЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоАЁРоЕЁРоЛЁРоКЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоНЁРоИЁРоБЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоАЁРоДЁРоБЁРоКЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоАЁРоЗЁРоЕЁРоМЁРоА.</para>
         </listitem>
         <listitem tag="▄Т."><para>ЁРоИЁРоЛЁРоИЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоИЁРоКЁРоГЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоАЁРоИЁРоСЁРоКЁРоДЁРоЕЁРоМ ЁРоДЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЛЁРоА ЁРоСЁРоВЁРоБЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоДЁРоИЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЛЁРоСЁРоГЁРоКЁРоМЁРоИЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоИЁРоДЁРоКЁРоА ЁРоБЁРоЕЁРоИЁРоА ЁРоБЁРоАЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоЗЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоВЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоА ЁРоИЁРоМ ЁРоКЁРоА ЁРоАЁРоИЁРоСЁРоКЁРоДЁРоЕЁРоМ ЁРоДЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоАЁРоИЁРоЙ ЁРоАЁРоЗЁРоГЁРоГЁРоА.</para>
         </listitem>
      </orderedlist>
   </article>
   <article number="26"><title>ЁРоЛЁРоКЁРоЕЁРоАЁРоА 26</title>
      <orderedlist><listitem tag="▄Р."><para>ЁРоЙЁРоК ЁРоЗЁРоГ ЁРоАЁРоИЁРоСЁРоКЁРоД ЁРоДЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоКЁРоИЁРоЕЁРоКЁРоОЁРоМЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоИЁРоЕЁРоКЁРоОЁРоМЁРоА ЁРоВЁРоЕЁРоВ ЁРоДЁРоБЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоКЁРоА ЁРоОЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоМЁРоА ЁРоВЁРоЕ ЁРоЛЁРоГЁРоЕЁРоРЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоРЁРоЕЁРоБЁРоИЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоДЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоРЁРоСЁРоАЁРоНЁРоМЁРоА. ЁРоЕЁРоВЁРоЕЁРоВ ЁРоЙЁРоК ЁРоАЁРоМЁРоРЁРоА ЁРоРЁРоЛЁРоК ЁРоИЁРоЕЁРоКЁРоОЁРоМЁРоА ЁРоРЁРоЕЁРоБЁРоИЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоИЁРоЕЁРоКЁРоОЁРоМЁРоА ЁРоСЁРоЛЁРоМЁРоИЁРоЛЁРоИЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоКЁРоИЁРоА ЁРоВЁРоЕЁРоВ ЁРоДЁРоБЁРоА ЁРоОЁРоСЁРоИЁРоЗЁРоА ЁРоЛЁРоА ЁРоЙЁРоК ЁРоЗЁРоГ ЁРоГЁРоКЁРоА ЁРоОЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоРЁРоЕЁРоМЁРоИЁРоА ЁРоБЁРоМЁРоИЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоК ЁРоЛЁРоПЁРоИЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоАЁРоМЁРоРЁРоА.</para>
         </listitem>
         <listitem tag="▄Т."><para>ЁРоИЁРоЕЁРоКЁРоОЁРоМЁРоА ЁРоВЁРоЕЁРоВ ЁРоДЁРоБЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоРЁРоИЁРоЛЁРоА ЁРоКЁРоЛЁРоСЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоАЁРоМЁРоРЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоЛЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоИЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЛЁРоИЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЖЁРоГЁРоЛЁРоА ЁРоАЁРоМЁРоРЁРоИЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоИЁРоАЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоРЁРоЕЁРоРЁРоАЁРоМЁРоИЁРоСЁРоА. ЁРоВЁРоЕЁРоВ ЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоЗЁРоА ЁРоОЁРоЕЁРоЛЁРоИЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоЛЁРоСЁРоЛЁРоБЁРоКЁРоМЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоЗЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоБЁРоИЁРоК ЁРоЙЁРоКЁРоИ ЁРоАЁРоСЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоВЁРоМЁРоНЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоВЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоСЁРоЕЁРоГЁРоСЁРоМЁРоИЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоЛЁРоЖЁРоИЁРоГ ЁРоЕЁРоБЁРоГЁРоЕЁРоИЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоАЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЛЁРоЗЁРоИЁРоГЁРоА ЁРоКЁРоЗЁРоЛЁРоИЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоРЁРоКЁРоЛЁРоА.</para>
         </listitem>
         <listitem tag="▄У."><para>ЁРоАЁРоБЁРоДЁРоА ЁРоАЁРоИЁРоСЁРоКЁРоДЁРоЕЁРоМ ЁРоДЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоКЁРоВЁРоБЁРоИЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоИЁРоЕЁРоКЁРоОЁРоМЁРоА ЁРоЛЁРоА ЁРоИЁРоДЁРоКЁРоИЁРоДЁРоИ.</para>
         </listitem>
      </orderedlist>
   </article>
   <article number="27"><title>ЁРоЛЁРоКЁРоЕЁРоАЁРоА 27</title>
      <orderedlist><listitem tag="▄Р."><para>ЁРоЙЁРоК ЁРоЗЁРоГ ЁРоАЁРоИЁРоСЁРоКЁРоД ЁРоДЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЛЁРоА ЁРоРЁРоЕЁРоЙЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоВЁРоЕ ЁРоЗЁРоИЁРоА ЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоГЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоМЁРоИЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоЗЁРоГ ЁРоРЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоОЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоРЁРоЛЁРоКЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоИЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоЕЁРоМЁРоА ЁРоЛЁРоМ ЁРоАЁРоЛЁРоМЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоРЁРоЕЁРоЙЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоВЁРоЕ ЁРоЛЁРоСЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоМЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоКЁРоЛЁРоИЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоИЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоЕЁРоАЁРоМЁРоЕ.</para>
         </listitem>
         <listitem tag="▄Т."><para>ЁРоЙЁРоК ЁРоЗЁРоГ ЁРоАЁРоИЁРоСЁРоКЁРоД ЁРоДЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоКЁРоМЁРоСЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоИЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоЕЁРоМЁРоА ЁРоЛЁРоМ ЁРоОЁРоЕЁРоКЁРоЗЁРоМЁРоА ЁРоСЁРоБЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоДЁРоЕЁРоКЁРоМЁРоИЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоОЁРоКЁРоСЁРоИ ЁРоЛЁРоМ ЁРоАЁРоЛЁРоМЁРоА ЁРоАЁРоИЁРоЙЁРоА ЁРоДЁРоЕ ЁРоИЁРоКЁРоД ЁРоНЁРоИЁРоЕЁРоЛЁРоА.</para>
         </listitem>
      </orderedlist>
   </article>
   <article number="28"><title>ЁРоЛЁРоКЁРоЕЁРоАЁРоА 28</title>
      <para>ЁРоЙЁРоК ЁРоЗЁРоГ ЁРоАЁРоИЁРоСЁРоКЁРоД ЁРоДЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЛЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоИЁРоЖЁРоА ЁРоРЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоОЁРоИЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоБЁРоКЁРоИЁРоА ЁРоАЁРоИЁРоЙЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоЖЁРоГЁРоЛЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоЗЁРоАЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоЗЁРоЕЁРоМЁРоА ЁРоВЁРоЕ ЁРоАЁРоДЁРоА ЁРоБЁРоЕЁРоГЁРоЛЁРоА ЁРоОЁРоИЁРоРЁРоИ ЁРоМЁРоСЁРоИЁРоЕЁРоА ЁРоБЁРоЗЁРоГ ЁРоРЁРоЙЁРоКЁРоА ЁРоВЁРоЕЁРоМЁРоИЁРоА.</para>
   </article>
   <article number="29"><title>ЁРоЛЁРоКЁРоЕЁРоАЁРоА 29</title>
      <orderedlist><listitem tag="▄Р."><para>ЁРоЙЁРоК ЁРоЗЁРоГ ЁРоАЁРоМЁРоРЁРоА ЁРоАЁРоИЁРоСЁРоКЁРоД ЁРоЕЁРоВЁРоБЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоКЁРоОЁРоЕЁРоС ЁРоРЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоОЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоАЁРоИЁРоЙЁРоА ЁРоЛЁРоСЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоМЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоОЁРоЕЁРоНЁРоЕЁРоОЁРоИЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоИЁРоКЁРоД ЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоЛЁРоЙЁРоЕЁРоМ.</para>
         </listitem>
         <listitem tag="▄Т."><para>ЁРоБЁРоГЁРоЕЁРоМЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоЛЁРоОЁРоКЁРоЗЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоДЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоИЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоЗЁРоАЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЙЁРоК ЁРоЗЁРоГ ЁРоВЁРоЕЁРоВ ЁРоЛЁРоИЁРоЛЁРоЕ ЁРоДЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоЗЁРоАЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоАЁРоЗЁРоЕЁРоМЁРоА.</para>
         </listitem>
         <listitem tag="▄У."><para>ЁРоАЁРоМЁРоА ЁРоЖЁРоГЁРоЛЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоЗЁРоАЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоИЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоВЁРоЕЁРоВ ЁРоВЁРоЕ ЁРоЙЁРоКЁРоИ ЁРоАЁРоДЁРоБЁРоКЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоКЁРоА ЁРоОЁРоИЁРоРЁРоИ ЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоОЁРоКЁРоЗЁРоА ЁРоБЁРоЗЁРоГ ЁРоАЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоЗЁРоА ЁРоКЁРоБЁРоГЁРоЕ ЁРоЛЁРоМ ЁРоМЁРоИЁРоРЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоБЁРоМЁРоИЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоАЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЛЁРоЗЁРоИЁРоГЁРоА.</para>
         </listitem>
      </orderedlist>
   </article>
   <article number="30"><title>ЁРоЛЁРоКЁРоЕЁРоАЁРоА 30</title>
      <para>ЁРоЛЁРоМЁРоГЁРоИЁРоМЁРоА ЁРоГЁРоКЁРоИЁРоМЁРоА ЁРоОЁРоИЁРоРЁРоА ЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоЗЁРоЕЁРоА ЁРоВЁРоЕ ЁРоАЁРоДЁРоА ЁРоБЁРоЕЁРоГЁРоЛЁРоА ЁРоВЁРоЕЁРоВ ЁРоКЁРоА ЁРоОЁРоИЁРоРЁРоИ ЁРоЛЁРоСЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоВЁРоЛЁРоА ЁРоБЁРоИЁРоГ ЁРоЗЁРоГ ЁРоАЁРоСЁРоЕЁРоА ЁРоИЁРоМ ЁРоВЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоИЁРоМ ЁРоОЁРоЕЁРоНЁРоЕЁРоОЁРоА ЁРоКЁРоБЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоВЁРоЕ ЁРоЕЁРоБЁРоЕЁРоГЁРоЕЁРоИЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЛЁРоЗЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоДЁРоЙ ЁРоЗЁРоГ ЁРоЛЁРоМ ЁРоАЁРоМЁРоА ЁРоДЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоИЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоИЁРоМ ЁРоЗЁРоАЁРоЕЁРоЕЁРоИЁРоСЁРоА ЁРоЛЁРоЕЁРоСЁРоЗЁРоЕЁРоА ЁРоЕЁРоКЁРоК.</para>
   </article>
</udhr>
