<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<!--© The Office of the High Commisioner for Human Rights-->
<udhr xmlns="http://www.unhchr.ch/udhr" iso639-3="san" xml:lang="sa-Sidd" key="san_sidd" n="Sanskrit (Siddham)" dir="ltr" iso15924="Sidd"><note><para>𑖦𑖯𑖡𑖪𑖯𑖠𑖰𑖎𑖯𑖨𑖯𑖜𑖯𑖽 𑖕𑖯𑖐𑖝-𑖀𑖥𑖰𑖑𑖺𑖬𑖜𑖯𑖧𑖯𑖾 𑖢𑖽𑖓𑖯𑖫𑖝𑖿𑖝𑖦𑖯 𑖪𑖨𑖿𑖬𑖢𑖳𑖨𑖿𑖝𑖰𑖾𑗂</para>
      <para>1948-1998</para>
      <para>𑖦𑖯𑖡𑖪𑖯𑖠𑖰𑖎𑖯𑖨𑖯𑖜𑖯𑖽 𑖕𑖯𑖐𑖝-𑖀𑖥𑖰𑖑𑖺𑖬𑖜𑖯 {𑖀𑖡𑖿𑖧-𑖥𑖯𑖬𑖯-𑖨𑖳𑖢𑖯𑖡𑖿𑖝𑖨𑖯𑖜𑖰 𑖭𑖯𑖦𑖐𑖿𑖨𑖿𑖧𑖫𑖿𑖓}</para>
      <para>𑖊𑖝𑖓𑖿𑖔𑖝𑖯𑖤𑖿𑖟𑖭𑖿𑖧 𑖀𑖬𑖿𑖘𑖓𑖝𑖿𑖪𑖯𑖨𑖰𑖽𑖫𑖝𑖿𑖝𑖦𑖸 𑖪𑖨𑖿𑖬𑖸 𑖚𑖰𑖭𑖸𑖦𑖿𑖤𑖨-𑖦𑖯𑖭𑖸 𑖀𑖥𑖿𑖧𑖲𑖢𑖐𑖝𑖾 𑖀𑖥𑖰𑖑𑖺𑖬𑖰𑖝𑖫𑖿𑖓, 𑖦𑖮𑖯𑖭𑖥𑖯𑖧𑖯𑖾 217-𑖀-{3}-𑖂𑖝𑖿𑖧𑖯𑖏𑖿𑖧𑖾 𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖭𑖿𑖝𑖯𑖪𑖾𑗂</para>
   </note>
   <preamble><title>𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖭𑖿𑖝𑖯𑖪𑖡𑖯</title>
      <para>𑖧𑖝𑖿𑖨 𑖕𑖐𑖝𑖰 𑖫𑖯𑖡𑖿𑖝𑖰-𑖡𑖿𑖧𑖯𑖧-𑖭𑖿𑖪𑖯𑖝𑖡𑖿𑖝𑖿𑖨𑖿𑖧𑖯𑖜𑖯𑖽 𑖁𑖠𑖯𑖨𑖾 𑖦𑖯𑖡𑖪-𑖢𑖨𑖰𑖪𑖯𑖨𑖭𑖿𑖧 𑖭𑖨𑖿𑖪𑖸𑖬𑖯𑖦𑖢𑖰 𑖭𑖟𑖭𑖿𑖧𑖯𑖡𑖯𑖽 𑖭𑖯𑖦𑖿𑖧𑖯𑖡𑖯𑖽 𑖀𑖏𑖜𑖿𑖚𑖰𑖝𑖯𑖡𑖯𑖗𑖿𑖓 𑖀𑖠𑖰𑖎𑖯𑖨𑖯𑖜𑖯𑖽, 𑖢𑖯𑖨𑖦𑖿𑖢𑖨𑖰𑖎-𑖐𑖻𑖨𑖪𑖭𑖿𑖧 𑖓𑖯𑖥𑖰𑖕𑖿𑖗𑖯𑖡𑖸 𑖭𑖿𑖧𑖯𑖝𑖿,𑖧𑖝𑖿𑖨 𑖦𑖯𑖡𑖪𑖯𑖠𑖰𑖎𑖯𑖨𑖯𑖜𑖯𑖽 𑖀𑖪𑖦𑖯𑖡𑖸𑖡 𑖀𑖡𑖯𑖟𑖨𑖸𑖜 𑖓 𑖎𑖯𑖨𑖿𑖧𑖯𑖜𑖰 𑖟𑖲𑖨𑖿𑖟𑖯𑖡𑖿𑖝𑖨𑖳𑖢𑖸𑖜 𑖢𑖨𑖰𑖜𑖦𑖰𑖝𑖯𑖡𑖰, 𑖧𑖹𑖾 𑖦𑖯𑖡𑖪𑖱𑖧-𑖓𑖸𑖝𑖡𑖯 𑖪𑖰𑖎𑖿𑖬𑖺𑖥𑖰𑖝𑖯, 𑖀𑖢𑖰 𑖓,𑖭𑖯𑖦𑖯𑖡𑖿𑖧-𑖕𑖡𑖯𑖡𑖯𑖽 𑖄𑖓𑖿𑖓𑖝𑖦𑖯𑖎𑖯𑖽𑖎𑖿𑖬𑖯𑖾 𑖀𑖥𑖰𑖑𑖺𑖬𑖰𑖝𑖯𑖾 𑖭𑖿𑖧𑖲𑖾, 𑖊𑖪𑖽 𑖮𑖰 𑖡𑖳𑖝𑖡𑖪𑖰𑖫𑖿𑖪𑖯𑖨𑖽𑖥𑖸𑖜, 𑖦𑖯𑖡𑖪𑖯𑖾 𑖀𑖥𑖰𑖪𑖿𑖧𑖎𑖿𑖝𑖸𑖾 𑖭𑖿𑖪𑖯𑖝𑖡𑖿𑖝𑖿𑖨𑖿𑖧𑖦𑖡𑖲𑖥𑖪𑖰𑖝𑖲𑖽 𑖫𑖎𑖿𑖬𑖿𑖧𑖡𑖿𑖝𑖰, 𑖡𑖰𑖨𑖿𑖥𑖧𑖯𑖫𑖿𑖓 𑖥𑖪𑖰𑖝𑖯𑖨𑖾, 𑖧𑖝𑖿𑖨 𑖓𑖹𑖝𑖝𑖿 𑖀𑖡𑖰𑖪𑖯𑖨𑖿𑖧𑖦𑖿 𑖧𑖟𑖰 𑖫𑖺𑖬𑖜𑖯𑖝𑖿𑖧𑖯𑖓𑖯𑖨𑖯𑖡𑖿 𑖪𑖰𑖨𑖲𑖠𑖿𑖧 𑖀𑖡𑖿𑖝𑖰𑖦-𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖧𑖯𑖭𑖝𑖿𑖪𑖸𑖡 𑖦𑖡𑖲𑖬𑖿𑖧𑖾, 𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖧𑖯𑖭𑖯𑖡𑖲𑖬𑖿𑖙𑖯𑖡𑖯𑖨𑖿𑖞𑖽 𑖡𑖹𑖪 𑖪𑖰𑖪𑖫𑖱𑖎𑖿𑖨𑖰𑖧𑖝𑖸 𑖓𑖸𑖝𑖿𑖝𑖟𑖯, 𑖦𑖯𑖡𑖪𑖯𑖠𑖰𑖎𑖯𑖨𑖯𑖾 𑖪𑖰𑖠𑖰-𑖡𑖰𑖧𑖦𑖸𑖡 𑖭𑖽𑖨𑖎𑖿𑖬𑖜𑖱𑖧𑖯𑖾,𑖧𑖝𑖿𑖨 𑖓 𑖨𑖯𑖬𑖿𑖘𑖿𑖨𑖸𑖬𑖲 𑖢𑖨𑖭𑖿𑖢𑖨𑖽 𑖭𑖏𑖿𑖧-𑖭𑖦𑖿𑖤𑖡𑖿𑖠𑖯𑖡𑖯𑖽 𑖪𑖰𑖎𑖯𑖭𑖕𑖯𑖝𑖽 𑖭𑖦𑖲𑖡𑖿𑖡𑖸𑖝𑖲𑖽 𑖢𑖨𑖦𑖯𑖪𑖫𑖿𑖧𑖎𑖽 𑖭𑖿𑖧𑖯𑖝𑖿,𑖧𑖝𑖿𑖨 𑖦𑖻𑖩𑖰𑖎𑖸𑖬𑖲 𑖦𑖯𑖡𑖪𑖯𑖠𑖰𑖎𑖯𑖨𑖸𑖬𑖲 𑖭𑖽𑖧𑖲𑖎𑖿𑖝-𑖨𑖯𑖬𑖿𑖘𑖿𑖨-𑖭𑖽𑖑𑖭𑖿𑖧 𑖕𑖡𑖯𑖾 𑖑𑖺𑖬𑖜𑖯𑖢𑖝𑖿𑖨𑖸 𑖭𑖿𑖪𑖱𑖧𑖯𑖭𑖿𑖞𑖯𑖽 𑖟𑖴𑖛𑗀𑖱𑖎𑖴𑖝𑖪𑖡𑖿𑖝𑖾, 𑖤𑖴𑖮𑖝𑖿𑖝𑖨𑖸 𑖓 𑖭𑖿𑖪𑖯𑖝𑖡𑖿𑖝𑖿𑖨𑖿𑖧𑖸 𑖥𑖟𑖿𑖨𑖝𑖨𑖽 𑖕𑖱𑖪𑖡𑖭𑖿𑖝𑖨𑖽 𑖭𑖯𑖦𑖯𑖕𑖰𑖎-𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖐𑖝𑖰𑖽 𑖓 𑖭𑖦𑖲𑖡𑖿𑖡𑖸𑖝𑖲𑖽 𑖡𑖰𑖨𑖿𑖜𑖱𑖝𑖦𑖿, 𑖭𑖿𑖝𑖿𑖨𑖱-𑖢𑖲𑖨𑖲𑖬𑖯𑖜𑖯𑖽 𑖭𑖯𑖦𑖿𑖧𑖯𑖠𑖰𑖎𑖯𑖨𑖸𑖬𑖲 𑖦𑖯𑖡𑖪-𑖪𑖿𑖧𑖎𑖿𑖝𑖸𑖾 𑖐𑖻𑖨𑖪𑖸 𑖦𑖳𑖩𑖿𑖧𑖸 𑖓 𑖡𑖰𑖬𑖿𑖙𑖯 𑖟𑖴𑖛𑗀𑖱𑖎𑖴𑖝𑖯,𑖧𑖝𑖿𑖨, 𑖭𑖟𑖭𑖿𑖧𑖟𑖸𑖫𑖯𑖾 𑖦𑖻𑖩𑖰𑖎-𑖭𑖿𑖪𑖯𑖝𑖡𑖿𑖗𑖿𑖧𑖯𑖜𑖯𑖽 𑖦𑖯𑖡𑖪𑖯𑖠𑖰𑖎𑖯𑖨𑖯𑖜𑖯𑖗𑖿𑖓 𑖢𑖨𑖰𑖢𑖯𑖩𑖡𑖯𑖨𑖿𑖞𑖽 𑖪𑖹𑖫𑖿𑖪𑖰𑖎𑖯𑖟𑖨𑖭𑖿𑖧 𑖭𑖦𑖲𑖡𑖿𑖡𑖝𑖧𑖸 𑖓, 𑖭𑖽𑖧𑖲𑖎𑖿𑖝-𑖨𑖯𑖬𑖿𑖘𑖿𑖨-𑖭𑖽𑖑𑖸𑖡 𑖭𑖽𑖥𑖳𑖧 𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖝𑖰𑖫𑖿𑖨𑖲𑖝𑖯𑖾 𑖭𑖿𑖧𑖲𑖾,𑖧𑖝𑖿𑖨 𑖭𑖿𑖪𑖱𑖧-𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖝𑖰𑖫𑖿𑖨𑖲𑖝𑖱𑖡𑖯𑖽 𑖢𑖨𑖰𑖢𑖳𑖨𑖿𑖜𑖝𑖯𑖧𑖹 𑖊𑖝𑖸𑖬𑖯𑖽 𑖀𑖠𑖰𑖎𑖯𑖨𑖯𑖜𑖯𑖽𑖭𑖿𑖪𑖯𑖝𑖡𑖿𑖝𑖿𑖨𑖿𑖧𑖯𑖜𑖯𑖽 𑖓 𑖭𑖯𑖦𑖯𑖡𑖿𑖧𑖯𑖪𑖐𑖦𑖡𑖽 𑖦𑖮𑖝𑖿𑖝𑖦𑖽 𑖦𑖮𑖝𑖿𑖝𑖿𑖪𑖯𑖠𑖯𑖧𑖰 𑖓 𑖭𑖿𑖧𑖯𑖝𑖿,𑖝𑖟𑖨𑖿𑖞𑖽 𑖭𑖯𑖦𑖿𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖝𑖦𑖿,𑖦𑖮𑖯𑖭𑖥𑖯 𑖭𑖨𑖿𑖪𑖸𑖬𑖯𑖽 𑖨𑖯𑖬𑖿𑖘𑖿𑖨𑖯𑖜𑖯𑖽 𑖭𑖨𑖿𑖪𑖸𑖬𑖯𑖽 𑖓 𑖕𑖡𑖯𑖡𑖯𑖽 𑖎𑖴𑖝𑖸 𑖭𑖯𑖦𑖯𑖡𑖿𑖧𑖺𑖢𑖩𑖤𑖿𑖠𑖰-𑖭𑖿𑖝𑖨-𑖨𑖳𑖢𑖸𑖜 𑖦𑖯𑖡𑖪𑖯𑖠𑖰𑖎𑖯𑖨𑖯𑖜𑖯𑖽 𑖊𑖡𑖯𑖽 𑖕𑖯𑖐𑖝𑖯𑖥𑖰𑖑𑖺𑖬𑖜𑖯𑖽 𑖀𑖥𑖰𑖑𑖺𑖬𑖧𑖝𑖰𑗂 𑖭𑖦𑖯𑖕𑖭𑖿𑖧 𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖝𑖿𑖧𑖸𑖎𑖦𑖢𑖰 𑖀𑖽𑖐𑖦𑖿, 𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖝𑖿𑖧𑖸𑖎𑖦𑖢𑖰 𑖕𑖡𑖾, 𑖦𑖡𑖭𑖰 𑖭𑖝𑖝𑖽 𑖀𑖥𑖰𑖑𑖺𑖬𑖜𑖯𑖦𑖸𑖡𑖯𑖽 𑖡𑖰𑖠𑖯𑖧, 𑖊𑖝𑖸𑖬𑖯𑖽 𑖀𑖠𑖰𑖎𑖯𑖨𑖯𑖜𑖯𑖽𑖭𑖿𑖪𑖯𑖝𑖡𑖿𑖝𑖿𑖨𑖿𑖧𑖯𑖜𑖯𑖽 𑖓 𑖎𑖴𑖝𑖸 𑖭𑖦𑖿𑖦𑖯𑖡𑖽 𑖭𑖦𑖲𑖡𑖿𑖡𑖸𑖝𑖲𑖽 𑖫𑖰𑖎𑖿𑖬𑖯𑖠𑖿𑖧𑖯𑖢𑖡𑖯𑖨𑖿𑖞𑖽 𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖧𑖝𑖰𑖬𑖿𑖧𑖝𑖸, 𑖀𑖢𑖰 𑖓, 𑖭𑖿𑖪𑖱𑖧-𑖎𑖿𑖬𑖸𑖝𑖿𑖨𑖯𑖠𑖰𑖎𑖯𑖨𑖯𑖡𑖿𑖝𑖨𑖿𑖐𑖝𑖽 𑖎𑖿𑖬𑖸𑖝𑖿𑖨𑖪𑖯𑖭𑖿𑖝𑖪𑖿𑖧𑖸𑖬𑖲 𑖕𑖡𑖸𑖬𑖲 𑖭𑖿𑖪𑖸𑖬𑖲 𑖓 𑖭𑖟𑖭𑖿𑖧𑖟𑖸𑖫𑖸𑖬𑖲 𑖝𑖟𑖱𑖧𑖸𑖬𑖲 𑖕𑖡𑖸𑖬𑖲 𑖓 𑖭𑖿𑖪𑖱𑖧-𑖪𑖹𑖫𑖿𑖪𑖰𑖎-𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖥𑖯𑖪𑖰-𑖢𑖨𑖰𑖢𑖯𑖩𑖡𑖯𑖥𑖿𑖧𑖲𑖢𑖐𑖦𑖡𑖯𑖡𑖰 𑖭𑖽𑖨𑖎𑖿𑖬𑖰𑖝𑖲𑖽 𑖁𑖡𑖿𑖝𑖯𑖨𑖯𑖬𑖿𑖘𑖿𑖨𑖰𑖎𑖯𑖜𑖯𑖽 𑖨𑖯𑖬𑖿𑖘𑖿𑖨𑖰𑖎𑖯𑖜𑖯𑖗𑖿𑖓 𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖐𑖝𑖰𑖫𑖱𑖩𑖺𑖢𑖯𑖧𑖯𑖡𑖯𑖽 𑖓 𑖦𑖯𑖠𑖿𑖧𑖦𑖸𑖡 𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖧𑖝𑖰𑖬𑖿𑖧𑖝𑖸𑗂</para>
   </preamble>
   <article number="1"><title>𑖀𑖡𑖲𑖓𑖿𑖔𑖸𑖟𑖾 1</title>
      <para>𑖭𑖨𑖿𑖪𑖸 𑖦𑖯𑖡𑖪𑖯𑖾 𑖭𑖿𑖪𑖝𑖡𑖿𑖝𑖿𑖨𑖯𑖾 𑖭𑖦𑖲𑖝𑖿𑖢𑖡𑖿𑖡𑖯𑖾 𑖪𑖨𑖿𑖝𑖡𑖿𑖝𑖸 𑖀𑖢𑖰 𑖓, 𑖐𑖻𑖨𑖪𑖟𑖴𑖫𑖯 𑖀𑖠𑖰𑖎𑖯𑖨𑖟𑖴𑖫𑖯 𑖓 𑖭𑖦𑖯𑖡𑖯𑖾 𑖊𑖪 𑖪𑖨𑖿𑖝𑖡𑖿𑖝𑖸𑗂 𑖊𑖝𑖸 𑖭𑖨𑖿𑖪𑖸 𑖓𑖸𑖝𑖡𑖯-𑖝𑖨𑖿𑖎-𑖫𑖎𑖿𑖝𑖰𑖥𑖿𑖧𑖯𑖽 𑖭𑖲𑖭𑖦𑖿𑖢𑖡𑖿𑖡𑖯𑖾 𑖭𑖡𑖿𑖝𑖰𑗂 𑖀𑖢𑖰 𑖓, 𑖭𑖨𑖿𑖪𑖸𑖢𑖰 𑖤𑖡𑖿𑖠𑖲𑖝𑖿𑖪-𑖥𑖯𑖪𑖡𑖧𑖯 𑖢𑖨𑖭𑖿𑖢𑖨𑖽 𑖪𑖿𑖧𑖪𑖮𑖨𑖡𑖿𑖝𑖲𑗂</para>
   </article>
   <article number="2"><title>𑖀𑖡𑖲𑖓𑖿𑖔𑖸𑖟𑖾 2</title>
      <para>𑖀𑖭𑖿𑖧𑖯𑖽 𑖀𑖥𑖰𑖑𑖺𑖬𑖜𑖯𑖧𑖯𑖽 𑖡𑖰𑖨𑖿𑖟𑖰𑖬𑖿𑖘𑖯𑖾 𑖭𑖨𑖿𑖪𑖸𑖢𑖰 𑖀𑖠𑖰𑖎𑖯𑖨𑖯𑖾 𑖭𑖨𑖿𑖪𑖯𑖜𑖿𑖧𑖢𑖰 𑖓 𑖭𑖿𑖪𑖯𑖝𑖡𑖿𑖝𑖿𑖨𑖿𑖧𑖯𑖜𑖰, 𑖪𑖰𑖡𑖹𑖪 𑖕𑖯𑖝𑖰-𑖪𑖨𑖿𑖜-𑖩𑖰𑖽𑖐-𑖥𑖯𑖬𑖯-𑖠𑖨𑖿𑖦-𑖨𑖯𑖕𑖡𑖱𑖝𑖰𑖎-𑖝𑖟𑖰𑖝𑖨-𑖦𑖡𑖿𑖝𑖪𑖿𑖧𑖯𑖟𑖰-𑖥𑖸𑖟𑖦𑖿, 𑖨𑖯𑖬𑖿𑖘𑖿𑖨𑖰𑖧𑖽 𑖭𑖯𑖦𑖯𑖕𑖰𑖎𑖯𑖠𑖯𑖨𑖽 𑖭𑖦𑖿𑖢𑖕𑖿𑖕𑖡𑖿𑖦-𑖝𑖟𑖰𑖝𑖨 𑖭𑖿𑖝𑖨𑖗𑖿𑖓 𑖀𑖪𑖰𑖐𑖜𑖧𑖿𑖧, 𑖀𑖠𑖰𑖐𑖡𑖿𑖝𑖲𑖽 𑖭𑖨𑖿𑖪𑖺𑖢𑖰 𑖕𑖡𑖾 𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖥𑖪𑖝𑖰𑗂</para>
      <para>𑖊𑖝𑖟𑖝𑖰𑖨𑖰𑖎𑖿𑖝𑖦𑖿, 𑖎𑖭𑖿𑖧𑖯𑖫𑖿𑖓𑖰𑖟𑖢𑖰 𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖥𑖲𑖭𑖝𑖿𑖝𑖯𑖧𑖯𑖾 𑖡𑖰𑖧𑖦𑖡𑖯𑖡𑖿𑖝𑖨𑖿𑖐𑖝𑖦𑖿, 𑖭𑖿𑖪𑖯𑖠𑖱𑖡𑖭𑖿𑖧 𑖁𑖝𑖿𑖦𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖫𑖯𑖭𑖡𑖸𑖝𑖨-𑖝𑖡𑖿𑖝𑖿𑖨𑖭𑖿𑖧, 𑖡𑖿𑖧𑖯𑖭𑖰𑖝𑖡𑖿𑖝𑖿𑖨𑖭𑖿𑖧 𑖪𑖯 𑖪𑖯𑖭𑖿𑖝𑖪𑖿𑖧𑖭𑖿𑖧 𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖟𑖸𑖫𑖭𑖿𑖧 𑖟𑖸𑖫𑖭𑖿𑖧 𑖪𑖯 𑖨𑖯𑖕𑖡𑖱𑖝𑖰𑖎-𑖭𑖱𑖦𑖯-𑖡𑖰𑖤𑖡𑖿𑖠𑖡𑖯𑖡𑖿𑖝𑖯𑖨𑖯𑖬𑖿𑖘𑖿𑖨𑖰𑖎-𑖭𑖿𑖝𑖨𑖯𑖠𑖯𑖨𑖸𑖜 𑖡 𑖎𑖺𑖢𑖰 𑖥𑖸𑖟𑖺 𑖪𑖰𑖠𑖯𑖭𑖿𑖧𑖝𑖸𑗂</para>
   </article>
   <article number="3"><title>𑖀𑖡𑖲𑖓𑖿𑖔𑖸𑖟𑖾 3</title>
      <para>𑖭𑖨𑖿𑖪𑖺𑖢𑖰 𑖕𑖡𑖾 𑖕𑖱𑖪𑖡-𑖭𑖿𑖪𑖯𑖝𑖡𑖿𑖝𑖿𑖨𑖿𑖧-𑖭𑖲𑖨𑖎𑖿𑖬𑖯𑖠𑖰𑖎𑖯𑖨𑖽 𑖭𑖽𑖠𑖝𑖿𑖝𑖸𑗂</para>
   </article>
   <article number="4"><title>𑖀𑖡𑖲𑖓𑖿𑖔𑖸𑖟𑖾 4</title>
      <para>𑖡 𑖎𑖦𑖢𑖰 𑖕𑖡𑖽 𑖟𑖯𑖭𑖝𑖿𑖪𑖸𑖡 𑖢𑖨𑖯𑖠𑖱𑖡𑖝𑖿𑖪𑖸𑖡 𑖪𑖯 𑖠𑖯𑖨𑖧𑖰𑖝𑖲𑖽 𑖀𑖡𑖲𑖕𑖿𑖗𑖯𑖭𑖿𑖧𑖝𑖸𑗂 𑖀𑖢𑖰 𑖓 𑖟𑖯𑖭𑖪𑖿𑖧𑖯𑖢𑖯𑖨𑖾 𑖢𑖳𑖨𑖿𑖜𑖨𑖳𑖢𑖸𑖜 𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖝𑖰𑖬𑖰𑖟𑖿𑖠𑖾 𑖭𑖿𑖞𑖯𑖭𑖿𑖧𑖝𑖰𑗂</para>
   </article>
   <article number="5"><title>𑖀𑖡𑖲𑖓𑖿𑖔𑖸𑖟𑖾 5</title>
      <para>𑖡 𑖎𑖦𑖢𑖰 𑖕𑖡𑖽 𑖪𑖰𑖨𑖲𑖠𑖿𑖧 𑖀𑖪𑖦𑖯𑖡𑖡𑖯𑖝𑖿𑖦𑖎𑖽 𑖪𑖿𑖧𑖪𑖮𑖯𑖨𑖽 𑖟𑖜𑖿𑖚𑖽 𑖪𑖯 𑖎𑖿𑖨𑖳𑖨𑖽 𑖀𑖦𑖯𑖡𑖪𑖱𑖧𑖽 𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖝𑖺𑖟𑖡𑖽 𑖪𑖯 𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖪𑖨𑖿𑖝𑖧𑖰𑖝𑖲𑖽 𑖀𑖡𑖲𑖕𑖿𑖗𑖯𑖭𑖿𑖧𑖝𑖸𑗂</para>
   </article>
   <article number="6"><title>𑖀𑖡𑖲𑖓𑖿𑖔𑖸𑖟𑖾 6</title>
      <para>𑖪𑖰𑖠𑖸𑖾 𑖭𑖦𑖎𑖿𑖬𑖽 𑖭𑖨𑖿𑖪𑖺𑖢𑖰 𑖕𑖡𑖾 𑖭𑖨𑖿𑖪𑖝𑖿𑖨 𑖀𑖥𑖰𑖕𑖿𑖗𑖯𑖝𑖲𑖽 𑖀𑖠𑖰𑖎𑖯𑖨𑖽 𑖭𑖽𑖠𑖝𑖿𑖝𑖸𑗂</para>
   </article>
   <article number="7"><title>𑖀𑖡𑖲𑖓𑖿𑖔𑖸𑖟𑖾 7</title>
      <para>𑖪𑖰𑖠𑖸𑖾 𑖭𑖦𑖎𑖿𑖬𑖽 𑖭𑖨𑖿𑖪𑖸𑖢𑖰 𑖝𑖲𑖩𑖿𑖧𑖯𑖾 𑖭𑖦𑖯𑖡𑖯𑖫𑖿𑖓 𑖪𑖨𑖿𑖝𑖡𑖿𑖝𑖸𑗂 𑖀𑖢𑖰 𑖓 𑖪𑖰𑖡𑖹𑖪 𑖎𑖦𑖢𑖰 𑖥𑖸𑖟𑖽 𑖪𑖰𑖠𑖸𑖾 𑖝𑖲𑖩𑖿𑖧𑖽 𑖭𑖽𑖨𑖎𑖿𑖬𑖜𑖦𑖪𑖯𑖢𑖿𑖝𑖲𑖽 𑖀𑖨𑖿𑖮𑖡𑖿𑖝𑖰𑗂 𑖀𑖭𑖿𑖧𑖯𑖾 𑖀𑖥𑖰𑖑𑖺𑖬𑖜𑖯𑖧𑖯𑖾 𑖄𑖩𑖿𑖩𑖽𑖑𑖡𑖸 𑖎𑖦𑖢𑖰 𑖥𑖸𑖟𑖽, 𑖊𑖝𑖯𑖟𑖴𑖐𑖿𑖥𑖸𑖟𑖽 𑖪𑖯 𑖀𑖥𑖰𑖩𑖎𑖿𑖬𑖿𑖧 𑖎𑖯𑖦𑖢𑖰 𑖓𑖸𑖬𑖿𑖘𑖯𑖽 𑖪𑖰𑖨𑖲𑖠𑖿𑖧 𑖭𑖦𑖯𑖡-𑖭𑖽𑖨𑖎𑖿𑖬𑖜𑖯𑖨𑖿𑖮𑖯𑖾 𑖭𑖨𑖿𑖪𑖸𑖢𑖰 𑖪𑖨𑖿𑖝𑖡𑖿𑖝𑖸𑗂</para>
   </article>
   <article number="8"><title>𑖀𑖡𑖲𑖓𑖿𑖔𑖸𑖟𑖾 8</title>
      <para>𑖪𑖰𑖠𑖰𑖡𑖯 𑖭𑖽𑖪𑖰𑖠𑖯𑖡𑖸𑖡 𑖪𑖯 𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖟𑖝𑖿𑖝𑖯𑖡𑖯𑖽 𑖦𑖻𑖩𑖰𑖎𑖯𑖠𑖰𑖎𑖯𑖨𑖯𑖜𑖯𑖦𑖲𑖩𑖿𑖩𑖽𑖑𑖡-𑖎𑖯𑖨𑖿𑖧𑖯𑖜𑖯𑖽 𑖎𑖴𑖝𑖸, 𑖧𑖺𑖐𑖿𑖧𑖹𑖾 𑖨𑖯𑖬𑖿𑖘𑖿𑖨𑖰𑖧-𑖡𑖿𑖧𑖯𑖧𑖢𑖱𑖙𑖹𑖾 𑖭𑖽𑖭𑖿𑖝𑖲𑖝𑖯𑖡𑖯𑖽 𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖥𑖯𑖪𑖰𑖡𑖯𑖽 𑖭𑖦𑖲𑖢𑖯𑖧𑖯𑖡𑖯𑖽 𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖧𑖺𑖐𑖯𑖨𑖿𑖮𑖺 𑖮𑖰 𑖭𑖨𑖿𑖪𑖺 𑖕𑖡𑖺𑖭𑖿𑖝𑖰𑗂</para>
   </article>
   <article number="9"><title>𑖀𑖡𑖲𑖓𑖿𑖔𑖸𑖟𑖾 9</title>
      <para>𑖡 𑖎𑖺𑖢𑖰 𑖕𑖡𑖾 𑖭𑖿𑖪𑖸𑖓𑖿𑖔𑖧𑖯 𑖡𑖰𑖐𑖿𑖨𑖮𑖱𑖝𑖲𑖽, 𑖠𑖨𑖿𑖝𑖲𑖽, 𑖡𑖰𑖬𑖿𑖎𑖯𑖭𑖧𑖰𑖝𑖲𑖽 𑖪𑖯 𑖀𑖡𑖲𑖕𑖿𑖗𑖯𑖭𑖿𑖧𑖝𑖸𑗂</para>
   </article>
   <article number="10"><title>𑖀𑖡𑖲𑖓𑖿𑖔𑖸𑖟𑖾 10</title>
      <para>𑖭𑖨𑖿𑖪𑖺𑖢𑖰 𑖕𑖡𑖾, 𑖭𑖿𑖪𑖽 𑖪𑖰𑖨𑖲𑖠𑖿𑖧 𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖪𑖨𑖿𑖝𑖿𑖝𑖰𑖝𑖭𑖿𑖧 𑖎𑖭𑖿𑖧𑖯𑖢𑖰 𑖁𑖢𑖨𑖯𑖠𑖰𑖎𑖯𑖎𑖿𑖬𑖸𑖢𑖭𑖿𑖧, 𑖭𑖿𑖪𑖱𑖧𑖯𑖠𑖰𑖎𑖯𑖨𑖯𑖜𑖯𑖽 𑖟𑖯𑖧𑖰𑖝𑖿𑖪𑖯𑖡𑖯𑖽 𑖓, 𑖪𑖰𑖡𑖰𑖨𑖿𑖠𑖯𑖨𑖜𑖭𑖿𑖧 𑖓 𑖎𑖴𑖝𑖸, 𑖭𑖿𑖪𑖯𑖠𑖱𑖡𑖸𑖡 𑖡𑖰𑖬𑖿𑖢𑖎𑖿𑖬𑖸𑖜 𑖓 𑖡𑖿𑖧𑖯𑖧𑖢𑖱𑖙𑖸𑖡 𑖪𑖰𑖠𑖱𑖧𑖦𑖯𑖡𑖭𑖿𑖧 𑖭𑖦𑖲𑖓𑖰𑖝𑖭𑖿𑖧 𑖭𑖯𑖨𑖿𑖪𑖕𑖡𑖰𑖎𑖭𑖿𑖧 𑖫𑖿𑖨𑖪𑖜𑖭𑖿𑖧 𑖓 𑖎𑖴𑖝𑖸 𑖭𑖨𑖿𑖪𑖺𑖢𑖰 𑖕𑖡𑖾 𑖢𑖳𑖨𑖿𑖜𑖯𑖽 𑖭𑖦𑖯𑖡𑖝𑖯𑖽 𑖠𑖯𑖨𑖧𑖝𑖰𑗂</para>
   </article>
   <article number="11"><title>𑖀𑖡𑖲𑖓𑖿𑖔𑖸𑖟𑖾 11</title>
      <orderedlist><listitem tag="(१)"><para>𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖝𑖿𑖧𑖸𑖎𑖦𑖢𑖰 𑖕𑖡𑖾, 𑖪𑖰𑖠𑖸𑖨𑖡𑖲𑖭𑖯𑖨𑖸𑖜 𑖧𑖯𑖪𑖟𑖪𑖠𑖰 𑖭𑖯𑖨𑖿𑖪𑖕𑖡𑖰𑖎𑖯𑖥𑖰𑖧𑖺𑖐-𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖎𑖨𑖜𑖸 𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖦𑖲𑖏𑖯𑖢𑖨𑖯𑖠-𑖭𑖰𑖟𑖿𑖠𑖰𑖽 𑖡𑖹𑖪 𑖥𑖕𑖝𑖸, 𑖝𑖯𑖪𑖝𑖿𑖢𑖨𑖿𑖧𑖡𑖿𑖝𑖽 𑖡𑖰𑖨𑖿𑖟𑖲𑖬𑖿𑖘𑖾 𑖂𑖝𑖿𑖧𑖯𑖦𑖽𑖭𑖿𑖧𑖝𑖸𑗂 𑖀𑖢𑖰 𑖓, 𑖭𑖿𑖪𑖱𑖧-𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖝𑖰𑖨𑖎𑖿𑖬𑖯𑖨𑖿𑖞𑖽 𑖝𑖸𑖡 𑖕𑖡𑖸𑖡 𑖭𑖨𑖿𑖪𑖦𑖢𑖰 𑖁𑖪𑖫𑖿𑖧𑖎-𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖝𑖰𑖥𑖳𑖝𑖰𑖕𑖯𑖝𑖽 𑖄𑖢𑖢𑖯𑖟𑖡𑖱𑖧𑖽 𑖪𑖨𑖿𑖝𑖝𑖸𑗂</para>
         </listitem>
         <listitem tag="(२)"><para>𑖁𑖡𑖿𑖝𑖯𑖨𑖯𑖬𑖿𑖘𑖿𑖨𑖰𑖎𑖭𑖿𑖧 𑖨𑖯𑖬𑖿𑖘𑖿𑖨𑖰𑖎𑖭𑖿𑖧 𑖓 𑖪𑖰𑖠𑖸𑖨𑖡𑖿𑖝𑖨𑖿𑖐𑖝𑖦𑖿 𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖦𑖲𑖏𑖯𑖢𑖨𑖯𑖠-𑖡𑖰𑖬𑖿𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖥𑖯𑖪𑖎𑖭𑖿𑖧 𑖎𑖭𑖿𑖧𑖯𑖢𑖰 𑖎𑖯𑖨𑖿𑖧𑖭𑖿𑖧 𑖎𑖯𑖨𑖜𑖯𑖝𑖿 𑖡 𑖎𑖺𑖢𑖰 𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖦𑖲𑖏𑖯𑖢𑖨𑖯𑖠𑖯𑖨𑖿𑖞𑖽 𑖀𑖢𑖨𑖯𑖠𑖱𑖝𑖰 𑖐𑖜𑖧𑖰𑖬𑖿𑖧𑖝𑖸𑗂 𑖡 𑖪𑖯, 𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖦𑖲𑖏𑖯𑖢𑖨𑖯𑖠-𑖎𑖯𑖩𑖸 𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖪𑖨𑖿𑖝𑖡𑖱𑖧-𑖟𑖜𑖿𑖚-𑖟𑖯𑖡𑖯𑖝𑖿 𑖡𑖯𑖠𑖰𑖎𑖝𑖨𑖺 𑖟𑖜𑖿𑖚𑖾 𑖎𑖭𑖿𑖦𑖰𑖽𑖫𑖿𑖓𑖰𑖟𑖢𑖰 𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖪𑖨𑖿𑖝𑖡𑖱𑖧𑖺 𑖥𑖪𑖰𑖝𑖯𑗂</para>
         </listitem>
      </orderedlist>
   </article>
   <article number="12"><title>𑖀𑖡𑖲𑖓𑖿𑖔𑖸𑖟𑖾 12</title>
      <para>𑖡 𑖎𑖭𑖿𑖧𑖯𑖢𑖰 𑖪𑖿𑖧𑖎𑖿𑖝𑖰𑖐𑖝𑖸 𑖢𑖯𑖨𑖰𑖪𑖯𑖨𑖰𑖎𑖸 𑖓 𑖕𑖱𑖪𑖡𑖸, 𑖐𑖴𑖮𑖸, 𑖢𑖝𑖿𑖨𑖪𑖿𑖧𑖪𑖮𑖯𑖨𑖸 𑖓 𑖭𑖿𑖪𑖸𑖓𑖿𑖔𑖧𑖯 𑖮𑖭𑖿𑖝𑖎𑖿𑖬𑖸𑖢𑖺𑖡𑖲𑖕𑖿𑖗𑖯𑖭𑖿𑖧𑖝𑖸, 𑖡 𑖪𑖯 𑖎𑖭𑖿𑖧𑖯𑖢𑖰 𑖏𑖿𑖧𑖯𑖝𑖰𑖽 𑖭𑖦𑖿𑖦𑖯𑖡𑖽 𑖪𑖯𑖎𑖿𑖨𑖯𑖡𑖿𑖝𑖲𑖽 𑖎𑖺𑖢𑖰 𑖫𑖎𑖿𑖬𑖿𑖧𑖝𑖰𑗂 𑖊𑖝𑖯𑖮𑖎𑖿-𑖮𑖭𑖿𑖝𑖎𑖿𑖬𑖸𑖢𑖯𑖎𑖿𑖨𑖦𑖜𑖯𑖡𑖰 𑖪𑖰𑖨𑖲𑖠𑖿𑖧 𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖝𑖿𑖧𑖸𑖎𑖦𑖢𑖰-𑖕𑖡𑖾 𑖪𑖰𑖠𑖰-𑖭𑖽𑖨𑖎𑖿𑖬𑖜𑖽 𑖭𑖽𑖠𑖝𑖿𑖝𑖸𑗂</para>
   </article>
   <article number="13"><title>𑖀𑖡𑖲𑖓𑖿𑖔𑖸𑖟𑖾 13</title>
      <orderedlist><listitem tag="(१)"><para>𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖝𑖿𑖧𑖸𑖎𑖦𑖢𑖰 𑖨𑖯𑖬𑖿𑖘𑖿𑖨𑖭𑖿𑖧 𑖭𑖱𑖦𑖿𑖡𑖰 𑖁𑖪𑖯𑖭𑖭𑖿𑖧 𑖐𑖦𑖡𑖯𑖐𑖦𑖡𑖭𑖿𑖧 𑖓𑖭𑖿𑖪𑖯𑖝𑖡𑖿𑖝𑖿𑖨𑖿𑖧𑖯𑖠𑖰𑖎𑖯𑖨𑖽 𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖝𑖿𑖧𑖸𑖎𑖦𑖢𑖰 𑖕𑖡𑖾 𑖭𑖽𑖠𑖯𑖨𑖧𑖝𑖰𑗂</para>
         </listitem>
         <listitem tag="(२)"><para>𑖭𑖿𑖪𑖟𑖸𑖫𑖺𑖢𑖸𑖝𑖽 𑖎𑖦𑖢𑖰 𑖟𑖸𑖫𑖽 𑖝𑖿𑖧𑖎𑖿𑖝𑖲𑖽 𑖭𑖿𑖪𑖟𑖸𑖫𑖽 𑖓 𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖝𑖿𑖧𑖯𑖐𑖡𑖿𑖝𑖲𑖽 𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖝𑖿𑖧𑖸𑖎𑖦𑖢𑖰 𑖀𑖠𑖰𑖎𑖴𑖝𑖺𑖭𑖿𑖝𑖰𑗂</para>
         </listitem>
      </orderedlist>
   </article>
   <article number="14"><title>𑖀𑖡𑖲𑖓𑖿𑖔𑖸𑖟𑖾 14</title>
      <orderedlist><listitem tag="(१)"><para>𑖄𑖢𑖟𑖿𑖨𑖪𑖸𑖥𑖿𑖧𑖺 𑖨𑖎𑖿𑖬𑖰𑖝𑖲𑖽 𑖀𑖡𑖿𑖧𑖟𑖸𑖫𑖸𑖬𑖲 𑖫𑖨𑖜𑖦𑖠𑖰𑖐𑖡𑖿𑖝𑖲𑖽 𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖝𑖿𑖧𑖸𑖎𑖦𑖢𑖰 𑖀𑖠𑖰𑖎𑖯𑖨𑖽 𑖭𑖽𑖠𑖝𑖿𑖝𑖸𑗂</para>
         </listitem>
         <listitem tag="(२)"><para>𑖭𑖽𑖧𑖲𑖎𑖿𑖝𑖨𑖯𑖬𑖿𑖘𑖿𑖨𑖭𑖽𑖑𑖭𑖿𑖧 𑖭𑖰𑖟𑖿𑖠𑖯𑖡𑖿𑖝𑖯𑖡𑖯𑖽 𑖄𑖟𑖿𑖟𑖸𑖫𑖿𑖧𑖯𑖡𑖯𑖽 𑖓 𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖝𑖰𑖎𑖳𑖩𑖎𑖯𑖨𑖿𑖧𑖸𑖥𑖿𑖧𑖾 𑖨𑖯𑖕𑖡𑖱𑖝𑖰𑖎𑖸𑖝𑖨𑖯𑖢𑖨𑖯𑖠𑖸𑖥𑖿𑖧𑖫𑖿𑖓 𑖭𑖦𑖲𑖝𑖿𑖝𑖿𑖞𑖰𑖝𑖸𑖬𑖲 𑖪𑖯𑖭𑖿𑖝𑖪𑖰𑖎𑖯𑖥𑖰𑖧𑖺𑖐-𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖎𑖨𑖜𑖸𑖬𑖲 𑖀𑖠𑖰𑖎𑖯𑖨𑖺𑖧𑖽 𑖡𑖹𑖪 𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖥𑖪𑖰𑖝𑖯𑗂</para>
         </listitem>
      </orderedlist>
   </article>
   <article number="15"><title>𑖀𑖡𑖲𑖓𑖿𑖔𑖸𑖟𑖾 15</title>
      <orderedlist><listitem tag="(१)"><para>𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖝𑖿𑖧𑖸𑖎𑖦𑖢𑖰 𑖨𑖯𑖬𑖿𑖘𑖿𑖨𑖰𑖧𑖝𑖯𑖧𑖯𑖾 𑖀𑖠𑖰𑖎𑖯𑖨𑖽 𑖠𑖯𑖨𑖧𑖝𑖰𑗂</para>
         </listitem>
         <listitem tag="(२)"><para>𑖡 𑖎𑖺𑖢𑖰 𑖭𑖿𑖪𑖸𑖓𑖿𑖔𑖧𑖯 𑖭𑖿𑖪𑖱𑖧𑖨𑖯𑖬𑖿𑖘𑖿𑖨𑖰𑖧𑖝𑖯𑖝𑖺 𑖪𑖗𑖿𑖓𑖰𑖝𑖾 𑖭𑖿𑖧𑖯𑖝𑖿, 𑖡 𑖪𑖯 𑖭𑖿𑖪𑖱𑖧-𑖨𑖯𑖬𑖿𑖘𑖿𑖨𑖰𑖧𑖝𑖯-𑖢𑖨𑖰𑖪𑖨𑖿𑖝𑖡𑖯𑖠𑖰𑖎𑖯𑖨𑖯𑖝𑖿 𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖝𑖿𑖧𑖯𑖏𑖿𑖧𑖯𑖝𑖺 𑖥𑖪𑖸𑖝𑖿𑗂</para>
         </listitem>
      </orderedlist>
   </article>
   <article number="16"><title>𑖀𑖡𑖲𑖓𑖿𑖔𑖸𑖟𑖾 16</title>
      <orderedlist><listitem tag="(१)"><para>𑖕𑖯𑖝𑖰-𑖠𑖨𑖿𑖦-𑖨𑖯𑖬𑖿𑖘𑖿𑖨𑖰𑖧𑖝𑖯-𑖡𑖰𑖧𑖦𑖡𑖽 𑖪𑖰𑖡𑖹𑖪 𑖢𑖳𑖨𑖿𑖜-𑖪𑖧𑖭𑖿𑖎𑖯𑖾 𑖭𑖿𑖝𑖿𑖨𑖱-𑖢𑖲𑖨𑖲𑖬𑖯𑖾, 𑖢𑖨𑖰𑖪𑖯𑖨𑖽 𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖝𑖰𑖬𑖿𑖙𑖯𑖢𑖧𑖰𑖝𑖲𑖽 𑖪𑖰𑖪𑖯𑖮𑖯𑖠𑖰𑖎𑖯𑖨𑖪𑖡𑖿𑖝𑖺 𑖪𑖨𑖿𑖝𑖿𑖝𑖡𑖿𑖝𑖸𑗂</para>
         </listitem>
         <listitem tag="(२)"><para>𑖪𑖰𑖪𑖯𑖮𑖯𑖨𑖿𑖞𑖽, 𑖪𑖰𑖪𑖯𑖮𑖯𑖪𑖭𑖨𑖸, 𑖪𑖰𑖪𑖯𑖮-𑖪𑖰𑖓𑖿𑖔𑖸𑖟𑖸 𑖪𑖯 𑖝𑖸 𑖭𑖦𑖯𑖡𑖯𑖠𑖰𑖎𑖯𑖨𑖯𑖡𑖿 𑖭𑖽𑖠𑖯𑖨𑖧𑖡𑖿𑖝𑖰𑗂</para>
         </listitem>
         <listitem tag="(३)"><para>𑖪𑖰𑖪𑖯𑖮𑖸𑖓𑖿𑖔𑖲𑖎𑖯𑖡𑖯𑖽 𑖢𑖳𑖨𑖿𑖜-𑖭𑖿𑖪𑖝𑖡𑖿𑖝𑖿𑖨-𑖭𑖮𑖦𑖝𑖿𑖧𑖹𑖪 𑖪𑖰𑖪𑖯𑖮-𑖭𑖽𑖭𑖿𑖎𑖯𑖨𑖾 𑖀𑖡𑖲𑖬𑖿𑖙𑖸𑖧𑖺𑖭𑖿𑖝𑖰𑗂𑖢𑖨𑖰𑖪𑖯𑖨𑖭𑖿𑖝𑖲, 𑖭𑖦𑖯𑖕𑖭𑖿𑖧 𑖭𑖿𑖪𑖯𑖥𑖯𑖪𑖰𑖎𑖺 𑖦𑖻𑖩𑖰𑖎𑖫𑖿𑖓 𑖪𑖨𑖿𑖐𑖱𑖧𑖹𑖎𑖯𑖽𑖫𑖺 𑖪𑖨𑖿𑖝𑖝𑖸, 𑖀𑖢𑖰 𑖓𑖯𑖧𑖽 𑖭𑖦𑖯𑖕𑖸𑖡 𑖨𑖯𑖬𑖿𑖘𑖿𑖨𑖸𑖜 𑖪𑖯 𑖭𑖽𑖨𑖎𑖿𑖬𑖜𑖱𑖧𑖺𑖭𑖿𑖝𑖰𑗂</para>
         </listitem>
      </orderedlist>
   </article>
   <article number="17"><title>𑖀𑖡𑖲𑖓𑖿𑖔𑖸𑖟𑖾 17</title>
      <orderedlist><listitem tag="(१)"><para>𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖝𑖿𑖧𑖸𑖎𑖦𑖢𑖰 𑖀𑖡𑖿𑖧𑖸𑖬𑖯𑖽 𑖭𑖮𑖧𑖺𑖐-𑖢𑖲𑖨𑖭𑖿𑖭𑖨𑖽 𑖊𑖎𑖯𑖎𑖰 𑖊𑖪 𑖪𑖯 𑖭𑖦𑖿𑖢𑖝𑖿𑖭𑖽𑖠𑖯𑖨𑖜-𑖭𑖿𑖪𑖯𑖦𑖰𑖝𑖿𑖪𑖯𑖠𑖰𑖎𑖯𑖨𑖽 𑖭𑖽𑖠𑖝𑖿𑖝𑖸𑗂</para>
         </listitem>
         <listitem tag="(२)"><para>𑖡 𑖎𑖺𑖢𑖰 𑖭𑖿𑖪𑖸𑖓𑖿𑖔𑖧𑖯 𑖭𑖿𑖪𑖱𑖧𑖭𑖽𑖢𑖝𑖿𑖭𑖿𑖪𑖯𑖦𑖰𑖝𑖿𑖪𑖯𑖠𑖰𑖎𑖯𑖨𑖯𑖝𑖿 𑖪𑖗𑖿𑖓𑖰𑖝𑖺 𑖥𑖪𑖸𑖝𑖿𑗂</para>
         </listitem>
      </orderedlist>
   </article>
   <article number="18"><title>𑖀𑖡𑖲𑖓𑖿𑖔𑖸𑖟𑖾 18</title>
      <para>𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖝𑖿𑖧𑖸𑖎𑖦𑖢𑖰 𑖪𑖰𑖓𑖯𑖨𑖯𑖜𑖯𑖽 𑖓𑖸𑖝𑖡𑖯𑖧𑖯𑖾 𑖠𑖨𑖿𑖦𑖭𑖿𑖧 𑖓𑖭𑖿𑖪𑖯𑖝𑖡𑖿𑖝𑖿𑖨𑖿𑖧𑖯𑖠𑖰𑖎𑖯𑖨𑖽 𑖭𑖽𑖠𑖝𑖿𑖝𑖸𑗂 𑖀𑖭𑖿𑖦𑖰𑖡𑖿 𑖀𑖠𑖰𑖎𑖯𑖨𑖸, 𑖭𑖿𑖪𑖱𑖧𑖽 𑖠𑖨𑖿𑖦𑖽 𑖪𑖰𑖫𑖿𑖪𑖯𑖭𑖽 𑖪𑖯 𑖫𑖰𑖎𑖿𑖬𑖧𑖰𑖝𑖲𑖽 𑖀𑖥𑖿𑖧𑖭𑖿𑖝𑖲𑖽 𑖀𑖨𑖿𑖓𑖰𑖝𑖲𑖽 𑖢𑖨𑖰𑖢𑖯𑖩𑖧𑖰𑖝𑖲𑖽 𑖪𑖯, 𑖪𑖹𑖧𑖎𑖿𑖝𑖰𑖎𑖸 𑖭𑖯𑖦𑖯𑖕𑖰𑖎𑖸 𑖓 𑖕𑖱𑖪𑖡𑖸, 𑖀𑖡𑖿𑖧𑖹𑖫𑖿𑖓 𑖭𑖮 𑖭𑖯𑖦𑖲𑖟𑖯𑖧𑖰𑖎𑖕𑖱𑖪𑖡𑖸 𑖊𑖎𑖯𑖎𑖰𑖡𑖯 𑖪𑖯 𑖭𑖿𑖪𑖱𑖧𑖽 𑖠𑖨𑖿𑖦𑖽 𑖪𑖰𑖫𑖿𑖪𑖯𑖭𑖽𑖭𑖿𑖪𑖯𑖝𑖡𑖿𑖝𑖿𑖨𑖿𑖧𑖽 𑖓 𑖢𑖨𑖰𑖪𑖨𑖿𑖝𑖧𑖰𑖝𑖲𑖦𑖢𑖰 𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖝𑖿𑖧𑖸𑖎𑖽 𑖕𑖡𑖾 𑖭𑖿𑖪𑖯𑖝𑖡𑖿𑖝𑖿𑖨𑖿𑖧𑖽 𑖠𑖯𑖨𑖧𑖝𑖰𑗂</para>
   </article>
   <article number="19"><title>𑖀𑖡𑖲𑖓𑖿𑖔𑖸𑖟𑖾 19</title>
      <para>𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖝𑖿𑖧𑖸𑖎𑖦𑖢𑖰 𑖦𑖡𑖿𑖝𑖪𑖿𑖧𑖯𑖥𑖰𑖪𑖿𑖧𑖎𑖿𑖝𑖿𑖧𑖺𑖾 𑖀𑖠𑖰𑖎𑖯𑖨𑖽 𑖭𑖽𑖠𑖝𑖿𑖝𑖸𑗂 𑖭𑖱𑖦𑖯𑖪𑖿𑖧𑖪𑖠𑖯𑖡𑖽 𑖀𑖪𑖰𑖐𑖜𑖧𑖿𑖧, 𑖎𑖸𑖡𑖯𑖢𑖰 𑖭𑖽𑖓𑖯𑖨-𑖦𑖯𑖠𑖿𑖧𑖦𑖸𑖡 𑖪𑖰𑖓𑖯𑖨𑖯𑖜𑖯𑖽 𑖭𑖳𑖓𑖡𑖯𑖡𑖯𑖽 𑖓 𑖁𑖟𑖯𑖡-𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖟𑖯𑖡𑖯𑖨𑖿𑖞𑖽 𑖪𑖰𑖡𑖹𑖪 𑖮𑖭𑖿𑖝𑖎𑖿𑖬𑖸𑖢𑖽 𑖎𑖰𑖫𑖿𑖓𑖟𑖢𑖰 𑖕𑖡𑖾, 𑖭𑖿𑖪𑖱𑖧-𑖦𑖡𑖿𑖝𑖪𑖿𑖧-𑖭𑖽𑖑𑖯𑖨𑖜𑖯𑖨𑖿𑖞𑖽 𑖀𑖠𑖰𑖎𑖯𑖨𑖸𑖭𑖿𑖦𑖰𑖡𑖿 𑖀𑖨𑖿𑖮𑖰𑖬𑖿𑖧𑖝𑖸𑗂</para>
   </article>
   <article number="20"><title>𑖀𑖡𑖲𑖓𑖿𑖔𑖸𑖟𑖾 20</title>
      <orderedlist><listitem tag="(१)"><para>𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖝𑖿𑖧𑖸𑖎𑖦𑖸𑖪 𑖕𑖡𑖾 𑖫𑖯𑖡𑖿𑖝𑖰𑖢𑖳𑖨𑖿𑖜𑖨𑖱𑖝𑖿𑖧𑖯 𑖭𑖦𑖿𑖦𑖰𑖩𑖰𑖝𑖲𑖽 𑖭𑖽𑖑𑖘𑖡𑖯𑖡𑖰 𑖓 𑖪𑖰𑖨𑖓𑖧𑖰𑖝𑖲𑖦𑖨𑖿𑖮𑖺 𑖪𑖨𑖿𑖝𑖝𑖸𑗂</para>
         </listitem>
         <listitem tag="(२)"><para>𑖎𑖸𑖡𑖓𑖰𑖟𑖢𑖰 𑖭𑖽𑖑𑖘𑖡𑖸𑖡 𑖭𑖮 𑖁𑖝𑖿𑖦𑖯𑖡𑖽 𑖭𑖽𑖧𑖺𑖕𑖧𑖰𑖝𑖲𑖽 𑖡 𑖎𑖺𑖢𑖰 𑖪𑖰𑖪𑖫𑖱𑖎𑖨𑖿𑖝𑖲𑖽 𑖫𑖎𑖿𑖧𑖝𑖸𑗂</para>
         </listitem>
      </orderedlist>
   </article>
   <article number="21"><title>𑖀𑖡𑖲𑖓𑖿𑖔𑖸𑖟𑖾 21</title>
      <orderedlist><listitem tag="(१)"><para>𑖭𑖿𑖪𑖱𑖧𑖨𑖯𑖬𑖿𑖘𑖿𑖨𑖭𑖿𑖧 𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖫𑖯𑖭𑖡𑖸 𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖝𑖿𑖧𑖎𑖿𑖬𑖨𑖱𑖝𑖿𑖧𑖯 𑖀𑖞𑖪𑖯 𑖡𑖰𑖬𑖿𑖢𑖎𑖿𑖬𑖡𑖰𑖨𑖿𑖪𑖯𑖓𑖰𑖝-𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖝𑖰𑖡𑖰𑖠𑖰-𑖦𑖯𑖠𑖿𑖧𑖦𑖸𑖡 𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖝𑖿𑖧𑖸𑖎𑖽 𑖕𑖡𑖾 𑖭𑖮𑖥𑖯𑖐𑖰𑖥𑖪𑖰𑖝𑖲𑖦𑖨𑖿𑖮𑖝𑖰𑗂</para>
         </listitem>
         <listitem tag="(२)"><para>𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖝𑖿𑖧𑖸𑖎𑖽 𑖕𑖡𑖭𑖿𑖝𑖟𑖱𑖧𑖸 𑖨𑖯𑖬𑖿𑖘𑖿𑖨𑖸 𑖩𑖺𑖎𑖭𑖸𑖪𑖯𑖧𑖯𑖾 𑖝𑖲𑖩𑖿𑖧𑖦𑖠𑖰𑖎𑖯𑖨𑖽 𑖭𑖽𑖠𑖝𑖿𑖝𑖸𑗂</para>
         </listitem>
         <listitem tag="(३)"><para>𑖩𑖺𑖎𑖸𑖓𑖿𑖔𑖧𑖯 𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖫𑖯𑖭𑖡𑖯𑖠𑖰𑖎𑖯𑖨𑖺 𑖪𑖰𑖨𑖓𑖧𑖰𑖬𑖿𑖧𑖝𑖸; 𑖂𑖧𑖦𑖰𑖓𑖿𑖔𑖯 𑖎𑖯𑖩𑖤𑖟𑖿𑖠𑖹𑖾 𑖡𑖰𑖧𑖦𑖺𑖓𑖰𑖝𑖹𑖫𑖿𑖓 𑖡𑖰𑖨𑖿𑖪𑖯𑖓𑖡𑖹𑖾 𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖎𑖯𑖫𑖿𑖧𑖦𑖿 𑖁𑖐𑖡𑖿𑖝𑖿𑖨𑖱; 𑖂𑖦𑖯𑖡𑖰 𑖡𑖰𑖨𑖿𑖪𑖯𑖓𑖡𑖯𑖡𑖰 𑖓 𑖪𑖹𑖫𑖿𑖪𑖰𑖎𑖽 𑖝𑖲𑖩𑖿𑖧𑖽 𑖐𑖲𑖢𑖿𑖝𑖽 𑖦𑖝𑖟𑖯𑖡𑖸𑖡 𑖀𑖞𑖪𑖯 𑖝𑖲𑖩𑖿𑖧𑖦𑖸𑖪𑖸𑖝𑖨𑖸𑖜 𑖦𑖝𑖟𑖯𑖡𑖪𑖰𑖠𑖰𑖡𑖯 𑖥𑖪𑖰𑖝𑖯𑖨𑖾𑗂</para>
         </listitem>
      </orderedlist>
   </article>
   <article number="22"><title>𑖀𑖡𑖲𑖓𑖿𑖔𑖸𑖟𑖾 22</title>
      <para>𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖝𑖿𑖧𑖸𑖎𑖦𑖸𑖪 𑖕𑖡𑖾, 𑖭𑖯𑖦𑖯𑖕𑖰𑖎𑖝𑖿𑖪𑖯𑖝𑖿, 𑖭𑖯𑖦𑖯𑖕𑖰𑖎-𑖭𑖲𑖨𑖎𑖿𑖬𑖯𑖧𑖯 𑖀𑖠𑖰𑖎𑖯𑖨𑖽 𑖭𑖡𑖿𑖠𑖯𑖨𑖧𑖝𑖰; 𑖀𑖭𑖻 𑖮𑖰 𑖨𑖯𑖬𑖿𑖘𑖿𑖨𑖰𑖧𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖧𑖯𑖭𑖸𑖡 𑖁𑖡𑖿𑖝𑖯𑖨𑖯𑖬𑖿𑖘𑖿𑖨𑖰𑖧𑖭𑖮𑖧𑖺𑖐𑖸 𑖡 𑖓 𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖝𑖿𑖧𑖸𑖎𑖽 𑖨𑖯𑖕𑖿𑖧𑖭𑖿𑖧 𑖭𑖽𑖑𑖘𑖡-𑖭𑖽𑖭𑖯𑖠𑖡𑖯𑖡𑖲𑖨𑖳𑖢𑖦𑖿, 𑖭𑖿𑖪𑖱𑖧𑖯𑖪𑖰𑖥𑖯𑖕𑖿𑖧𑖯𑖨𑖿𑖞𑖰𑖎-𑖭𑖯𑖦𑖯𑖕𑖰𑖎-𑖭𑖯𑖽𑖭𑖿𑖎𑖴𑖝𑖰𑖎𑖯𑖠𑖰𑖎𑖯𑖨𑖯𑖜𑖯𑖽 𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖝𑖰𑖬𑖿𑖙𑖯𑖧𑖹, 𑖭𑖿𑖪𑖱𑖧𑖪𑖿𑖧𑖎𑖿𑖝𑖰𑖝𑖿𑖪𑖭𑖿𑖧 𑖄𑖡𑖿𑖦𑖲𑖎𑖿𑖝 {𑖭𑖨𑖿𑖪𑖯𑖽𑖐𑖱𑖜} 𑖪𑖰𑖎𑖯𑖭𑖯𑖨𑖿𑖞𑖽 𑖓 𑖭𑖽𑖭𑖰𑖟𑖿𑖠𑖰𑖽 𑖀𑖨𑖿𑖮𑖝𑖰𑗂</para>
   </article>
   <article number="23"><title>𑖀𑖡𑖲𑖓𑖿𑖔𑖸𑖟𑖾 23</title>
      <orderedlist><listitem tag="(१)"><para>𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖝𑖿𑖧𑖸𑖎𑖦𑖢𑖰 𑖡𑖰𑖨𑖿𑖪𑖴𑖝𑖿𑖝𑖰𑖝𑖯𑖽 𑖪𑖰𑖨𑖲𑖠𑖿𑖧 𑖭𑖽𑖨𑖎𑖿𑖬𑖜𑖦𑖠𑖰𑖐𑖡𑖿𑖝𑖲𑖽, 𑖀𑖡𑖲𑖎𑖳𑖩-𑖎𑖯𑖨𑖿𑖧-𑖭𑖿𑖞𑖰𑖝𑖱𑖡𑖯𑖽 𑖡𑖿𑖧𑖯𑖧𑖱𑖎𑖨𑖜𑖦𑖪𑖯𑖢𑖿𑖝𑖲𑖽 𑖭𑖿𑖪𑖝𑖡𑖿𑖝𑖿𑖨-𑖪𑖴𑖝𑖿𑖝𑖰𑖝𑖯-𑖓𑖧𑖡𑖽 𑖪𑖰𑖠𑖯𑖝𑖲𑖽 𑖎𑖯𑖨𑖿𑖧𑖯𑖜𑖰 𑖓𑖯𑖡𑖲𑖬𑖿𑖙𑖯𑖝𑖲𑖽 𑖀𑖠𑖰𑖎𑖯𑖨𑖽 𑖠𑖝𑖿𑖝𑖸𑗂𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖝𑖿𑖧𑖸𑖎𑖦𑖿, 𑖪𑖰𑖡𑖹𑖪 𑖥𑖸𑖟𑖦𑖿, 𑖭𑖦-𑖎𑖯𑖨𑖿𑖧𑖯𑖨𑖿𑖞𑖦𑖿, 𑖭𑖦𑖯𑖡-𑖪𑖸𑖝𑖡𑖦𑖯𑖡𑖽 {𑖢𑖯𑖨𑖰𑖫𑖿𑖨𑖦𑖰𑖎𑖽} 𑖀𑖠𑖰𑖐𑖡𑖿𑖝𑖲𑖽 𑖀𑖠𑖰𑖎𑖴𑖝𑖺𑖭𑖿𑖝𑖰𑗂</para>
         </listitem>
         <listitem tag="(२)"><para>𑖎𑖯𑖨𑖿𑖧𑖡𑖰𑖨𑖝𑖾 𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖝𑖿𑖧𑖸𑖎𑖦𑖢𑖰 𑖕𑖡𑖾, 𑖭𑖿𑖪𑖭𑖿𑖧 𑖭𑖿𑖪𑖱𑖧-𑖢𑖨𑖰𑖪𑖯𑖨𑖭𑖿𑖧 𑖓 𑖦𑖯𑖡𑖪𑖱𑖧-𑖐𑖻𑖨𑖪-𑖧𑖲𑖝𑖭𑖿𑖧 𑖀𑖭𑖿𑖝𑖰𑖝𑖿𑖪𑖭𑖿𑖧 𑖭𑖽𑖨𑖎𑖿𑖬𑖜𑖯𑖨𑖿𑖞𑖽 𑖭𑖦𑖲𑖓𑖰𑖝𑖯𑖡𑖲𑖎𑖳𑖩-𑖢𑖯𑖨𑖰𑖫𑖿𑖨𑖦𑖰𑖎𑖯𑖟𑖯𑖡𑖭𑖿𑖧 𑖀𑖠𑖰𑖎𑖯𑖨𑖽 𑖠𑖯𑖨𑖧𑖝𑖰𑗂</para>
         </listitem>
         <listitem tag="(३)"><para>𑖁𑖪𑖫𑖿𑖧𑖎𑖸 𑖭𑖝𑖰 𑖓𑖯𑖭𑖻 𑖭𑖯𑖦𑖯𑖕𑖰𑖎-𑖭𑖽𑖨𑖎𑖿𑖬𑖜𑖭𑖿𑖧 𑖀𑖡𑖿𑖧𑖺𑖢𑖯𑖧𑖹𑖾 𑖊𑖝𑖝𑖿𑖢𑖳𑖨𑖧𑖰𑖝𑖲𑖽 𑖀𑖨𑖿𑖮𑖰𑖬𑖿𑖧𑖝𑖸𑗂</para>
         </listitem>
         <listitem tag="(४)"><para>𑖭𑖿𑖪𑖱𑖧𑖮𑖰𑖝𑖯𑖡𑖯𑖽 𑖭𑖽𑖨𑖎𑖿𑖬𑖜𑖯𑖨𑖿𑖞𑖽 𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖝𑖿𑖧𑖸𑖎𑖦𑖿 𑖫𑖿𑖨𑖦𑖰𑖎𑖭𑖽𑖑𑖘𑖡𑖹𑖾 𑖭𑖯𑖎𑖽 𑖁𑖝𑖿𑖦𑖯𑖡𑖽 𑖭𑖽𑖧𑖺𑖕𑖧𑖰𑖝𑖲𑖽 𑖊𑖝𑖯𑖟𑖴𑖎𑖿-𑖭𑖽𑖑𑖘𑖡𑖽 𑖪𑖯 𑖭𑖽𑖨𑖓𑖧𑖰𑖝𑖲𑖽 𑖀𑖠𑖰𑖎𑖴𑖝𑖺𑖭𑖿𑖝𑖰𑗂</para>
         </listitem>
      </orderedlist>
   </article>
   <article number="24"><title>𑖀𑖡𑖲𑖓𑖿𑖔𑖸𑖟𑖾 24</title>
      <para>𑖎𑖯𑖨𑖿𑖧𑖮𑖺𑖨𑖯𑖜𑖯𑖽 𑖭𑖦𑖲𑖓𑖰𑖝-𑖡𑖰𑖧𑖦𑖡-𑖢𑖲𑖨𑖭𑖿𑖭𑖨𑖦𑖿, 𑖭𑖪𑖸𑖝𑖡𑖽 𑖓 𑖡𑖰𑖧𑖝𑖯𑖪𑖠𑖰𑖎𑖯𑖪𑖎𑖯𑖫𑖸𑖡 𑖭𑖮 𑖪𑖰𑖫𑖿𑖨𑖦𑖯𑖠𑖰𑖎𑖯𑖨𑖾 𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖝𑖿𑖧𑖎𑖭𑖿𑖦𑖹 𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖟𑖸𑖧𑖺𑖭𑖿𑖝𑖰𑗂</para>
   </article>
   <article number="25"><title>𑖀𑖡𑖲𑖓𑖿𑖔𑖸𑖟𑖾 25</title>
      <orderedlist><listitem tag="(१)"><para>𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖝𑖿𑖧𑖸𑖎𑖽 𑖕𑖡𑖾 𑖏𑖯𑖟𑖿𑖧-𑖪𑖭𑖿𑖝𑖿𑖨𑖯𑖪𑖯𑖭-𑖓𑖰𑖎𑖰𑖝𑖿𑖭𑖺𑖢𑖓𑖨𑖿𑖧𑖯𑖟𑖰𑖥𑖰𑖾, 𑖁𑖪𑖫𑖿𑖧𑖎-𑖭𑖯𑖦𑖯𑖕𑖰𑖎-𑖭𑖸𑖪𑖯𑖥𑖰𑖫𑖿𑖓 𑖭𑖮 𑖭𑖿𑖪𑖭𑖿𑖧 𑖭𑖿𑖪𑖱𑖧𑖢𑖨𑖰𑖪𑖯𑖨𑖭𑖿𑖧 𑖓 𑖀𑖡𑖯𑖦𑖧𑖝𑖯𑖧𑖹 𑖭𑖿𑖪𑖭𑖿𑖞𑖝𑖯𑖧𑖹 𑖓 𑖢𑖨𑖿𑖧𑖯𑖢𑖿𑖝𑖽 𑖕𑖱𑖪𑖡𑖭𑖿𑖝𑖨𑖽 𑖭𑖽𑖠𑖯𑖨𑖧𑖰𑖝𑖲𑖽 𑖀𑖠𑖰𑖎𑖴𑖝𑖺𑖭𑖿𑖝𑖰𑗂 𑖀𑖢𑖰 𑖓, 𑖡𑖰𑖧𑖡𑖿𑖝𑖿𑖨𑖜-𑖫𑖳𑖡𑖿𑖧𑖯𑖭𑖲 𑖢𑖨𑖰𑖭𑖿𑖞𑖰𑖝𑖰𑖬𑖲 𑖀𑖡𑖿𑖧𑖭𑖿𑖦𑖰𑖡𑖿 𑖕𑖱𑖪𑖎𑖺𑖢𑖯𑖨𑖿𑖕𑖡𑖯𑖥𑖯𑖪𑖸 𑖪𑖴𑖟𑖿𑖠𑖯𑖪𑖭𑖿𑖞𑖯𑖧𑖯𑖽, 𑖪𑖹𑖠𑖪𑖿𑖧𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖯𑖢𑖿𑖝𑖻, 𑖀𑖧𑖺𑖐𑖿𑖧𑖝𑖯𑖧𑖯𑖽, 𑖨𑖲𑖐𑖿𑖜𑖝𑖯𑖧𑖯𑖽 𑖡𑖰𑖨𑖿𑖪𑖴𑖝𑖿𑖝𑖰𑖝𑖯𑖧𑖯𑖽 𑖓 𑖭𑖝𑖿𑖧𑖯𑖦𑖿, 𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖝𑖿𑖧𑖸𑖎𑖦𑖢𑖰 𑖭𑖲𑖨𑖎𑖿𑖬𑖯𑖠𑖰𑖎𑖯𑖨𑖽 𑖭𑖡𑖿𑖠𑖯𑖨𑖧𑖝𑖰𑗂</para>
         </listitem>
         <listitem tag="(२)"><para>𑖦𑖯𑖝𑖴𑖝𑖿𑖪𑖭𑖿𑖧 𑖫𑖰𑖫𑖲𑖝𑖿𑖪𑖭𑖿𑖧 𑖓 𑖎𑖴𑖝𑖸 𑖪𑖰𑖫𑖰𑖬𑖿𑖘𑖭𑖯𑖮𑖯𑖧𑖿𑖧𑖺𑖢𑖓𑖨𑖿𑖧𑖯𑖕𑖯𑖝𑖽 𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖟𑖸𑖧𑖽 𑖥𑖪𑖰𑖝𑖯𑗂 𑖀𑖪𑖹𑖠𑖯𑖾 𑖪𑖹𑖠𑖯𑖫𑖿𑖓 𑖭𑖨𑖿𑖪𑖸𑖢𑖰 𑖤𑖯𑖩𑖯𑖾, 𑖭𑖦𑖯𑖡𑖽 𑖭𑖯𑖦𑖯𑖕𑖰𑖎𑖽 𑖭𑖽𑖨𑖎𑖿𑖬𑖜𑖽 𑖀𑖪𑖯𑖢𑖿𑖝𑖲𑖽 𑖀𑖨𑖿𑖮𑖰𑖬𑖿𑖧𑖡𑖿𑖝𑖰𑗂</para>
         </listitem>
      </orderedlist>
   </article>
   <article number="26"><title>𑖀𑖡𑖲𑖓𑖿𑖔𑖸𑖟𑖾 26</title>
      <orderedlist><listitem tag="(१)"><para>𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖝𑖿𑖧𑖸𑖎𑖦𑖢𑖰 𑖕𑖡𑖾 𑖫𑖰𑖎𑖿𑖬𑖯𑖠𑖰𑖎𑖯𑖨𑖽 𑖭𑖽𑖠𑖝𑖿𑖝𑖸𑗂 𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖯𑖞𑖦𑖰𑖎𑖸𑖬𑖲, 𑖦𑖻𑖩𑖰𑖎𑖭𑖿𑖝𑖨𑖸𑖬𑖲 𑖓 𑖫𑖰𑖎𑖿𑖬𑖯 𑖡𑖰𑖾𑖫𑖲𑖩𑖿𑖎𑖯 𑖪𑖨𑖿𑖝𑖰𑖝𑖯𑗂 𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖯𑖞𑖦𑖰𑖎𑖱 𑖫𑖰𑖎𑖿𑖬𑖯 𑖀𑖡𑖰𑖪𑖯𑖨𑖿𑖧𑖯 𑖥𑖪𑖰𑖝𑖯𑗂 𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖯𑖪𑖰𑖠𑖰𑖎𑖱 𑖪𑖿𑖧𑖯𑖪𑖭𑖯𑖧𑖰𑖎𑖱 𑖓 𑖫𑖰𑖎𑖿𑖬𑖯 𑖭𑖯𑖦𑖯𑖡𑖿𑖧𑖝𑖧𑖯 𑖄𑖢𑖢𑖯𑖟𑖧𑖰𑖬𑖿𑖧𑖝𑖸, 𑖄𑖓𑖿𑖓𑖝𑖨𑖫𑖰𑖎𑖿𑖬𑖯 𑖓, 𑖭𑖨𑖿𑖪𑖸𑖬𑖯𑖦𑖢𑖰 𑖎𑖴𑖝𑖸 𑖧𑖺𑖐𑖿𑖧𑖝𑖯𑖠𑖯𑖨𑖸𑖜 𑖭𑖦𑖯𑖡𑖨𑖳𑖢𑖸𑖜 𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖯𑖢𑖿𑖧𑖯 𑖥𑖪𑖰𑖝𑖯𑗂</para>
         </listitem>
         <listitem tag="(२)"><para>𑖫𑖰𑖎𑖿𑖬𑖹𑖬𑖯 𑖦𑖯𑖡𑖪𑖱𑖧 𑖪𑖿𑖧𑖎𑖿𑖝𑖰𑖝𑖿𑖪𑖭𑖿𑖧 𑖭𑖨𑖿𑖪𑖯𑖽𑖐𑖱𑖜-𑖪𑖰𑖎𑖯𑖭𑖽 𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖝𑖰 𑖡𑖰𑖨𑖿𑖟𑖰𑖬𑖿𑖘𑖯 𑖥𑖪𑖰𑖝𑖯 𑖀𑖢𑖰 𑖓𑖹𑖬𑖯 𑖦𑖻𑖩𑖰𑖎𑖭𑖿𑖪𑖯𑖝𑖡𑖿𑖝𑖿𑖨𑖿𑖧𑖯𑖜𑖯𑖽 𑖦𑖯𑖡𑖪𑖯𑖠𑖰𑖎𑖯𑖨𑖯𑖜𑖯𑖽 𑖓 𑖎𑖴𑖝𑖸 𑖭𑖦𑖿𑖦𑖯𑖡-𑖭𑖽𑖪𑖨𑖿𑖠𑖰𑖎𑖯 𑖥𑖪𑖰𑖝𑖯𑗂 𑖭𑖨𑖿𑖪𑖸𑖭𑖿𑖪𑖢𑖰 𑖨𑖯𑖬𑖿𑖘𑖿𑖨𑖸𑖬𑖲 𑖕𑖯𑖝𑖱𑖧𑖸𑖬𑖲 𑖠𑖯𑖨𑖿𑖦𑖰𑖎𑖸𑖬𑖲-𑖪𑖯 𑖪𑖨𑖿𑖐𑖸𑖬𑖲 𑖫𑖰𑖎𑖿𑖬𑖹𑖬𑖯𑗂 𑖭𑖏𑖿𑖧𑖭𑖮𑖰𑖬𑖿𑖜𑖲𑖝𑖯-𑖭𑖟𑖿𑖥𑖯𑖪-𑖭𑖽𑖪𑖨𑖿𑖠𑖰𑖎𑖯 𑖪𑖨𑖿𑖝𑖿𑖝𑖰𑖝𑖯𑗂 𑖀𑖢𑖰 𑖓𑖹𑖬𑖯, 𑖫𑖯𑖡𑖿𑖝𑖰-𑖭𑖽𑖠𑖯𑖨𑖜𑖯𑖨𑖿𑖞𑖽 𑖭𑖽𑖧𑖲𑖎𑖿𑖝 𑖨𑖯𑖬𑖿𑖘𑖿𑖨𑖭𑖽𑖑𑖭𑖿𑖧 𑖎𑖯𑖨𑖿𑖧𑖯𑖜𑖰 𑖂𑖝𑖺𑖢𑖿𑖧𑖐𑖿𑖨𑖸 𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖭𑖯𑖨𑖧𑖰𑖬𑖿𑖧𑖝𑖰𑗂</para>
         </listitem>
         <listitem tag="(३)"><para>𑖤𑖯𑖩𑖯𑖡𑖯𑖽 𑖎𑖴𑖝𑖸 𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖟𑖸𑖧𑖯𑖽 𑖫𑖰𑖎𑖿𑖬𑖯𑖽 𑖓𑖸𑖝𑖲𑖽 𑖢𑖰𑖝𑖨𑖻 𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖯𑖞𑖦𑖿𑖧𑖯𑖠𑖴𑖝𑖽 𑖀𑖠𑖰𑖎𑖯𑖨𑖽 𑖠𑖯𑖨𑖧𑖝𑖾𑗂</para>
         </listitem>
      </orderedlist>
   </article>
   <article number="27"><title>𑖀𑖡𑖲𑖓𑖿𑖔𑖸𑖟𑖾 27</title>
      <orderedlist><listitem tag="(१)"><para>𑖪𑖰𑖪𑖰𑖠𑖎𑖩𑖯𑖡𑖯𑖽 𑖁𑖡𑖡𑖿𑖟-𑖭𑖡𑖿𑖟𑖺𑖮𑖦𑖡𑖲𑖥𑖪𑖰𑖝𑖲𑖽 𑖪𑖹𑖕𑖿𑖗𑖯𑖡𑖰𑖎𑖺-𑖢𑖩𑖭𑖿𑖠𑖱𑖡𑖯𑖽 𑖩𑖯𑖥𑖯𑖡𑖿 𑖓 𑖭𑖽𑖪𑖰𑖥𑖎𑖿𑖝𑖲𑖽 𑖪𑖰𑖥𑖰𑖡𑖿𑖡𑖯𑖡𑖯𑖽 𑖭𑖦𑖲𑖟𑖯𑖧𑖯𑖡𑖯𑖽 𑖭𑖯𑖽𑖭𑖿𑖎𑖴𑖝𑖰𑖎-𑖕𑖱𑖪𑖡𑖸 𑖓 𑖭𑖿𑖪𑖝𑖡𑖿𑖝𑖿𑖨𑖝𑖧𑖯 𑖭𑖮𑖧𑖺𑖎𑖿𑖝𑖲𑖽 𑖭𑖨𑖿𑖪𑖺𑖢𑖰 𑖕𑖡𑖾 𑖀𑖠𑖰𑖎𑖯𑖨𑖧𑖲𑖝𑖺𑖭𑖿𑖝𑖰𑗂</para>
         </listitem>
         <listitem tag="(२)"><para>𑖎𑖭𑖿𑖧𑖯𑖢𑖰 𑖪𑖹𑖕𑖿𑖗𑖯𑖡𑖰𑖎-𑖭𑖯𑖮𑖰𑖝𑖿𑖧𑖰𑖎-𑖎𑖩𑖯𑖝𑖿𑖦𑖎𑖯𑖡𑖯𑖽 𑖡𑖰𑖨𑖿𑖦𑖯𑖜𑖯𑖡𑖯𑖽, 𑖧𑖭𑖿𑖧𑖯𑖭𑖻 𑖨𑖓𑖧𑖰𑖝𑖯𑖭𑖿𑖝𑖰, 𑖡𑖹𑖝𑖰𑖎𑖯𑖡𑖯𑖽 𑖪𑖭𑖿𑖝𑖲𑖐𑖝𑖯𑖡𑖯𑖽 𑖮𑖰𑖝𑖯𑖡𑖯𑖽 𑖭𑖽𑖨𑖎𑖿𑖬𑖜𑖯𑖨𑖿𑖞𑖽 𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖝𑖿𑖧𑖸𑖎𑖽 𑖕𑖡𑖺𑖠𑖰𑖎𑖯𑖨𑖽 𑖭𑖽𑖠𑖝𑖿𑖝𑖸𑗂</para>
         </listitem>
      </orderedlist>
   </article>
   <article number="28"><title>𑖀𑖡𑖲𑖓𑖿𑖔𑖸𑖟𑖾 28</title>
      <para>𑖀𑖭𑖿𑖧𑖯𑖽 𑖀𑖥𑖰𑖑𑖺𑖬𑖜𑖯𑖧𑖯𑖽 𑖡𑖰𑖨𑖿𑖟𑖰𑖬𑖿𑖘𑖯𑖡𑖯𑖽 𑖀𑖠𑖰𑖎𑖯𑖨𑖯𑖜𑖯𑖽 𑖭𑖿𑖪𑖯𑖝𑖡𑖿𑖝𑖿𑖨𑖿𑖧𑖯𑖜𑖯𑖽 𑖓 𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖯𑖢𑖿𑖝𑖧𑖸 𑖭𑖯𑖦𑖯𑖕𑖰𑖎𑖯𑖡𑖿𑖝𑖯𑖨𑖯𑖬𑖿𑖘𑖿𑖨𑖰𑖎-𑖪𑖿𑖧𑖪𑖭𑖿𑖞𑖯𑖧𑖯𑖽 𑖓 𑖢𑖳𑖨𑖿𑖜𑖝𑖧𑖯 𑖊𑖝𑖯𑖡𑖿 𑖀𑖠𑖰𑖐𑖡𑖿𑖝𑖲𑖽 𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖝𑖿𑖧𑖸𑖎𑖦𑖢𑖰 𑖕𑖡𑖺𑖨𑖿𑖮𑖰𑖬𑖿𑖧𑖝𑖸𑗂</para>
   </article>
   <article number="29"><title>𑖀𑖡𑖲𑖓𑖿𑖔𑖸𑖟𑖾 29</title>
      <orderedlist><listitem tag="(१)"><para>𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖝𑖿𑖧𑖸𑖎𑖽 𑖕𑖡𑖾 𑖭𑖦𑖲𑖟𑖯𑖧𑖭𑖿𑖧 𑖎𑖴𑖝𑖸 𑖎𑖨𑖿𑖝𑖪𑖿𑖧𑖟𑖯𑖧𑖰𑖝𑖿𑖪𑖽 𑖠𑖯𑖨𑖧𑖝𑖰 𑖧𑖸𑖡 𑖮𑖰 𑖭𑖿𑖪𑖱𑖧-𑖪𑖿𑖧𑖎𑖿𑖝𑖰𑖝𑖿𑖪𑖭𑖿𑖧 𑖢𑖳𑖨𑖿𑖜-𑖭𑖿𑖪𑖝𑖡𑖿𑖝𑖿𑖨-𑖪𑖰𑖎𑖯𑖭𑖾 𑖭𑖽𑖥𑖪𑖸𑖝𑖿𑗂</para>
         </listitem>
         <listitem tag="(२)"><para>𑖭𑖿𑖪𑖱𑖧𑖯𑖠𑖰𑖎𑖯𑖨-𑖭𑖿𑖪𑖯𑖝𑖡𑖿𑖝𑖿𑖨𑖿𑖧𑖯𑖜𑖯𑖽 𑖎𑖿𑖨𑖰𑖧𑖯𑖡𑖿𑖪𑖧𑖡𑖸 𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖝𑖿𑖧𑖸𑖎𑖦𑖿 𑖕𑖡𑖾, 𑖀𑖡𑖿𑖧𑖸𑖬𑖯𑖽 𑖀𑖠𑖰𑖎𑖯𑖨-𑖭𑖿𑖪𑖯𑖝𑖡𑖿𑖝𑖿𑖨𑖿𑖧𑖯𑖜𑖰 𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖝𑖰 𑖭𑖦𑖲𑖓𑖰𑖝𑖯𑖥𑖰𑖕𑖿𑖗𑖯𑖡𑖯𑖟𑖨-𑖭𑖽𑖨𑖎𑖿𑖬𑖜𑖟𑖴𑖫𑖯 𑖡𑖳𑖡𑖽 𑖪𑖿𑖧𑖪𑖮𑖨𑖰𑖬𑖿𑖧𑖝𑖰𑗂 𑖀𑖢𑖰 𑖓𑖯𑖭𑖻 𑖩𑖺𑖎𑖝𑖯𑖡𑖿𑖝𑖿𑖨𑖰𑖎-𑖭𑖦𑖯𑖕𑖸, 𑖭𑖯𑖦𑖯𑖡𑖿𑖧-𑖎𑖩𑖿𑖧𑖯𑖜𑖽 𑖭𑖯𑖨𑖿𑖪𑖕𑖡𑖰𑖎-𑖪𑖿𑖧𑖪𑖭𑖿𑖞𑖯𑖽 𑖡𑖹𑖝𑖰𑖎𑖝𑖯𑖧𑖯𑖾 𑖭𑖦𑖲𑖓𑖰𑖝𑖯𑖪𑖫𑖿𑖧𑖎𑖝𑖯𑖫𑖿𑖓 𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖝𑖰 𑖢𑖳𑖨𑖿𑖜𑖽 𑖟𑖯𑖧𑖰𑖝𑖿𑖪𑖽 𑖡𑖰𑖨𑖿𑖪𑖎𑖿𑖬𑖿𑖧𑖝𑖰𑗂</para>
         </listitem>
         <listitem tag="(३)"><para>𑖊𑖝𑖸𑖠𑖰𑖎𑖯𑖨𑖯𑖾 𑖊𑖝𑖯𑖡𑖰 𑖭𑖿𑖪𑖯𑖝𑖡𑖿𑖝𑖿𑖨𑖿𑖧𑖯𑖜𑖰 𑖓, 𑖭𑖽𑖧𑖲𑖎𑖿𑖝𑖨𑖯𑖬𑖿𑖘𑖿𑖨𑖭𑖽𑖑𑖭𑖿𑖧 𑖄𑖟𑖿𑖟𑖸𑖫𑖿𑖧𑖯𑖡𑖰 𑖭𑖰𑖟𑖿𑖠𑖯𑖡𑖿𑖝𑖯𑖡𑖿 𑖓 𑖪𑖰𑖨𑖲𑖠𑖿𑖧 𑖡 𑖎𑖞𑖦𑖢𑖰 𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖧𑖺𑖎𑖿𑖬𑖿𑖧𑖡𑖿𑖝𑖸𑗂</para>
         </listitem>
      </orderedlist>
   </article>
   <article number="30"><title>𑖀𑖡𑖲𑖓𑖿𑖔𑖸𑖟𑖾 30</title>
      <para>𑖀𑖭𑖿𑖧𑖯𑖽 𑖀𑖥𑖰𑖑𑖺𑖬𑖜𑖯𑖧𑖯𑖽 𑖡𑖰𑖨𑖿𑖟𑖰𑖬𑖿𑖘𑖯𑖡𑖯𑖽 𑖀𑖠𑖰𑖎𑖯𑖨𑖯𑖜𑖯𑖽 𑖭𑖿𑖪𑖯𑖝𑖡𑖿𑖝𑖿𑖨𑖧𑖯𑖜𑖯𑖽 𑖓 𑖡 𑖎𑖺𑖢𑖿𑖧𑖽𑖫𑖾, 𑖢𑖿𑖨𑖜𑖯𑖫-𑖩𑖎𑖿𑖬𑖿𑖧𑖯𑖠𑖯𑖨𑖸𑖜 𑖎𑖰𑖦𑖢𑖰 𑖎𑖯𑖨𑖿𑖧𑖦𑖡𑖲𑖬𑖿𑖙𑖯𑖝𑖲𑖽 𑖊𑖝𑖯𑖟𑖴𑖎𑖿𑖎𑖯𑖨𑖿𑖧𑖯𑖡𑖲𑖬𑖿𑖙𑖯𑖡𑖯𑖨𑖿𑖞𑖽 𑖪𑖯 𑖎𑖭𑖿𑖧𑖓𑖰𑖝𑖿 𑖨𑖯𑖬𑖿𑖘𑖿𑖨𑖭𑖿𑖧 𑖪𑖨𑖿𑖐𑖭𑖿𑖧 𑖕𑖡𑖭𑖿𑖧 𑖪𑖯 𑖭𑖦𑖱𑖮𑖰𑖝-𑖭𑖰𑖟𑖿𑖠𑖧𑖨𑖿𑖞𑖽 𑖀𑖡𑖿𑖧𑖞𑖯 𑖪𑖿𑖧𑖯𑖏𑖿𑖧𑖯𑖝𑖲𑖽 𑖡𑖹𑖪 𑖫𑖎𑖿𑖬𑖿𑖧𑖝𑖸𑗂</para>
   </article>
   <note><para>𑖭𑖿𑖪𑖝𑖿𑖪𑖯𑖠𑖰𑖎𑖯𑖨𑖾 1997</para>
      <para>𑖦𑖯𑖡𑖪𑖯𑖠𑖰𑖎𑖯𑖨𑖯𑖜𑖯𑖽 𑖎𑖴𑖝𑖸 𑖭𑖽𑖧𑖲𑖎𑖿𑖝𑖨𑖯𑖬𑖿𑖘𑖿𑖨𑖺𑖓𑖿𑖓𑖯𑖧𑖲𑖎𑖿𑖝𑖭𑖿𑖧 𑖎𑖯𑖨𑖿𑖧𑖯𑖩𑖧𑖾</para>
      <para>𑖕𑖰𑖡𑖸𑖪𑖯, 𑖭𑖿𑖪𑖱𑖘𑖿𑖕𑗀𑖨𑖩𑖹𑖜𑖿𑖚</para>
   </note>
</udhr>
